Chapter 503: Chase 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After a few days..

On the black plains, behind a black, giant, stone pillar.

"I'll fight with you!!"

Demon Phoenix shouted and leaped over. Suddenly, a fierce, strange, purple halo lit up. Numerous purple, one-eyed shadows slowly lit up behind her.

Chiiii!!

Before the shadows could completely materialize, they were punctured by a cloud of black air, like a balloon being poked.

Demon Phoenix who leaped over was grabbed by the face by Garen. She was tossed onto the ground with a bang. A few meters long pit directly opened up on the ground, swallowing the two people. Lots of smoke rose up, forming grey clouds instantly. The situation within couldn't be seen clearly.

"Your body structure is interesting. I won't eat you for the moment. Don't worry." Garen retrieved his hand and coughed. Blood flowed out from the corner of his mouth. He continued to close his eyes and rest.

Nowadays he didn't even skin the creatures. He ate them whole. Every day, he needed to eat more than ten gigantic creatures like the black elephants, as nutrients for the Nine-Headed Hydra to regenerate limbs.

Demon Phoenix and the rest got more and more scared. They could roughly guess the reasons Garen brought them along. On one hand, maybe he needed someone to serve him. On the other hand, most likely they were there as backup rations for him.

After being in emotional turmoil for a few days, finally, her hopelessness caused her to muster up the courage.

Under the plans of her three subordinates, Demon Phoenix finally found an opportunity. Garen came back today severely injured as usual. The left side of his body was completely gone. Demon Phoenix took advantage of this opportunity for a sudden attack. And then, she was still unexpectedly suppressed...

Naturally, the decision for Garen to capture Demon Phoenix wasn't a casual one.

In the midst of the battle between the Nine-Headed Hydra's will and the Cthulhu King, he used the aura of the Black Water True Technique to sense the area. He unexpectedly noticed the presence of several unique lives. One of the unique ones was the Demon Phoenix.

After careful investigation, the blood in the Demon Phoenix's body contained an ancient aura similar to the ancient Nine-Headed Hydra's will. This surprised him. Since it wasn't much of a burden, he caught the four of them as he left.

As expected, Demon Phoenix was a creature with a long lifespan. This was definitely a good news to him.

Although luminarists had different methods to lengthen their lives, according to the royal records, the longest lifespan of the strongest totem user was about 400 years. Although different methods were used, one of the most effective methods was converting life force into totems. This was the method that the Cthulhus of the Cthulhuism Society used to become Cthulhus. However, even the Cthulhu totems had a limit to their lifespan.

It was the number 400.

This was the limit of one's lifespan.

After Garen felt Demon Phoenix's ancient aura, he immediately captured the four of them for research on the secrets of longevity.

After a moment of silence, Demon Phoenix crawled to her feet. The courage that she had had completely disappeared. She and her three subordinates squatted at one side, feeling discouraged. They began sewing simple clothes for Garen using animal skins, bones plus some long feathered birds that they caught recently. To make simple disposal clothes weren't difficult.

Demon Phoenix had been enduring for more than a thousand years. No one was stronger than her in carrying a burden. It was the same when she met Sage Osaka previously. Once she couldn't defeat him, she instantly repented. Since she had a long lifespan, as long she lived longer than others, time would help her defeat her strongest enemy. She never thought that before his death, Osaka would seal her for thousands of years.

But that was before. Previously, she wasn't good with her mind. After thousands of years of hard work, her mind was much more active than before.

Demon Phoenix's eyes were glowing. She was thinking how to escape that monster's claws. The man was as strong as Osaka during the old days. But no matter how strong someone is, they would still have weaknesses.

"My Lord! I have an idea!" The purple-armored girl whispered.

"What's your plan? Say." Demon Phoenix quietly walked towards her.

"As long as we obediently listen to the man, he might not eat us. After a few hundred years, after he dies of old age, we can regain our freedom. As long as we perform better this time and don't get sealed, the Osaka incident won't repeat!" The purple-armored girl said with certainty.

"Good idea!" Demon Phoenix knocked her fists. Although not using her brain for thousands of years made it slow, but she didn't think so.

"We shall compete with him to see who lives longer!" The two others gathered around as well. "All elites also need subordinates. As long as we are obedient, we definitely wouldn't be in danger!"

From the other side, Garen opened his eyes and glanced at the four of them. Without uttering a word, he closed them again.

Removing the aura of ancient elites, the four of them were lunatics. Most likely they used to rely on brute force to solve problems. Since brute force couldn't solve the problem at hand, they were completely clueless.

After resting for a moment, a mild tremor came from the distance.

Garen glanced at it then raise his hands. Large amounts of black gas were emitted, surrounding all of them.

"Let's go!"

The five of them leaped to the sky, forming a bundle of black cloud, then headed towards the wave in the distance.

The mutated creatures that were kept captive on the ground quickly ran away like they were being amnestied.

*************

Another few days passed by.

On the grassy plains, the stars in the night sky were glittering silver. The jade-white crescent moon quietly glowed in the sky, surrounded by lingering clouds.

Garen's party started a campfire on the grassy plains. They could clearly be seen, like a yellow chess piece on a black chess board. White smoke billowed upwards. The smoke swayed after being blown by the wind. It dissipated then disappeared.

"What is this place?" Garen sat beside the campfire. He casually asked as he was fiddling with the fire. As soon as he asked, he realized that it wasn't probable that Demon Phoenix would know their current location. Hence he kept quiet.

"Not...Not sure…" Demon Phoenix answered carefully. She had already accepted her fate. After making sure that Garen wouldn't eat her, she used her ultimate technique - endure.

After enduring for thousands of years, enduring another few hundred years wouldn't be a huge problem. Compared to before, she could still see new sceneries around. It was evident that the current treatment she received was much better.

Garen gave her a glance.

"Do you know how to retract the parts of your body that are not human-like?"

"I know! I know I know!" Demon Phoenix quickly nodded. After these few days, she was afraid of being beaten up. She obediently listened and accepted herself as Garen's servant.

After some adjustments, Demon Phoenix and the rest retracted their abnormalities. All of them looked like normal humans.

Her three subordinates, two men, and a woman dispersed their armor. They reformed the armor to become clothes like ones Garen wore. They also revealed their faces that they had previously hidden.

The purple-armored girl changed into a purple robe. She was Demon Phoenix's top general, called Phantom. Her looks and figure were indescribable. She was an absolute beauty. Her appearance was gentle. It was only her strange, heavy, voice that could give anyone a scare.

The other two men looked about the same. They were beautiful and pure, with long purple hair. From their appearance, it was difficult to recognize that they were men. They didn't even have facial hair. If it wasn't for their Adam's apple or the lack of a protruding chest, just by their beautiful face and graceful figure, no one would know that they were men.

Their two names were relatively strange, Lata and Tala.

Demon Phoenix explained that initially, her main criteria for choosing subordinates had been beauty.

After the four of them joked around for a few times, they could be considered obedient. Since they were free while pursuing the Cthulhu King, Garen asked Demon Phoenix about the situation of the place she was from.

"Osaka used to be a region of chaos. There were a total of five countries. We lived there since we were born. The people there consecrated us and worshipped us as gods. After that, Osaka appeared and killed many of my servants and subordinates. After defeating us in the end, I do not know why she didn't kill me. Before her death, she sealed me up until now. I think after the death of Osaka's man, she herself no longer wanted to live. I am not very sure of the reason."

Demon Phoenix illogically talked about her past.

Her subordinates were carefully barbecuing some food. They also used some roots of plants that they had dug out to make soup.

The grassy plains were abnormally quiet. They only sound that could be heard was the faint wolf howls from the distance.

After the nest leaders recruited large amounts of strong monsters, the ones that remained outside were stupid or weak ones. Even the nest leaders did not consider them as one of their own.

For fifth form elites, if they were willing, as long as they didn't hide their presence, it would be sufficient to scare away almost all the monsters. But this was a little tricky for Garen. He couldn't replenish sufficient potential points without sufficient strong creatures.

Fortunately, he already had some rough ideas about the path of the Cthulhu King's martial arts.

The key reason he was superior to the martial artists of this world, was his understanding towards martial arts. With the support of the level of the previous world, he was able to reach terrifying heights.

This had nothing to with the realm that he was in. It was merely based on experience.

He had studied large amounts of martial arts in the martial arts world. At this point, his progress of deciphering the Cthulhu King's Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel was faster than the Cthulhu King expected.

One he could derive the complete demonic art, absorbing the Cthulhu's Origin would no longer be a problem.

After casually chatting with Demon Phoenix and the rest, he ordered them to be on guard. They would inform him once they notice something going on with the Cthulhu King.

He laid on the grass and gradually fell asleep. Even though his Black Water True Technique had strong stamina, the terrifying consumption due to two months of continuous battles and pursuit with no rest in the middle has pushed him to his limit.

Once he closed his eyes, he no longer wanted to open it. HIs weariness flooded him instantly like a tide.

He slept for an unknown period of time. As he opened his eyes, it was bright.

The sky was too bright. A rich, potato soup-like fragrance entered his nostrils.

Garen felt his brain hurt as he slowly sat up. He saw Demon Phoenix and Phantom busy cooking soup, while Lata and Tala were squatting on the ground. They were washing some leafy plants.

The sky was white and the wind that blew by was a little cooling.

As he stood upon the grassy plains, Garen looked towards the Cthulhu King from afar. There was no movement over there. It was obvious that he was also getting a little rest for one night.

He relied on the attribute bonuses of his body, his incredible martial arts realm, in addition to the Troll Grip and others, to be able to imitate the battling ability of a peak fifth form although he was merely at the lower level of fifth form. In actual fact, he was competing all these while.

Garen also had a clear positioning of his full strength.

Among peak fifth form, he was the weakest. In his battle with God Cloud, not to mention that God Cloud was already injured beforehand. After such a long pursuit, the other party managed to escape so far away although he was bringing along another person with him.

After that, the Cthulhu King was even more extreme. Everytime his attack hit, it would mean injury or even death. If the Black Water True Technique didn't gather on the surface of his body, he couldn't even break his defense, not to mention heavily injure him. Gathering the Black Water True Technique on his hands and legs like before wouldn't work at all. It was too weak.

Until today, although the Cthulhu King had an Immortal Body, he didn't even die once. In other words, by merely injuring him, the consumption of Cthulhu's Origin for the other party was not even worth mentioning.

Meanwhile, he himself had died for more than twenty times and been severely injured for more than thirty times. If it wasn't for his nine-life talent which could be replenished with potential points, in addition to the terrifying regenerative ability of the Nine-Headed Hydra, he simply did not qualify to fight his opponent until this stage.

Although by successfully suppressed the temperament of the Nine-Headed Hydra, he'd managed to increase his strength significantly, he was still much weaker as compared to the Cthulhu King.

After giving more thought, the Cthulhu King was oppressed by Phiroth. Without the glittering water, he would flee once he saw Phiroth.

Garen was making the comparisons in his mind. Finally, he positioned his strength on the level of the Lord of Royal Star Court. The Lord of Royal Star Court could hold his own against God Cloud with the Distorted Beads. Although he was slightly disadvantaged, he was still a true peak fifth form.

As the boss of the Geometry Service, his abilities were among the top three strongest in the Three Departments. Even if the Elder Council was included, he would still be top five. The Elder Council was a giant force across the East and West Continents, gathering all the top-notch elites.

Chapter 504: Chase 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Of course, they should be only four to five peak fifth form. Phiroth was definitely one of them. The bosses of the Three Departments were also definitely in the peak realm. Also the Director of the Parliament, who might be still alive. In the original history, the old man had been killed by Hellgate underground.

Once he thought of Hellgate, Garen shuddered. Looking at the time, it was about time for Hellgate's birth.

As he was busy battling the Cthulhu King and learning his martial arts, he actually forgot such a big matter. After all, fighting with an elite on the Cthulhu King's level requires complete concentration. Otherwise, once he slipped up, he would be completely put in a tough spot. No matter how many lives he had, the outcome was death.

After eating the soup and meat, Garen sat on one side. He looked towards the Cthulhu King's direction. There were clouds of smoke. It was obvious that he was cooking something. The Cthulhu King was obviously not as laid back as himself.

After searching his body for a moment, then only Garen remembered that his belongings were fully destroyed during his battles over this period of time.

As black clouds gathered below his feet, he slowly ascended higher and higher.

Demon Phoenix and the others below didn't dare to say much. They obediently stood in their positions, cleaning up the mess.

As the people below seemed smaller and smaller, his vision grew wider and wider.

As Garen slowly ascended, he swept his gaze over the grassy plains.

Very quickly, ten kilometers away, smoke from a bonfire was rising.

With a stomp of his feet, the black gas surrounded him and shot out towards the back. It headed in that direction like a meteorite.

On the Cthulhu King's side, there was some slight movement. But in the end, he stopped and didn't take that opportunity to leave.

Garen approached the position of the bonfire. From afar, he could see that on the side of the winding river, three human figures that looked like adventurers stood up and looked towards him as if a great enemy was coming. They already wielded weapons in their hands. Two wild boar totems with white spikes were also being summoned.

The three adventurers, two men, and one woman were in dark brown cotton armor. Their faces look weather-beaten. Evidently, they had been walking on the grassy plains for quite some time.

As Garen approached, then only the three of them saw that within the black gas was actually a young man. Unexpectedly, there was eagerness and warmth glowed in their eyes.

"Strong totem user, do you need any assistance?" Seeing that the other party was a man, the woman out of the three stood up and spoke. Usually, the opposite gender would be easier to get acquainted.

"Do you have a radio?" Since the other party was speaking pure Kovitan language, Garen directly replied with Kovitan language.

"Radio? Yes, yes yes!" The woman asked her companion to take out a white-silver square box. There was even a gold antenna on top. There was a knob to change channels in the middle. Basically, there weren't many differences from Earth's radios.

Garen grabbed it with one hand. A white stream of water instantly grabbed the radio over. It steadily landed on his plan with a clap.

As he was about to throw out a few Rumbs, Garen suddenly remembered that his wallet was totally destroyed in the battles. Suddenly, there was a sense of hesitation in his expression.

"Strong totem user, it is just a radio. Don't take it to heart." The woman looked about twenty years of age. She didn't seem to mingle much with aristocrats. The way she spoke was a little stiff.

"What is this place?" Gaern suddenly asked.

"Er… This is the Blue Jade Plains, between the Ultimate Protection and the hundreds of countries of the North." The woman quickly answered.

"What are you doing here?"

"We were initially hunting down a Four-Ear Fox on the plains. We accidentally got lost…" The girl laughed bitterly.

"In that case, this place is quite close to the Ultimate Protection, Kovitan?"

"Yes, My Lord."

Garen nodded. Suddenly, with a snap of his fingers, a stream of black gas shot out, leaving a black line in the air.

Very quickly, a pitiful shriek came from afar. After a while, a cloud of black gas was returning with a white fox-like creature. The fox had golden eyes and six limbs. As it was struggling non-stop within the gas, it let out sharp shrieks.

"This is your reward." Garen pointed with his finger. The black gas surrounding the small fox descended and landed in front of the three of them. The fox who was initially struggling was pierced in mid-air by the black gas. The black gas entered through one of its ears and exited from the other. The fox's body became numb and stopped moving completely.

"Six-Limb White Fox!! It is actually a Six-Limb White Fox!" The three people couldn't hold back their cries. This fox was obviously worth something.

"With this Six-Limb White Fox, we no longer need to catch a Four-Ear Fox!" "There is hope for father's sickness!"

As the three of them finished reacting and were ready to thank Garen, there was no longer anyone in the air.

As he returned to the camp, Garen landed and placed the radio on the ground. He switched it on and adjusted it to the Daniela channel that he remembered.

Although he was nearer to Kovitan, when he left, Kovitan's news channel still wasn't set up. He could only remember the one from Daniela.

Demon Phoenix and the rest stared at the small, white-silver box curiously. They didn't know what was it for.

"Sheesh….Oaz! Oaz!"

"Fast fast fast! Focus on this side! This side!!" "That is Edney's giant statue, the giant statue is on the move! Looks like the demonstration has reached the government's tolerance limit." There was a flurry of footsteps and a hurried man's voice came from the radio. There were also numerous people shouting in one accord.

"This is Edney's Cassadan City. It is 11:32 in the morning. The procession has already begun to confront the armed government. If things don't turn around, there might be another bloodshed."

Garen blinked his eyes and changed the channel to another news portal from Daniela. So happen, it was interval music.

He steadied the radio and sat on one side to rest as he was listening to the news.

A gentle female announcer was reporting the recent happenings. Most of it was unimportant matters. A mine somewhere collapsed, killing some people. The progress of the international census. The breakthrough in the research of the domestication of mutated creatures.

Demon Phoenix and the rest were abnormally curious. As they were busy doing their tasks, they were eavesdropping on the radio. Although they completely couldn't understand the Daniela language used, it didn't stop them from being curious towards the talking box.

The sky started to brighten up. Until about 2 o'clock in the afternoon, the Cthulhu King still didn't show any intention of leaving. Garen decided to go later in the day to test his martial arts. He wanted to understand the recent happenings first.

"....There was a secret gathering among East continents society in the Ye Qin Mountains a few days ago. Many elite societies and associations gathered in the black stone ruins of the giant cathedral to share their knowledge and experience. There was skirmish during the gathering which caused ten severe injuries and fifteen deaths. Among them were the leaders of the Terraflor Society, the Sisley Couple. The cause of the incident is still under investigation."

Garen suddenly opened his eyes. There was a hint of heaviness on his face.

"Sisley...Terraflor Society…"

The voice continued.

"The biggest terrorist organization, the Obscuro Society was declared to be responsible. King Phiroth released a statement where any challenge against peace was a challenge against Daniela. A heavy blow has to be delivered towards the Obscuro Society's rampant activities.

The new continued but Garen no longer wanted to listen. He turned off the radio. Although his heart was heavy, there was also a glimmer of hope in him.

Hellgate….The man that surpassed the limits of the world. Just by thinking how strong he was, it agitated people.

"Must speed up the progress." Garen stood up. His body slowly melted to become a cloud of black gas, which shot out towards the distance.

He covered about ten kilometers in a few breaths.

On the grassy plains, the Cthulhu King in red robes instantly opened his eyes. He gathered a red lightning spear in his hand and threw it over.

Crack.

Lightning flashed and thunder roared. The red lightning collided with the black cloud meteor. With a bang, a circle of transparent ripples diffused out on the ground. As though it was seawater, there were clear ripple lines on the grassy plains.

The dense white clouds in the sky were immediately scattered. A hole was created and golden sunlight shined through the hole, forming an eye-catching, golden beam of light.

Within the black cloud and red lightning, two blurs shot out, a black one and a red one. They collided, becoming a black-red meteor which crashed fiercely towards the ground.

Bang!

A pit was instantly formed on the ground. It was more than a hundred meters wide and more than ten meters deep. Garen's expression didn't change. His arms pierced outwards to his two sides, penetrating two red light beams that were coming towards him.

Battling until now, he no longer had any fixed form. The Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills slowly evolved, removing the unnecessary portions to become more and more refined. He also merged it the bits and pieces of some of the techniques that he invented in this world.

After he penetrated the two light beams, Garen turned to his side, extending his right leg like a whip. The black glow on the tip of his foot could clearly be seen.

In the pit, there was a light crack. A black crescent suddenly lit up, passing by the Cthulhu King's chest, then quickly disappeared.

"You!!" The Cthulhu King stared at Garen as if he was staring at a ghost. He was in complete disbelief.

Although the Black Crescent Leg Knife didn't touch him, traces of black lightning arcs strangely lingered on his chest. The lightning arc waves were abnormally familiar. It was very similar to his Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel.

Although it didn't cause any damage to him, this attack caused an unconcealable coldness the Cthulhu King's heart. As he looked at the man in front of him, he reflexively thought of that tyrannical man at the Ancestral God Tree. The two of them were so similar. The familiar coldness was rising in the Cthulhu King's heart.

"Light of Ten Thousand Laws!" The Cthulhu King bellowed. He finally used his strongest ability to date.

In the sky, the golden sun turned red in an instant. A red light dot fell out from the center of the sun. It grew faster and faster, bigger and bigger.

From the size of a sesame seed, it grew into the size of a fingernail. Very quickly, it became a giant red light beam that almost covered the whole sky.

There was no sound and no tremor.

The giant light beam of over a hundred meters suddenly descended. Together with the Cthulhu King, it wrapped Garen and submerged the both of them in a terrifying, high-temperature beam.

Chapter 505: Humbled 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The red light beam pierced the heavens and earth. It was like a red giant jade pillar that stood tall on the grassy plains. It penetrated the clouds. As the sun shone through the hole in the clouds onto the beam, there was a rapid flowing air-flow like movement.

The beam lasted for a few minutes before becoming narrower, lighter and eventually disappeared completely.

Beneath the beam, there was a pitch black hole in the ground. There was only darkness within the hole, and it seemed bottomless. Only traces of white smoke and black gas came from within.

Piak!

A hand suddenly stretched out, grabbing the soil on the sides of the hole. As the fingers bent, the five fingers were like sharp claws, penetrating deep into the soil instantly.

Two dark figures were hanging on the sides of the hole. One of them held onto the soil with one hand, while the other was hanging onto the former's right leg. Both of them hung on the wall of the hole. From time to time they would sway, like a pendant on the wall being blown by the wind.

Garen grabbed onto the Cthulhu King's right leg with all his might. His left arm was gone, while his two legs had also exploded, almost becoming a stick-man[1]. However, he was grinning, revealing white teeth as sharp as the teeth of a saw.

Woooooo~~~~

A desolate horn cry came from afar. It was distant and dull.

In the white sky, numerous dark red dots were heading over from the distance. Each of the dots was actually a dark red Dual-Headed Salamander. Each of them had a salamander-like body, and a pair of wings made out of flesh on its back. An extra head grew from the center of each of their chests.

On each of the Dual-Headed Salamanders' back was a strong, horned warrior. Some of them were swinging heavy metal flails. Some of them raised black crossbows, while some of them gathered balls of dark red flames with their hands.

The sky was slowly occupied by the red dots. The numerous dark red Dual-Headed Salamanders were like flies, hovering over the sky. The golden sunlight projected down to form a bright beam.

More and more Dual-Headed Salamanders gathered around the golden beam. They circled around the golden beam and roared.

Ming!!~~~~~~

The horn sounded again.

The Dual-Headed Salamanders hovered over their heads, completely surrounding the two of them.

"You are definitely going to die…!" The Cthulhu King stared fiercely at Garen. He saw his opponent smiling instead, not panicking at all.

"You've almost finished your Origin isn't it?" Garen laughed and asked casually.

"I wouldn't die before you." The Cthulhu King let out a cold laugh. However, he was trembling in his heart. He had actually used up his Cthulhu's Origin significantly. After taking the glittering water plus using the Cthulhu's Origin, then only he managed to recover the injuries to his spirit. He really wasn't left with much. He only had three chances at reviving. If he died here once...If he faced Phiroth in the future, victory was unpredictable.

This was one of the reasons he didn't kill himself voluntarily to return to the headquarters.

"Your regenerative abilities should be finishing as well?" The Cthulhu King did not reveal the changes in his heart. He coldly laughed and asked instead.

"Who knows?" Garen laughed and stopped speaking.

Quietly, on the contact point where he was grabbing the Cthulhu King's leg, there was a fight going on between black sticky liquid and red jade stone-like shell.

The black light and red light were slowly blooming. It was abnormally striking on the sides of the pitch black hole.

In actual fact, both of them didn't have much energy remaining, but both didn't want to admit defeat. Until this stage, regardless of whether the Cthulhu King was willing, his subconscious already considered Garen as his biggest rival other than of Phiroth.

　　*******************

Screams, hoof sounds and the roars of the dual-headed flying dragons..

The grassy plains were in chaos.

Large crowds of flying dragons and black knights rushed into the white circular tribe. They were like an unstoppable black tide. Each swipe of their machetes would cut off a head. Blood spilled all over the ground, dyeing the grassy plains in red.

At the door of the white tribe, two men in smart, black suits stood still on the ground, looking at the massacre happening in the tribe.

"The Thirteenth Tribe on the grassy plains. Other than Ramstead, the others are merely preys before the sharp eagle claws." One of the men had sharp eyes. There was a white beard on his chin which swayed to the left in the wind.

"This is the consequence of not obeying the Wolf Tribe." His voice was cold, without any warmth. "On the grassy plains, everything belongs to the Atria Alliance."

Before he finished speaking, there was a crisp noise. A white boomerang was spinning rapidly, heading towards his head.

The sides of the boomerang were incredibly sharp. There were some remnants of blood on the boomerang. There was an intense howling sound as it spun.

The boomerang passed the neck of a black knight in its way. With a poof that brought along a bloody smell, a head that was still laughing flew off.

The boomerang, with the power of a recent murder, headed towards the black-robed man with a cold voice.

Dang!

The black man abruptly raised his arm and blocked the boomerang heads-on. Golden sparks splattered from the clash between his arm and the boomerang. Surprisingly, the collision between flesh and metal could emit the sound of clashing metal.

Looking over at the direction where the boomerang originated, there was a squad of white knights protecting two youths, allowing them to retreat into the distance. The surrounding black knights and flying dragons leaped over but were all killed or knocked back by the boomerangs.

There was a knight in full white armor. He wore a white-silver helmet that only revealed his eyes. In his hand was a giant sword enchanted with white electric arcs. With every swing, a black knight would be chopped down. The Dual-Headed Flying Dragons didn't dare to approach. Once the white electric touched them from afar, their bodies would become numb. They would fall to the ground, quickly emitting black smoke, eventually becoming black ash.

The white-bearded leader in black robes looked at the gradually departing white knights. He slowly let out a faint smile.

"Gulaman! I'll go and kill them!" The one with the cold voice was asking to be sent into battle.

"Patience…" Through the gaps among the white knights, the white-bearded man saw the two people being protected.

It was a boy and a girl. Both of them were not more than thirteen, fourteen years of age. They were dressed luxuriously in a white bandana on their heads. On the bandana was a green gemstone.

The two children had fair skin and pretty faces. The boy was like a delicate porcelain doll. The girl's long hair draped over her shoulder. Her tight clothing revealed her tiny waist. She had red lips and white teeth. Her watery eyes were red and swollen.

"Looks like I will have some good stuff tonight." The white-bearded man stroke his beard, looking satisfied.

"Gulaman, let me go capture them for you!"

"I want that boy. It's been a while since I've seen someone so fair." The white-bearded man nodded.

"Er…." The other person was a little shocked. This Gulaman's preference…..He initially thought he wanted to capture the little girl, he never thought….As he glanced at the calm white-bearded man, there was an uncontrollable coldness in his heart.

　　*******************

"Sister! Don't bother about me! Run!!" The little boy Lajay shouted at the top of his lungs. He continuously struggled. Yet he was still clamped between the armpits of a black knight leader. He was being brought towards the direction of the two black-robed leaders.

"It's an honor to be chosen by Lord Gulaman! Treat the old man well and you might live!"

The black knight leader laughed.

Larain was being held in one hand by a white knight. She stretched out her hands and looked in tears towards the direction of her brother. The white knights around them were protecting them as they retreated into the distance. However, the black knights behind were like wolves that fixed their eyes on raw meat. They were not going to let them go.

From the gap between the helmet and the neck of the white knight, there was red blood flowing downwards, dying his breastplate in red. However, his posture did not change.

"Princess Rain. Do not let His Majesty, Jay sacrifice in vain!" A determined voice came from beneath the helmet.

"Let me go let me go! I want to save my brother! Let go! Let go…" Larain knocked on the white knight's breastplate. She didn't even realize that her hands were being scratched by the sharp parts of the armor.

"Woooo….wo…..Let go…" Larain's tears were like pouring rain but the white knight wasn't affected.

The White Wind Tribe was gone. The Wolf-Hawk Atria Alliance was too strong...

Their totems were all over the air and the ground, more than the raindrops in the sky. In the whole grassy plains, they were rampant and unbeatable. After the demise of the second strongest White Wind Tribe, no one could hinder their footsteps.

Wooo!

The totem light of one of the knights beside was penetrated by an arrow. He tumbled to the ground. Another knight took his place without any hint of panic.

They were the most skilled White Wind Knights. All of them were skilled totem users that were developed since young. They were elites that were chosen among uncountable departments. The White Wind Knights had more than a hundred men. They were like a device. Once one of them fell, there would be a new knight to fill the void. There was no fear or panic, only composure.

After this battle, thousands of skilled totem users sieged the White Wind Tribe's headquarters. The White Wind King died in battle. This battle would definitely shock all the tribes in the grassy plains.

Buzzz!!!

Suddenly, all they could see was red. A vast light instantly flooded their vision.

The white knights quickly held the reins of their horses. The cries of panicked horses constantly came, while the Dual-Headed Flying Dragons fell to the ground like dumplings.

Bang!

A flying dragon suddenly landed behind their squad. It knocked into a protruding stone and let out a cry. Its four eyes were in a daze as it tried to get up, but it didn't work.

The white knight quickly recovered his vision. He looked at the Flying Dragon. With a raise of his hand, a white light shot out. It accurately pierced the Flying Dragon's head. The Flying Dragon instantly stopped moving.

He retracted the white light and continued to lead his team to scurry away.

"What is this!" "My eyes!"

"It's the White Wind's secret weapon!"

"Stop screaming!" "Stay still on the ground! Stay still on the ground!!"

The bellows of the black knight leaders came from the distance.

Then only the white knights saw what happened.

From the grassy plains in the distance, a vast red beam penetrated the clouds. The red beam was like moving water, rotating upwards. The whole beam was light red-jade, emitting sharp red light. It was incredibly bright.

At this point, there were huge crowds of black knights appearing in front of the white knights. Their leader was a black knight in a winged helmet. He was riding a strong black horse. He turned sideways towards them, but he was evidently affected by the red light. From time to time, the horses who were still in shock would neigh as they walked back and forth

"Flee towards that direction!" The white knight decisively changed their route and headed towards the direction of the red pillar. Their horses were also affected but fortunately, they were not looking in the direction of the beam. Since they managed to avoid the majority of the sharp light, they recovered much faster than the black knights.

　　****************

"Gulaman...Us?"

"Red light from the sky. An heirloom must be born." Gulaman stroked his beard. His gaze was solemn.

"According to the scouts over there, two elites were battling to the death near the red light. Both of them were severely injured. They look like people from the Central region." A black-armored knight on the side whispered. "Boss, what should we do now?"

"Let's go take a look. According to the old rules, let them kneel and join our alliance. If they are not willing, kill the males. For the females, disable them and send them to the army's red tent." Gulaman muttered.

"Yes!"

　　****************

Their arms collided fiercely.

Bang!

The red light and black light exploded. Garen and the Cthulhu King both were about to fall as they retreated a few steps. One of them leaned on a giant stone pillar, while the other one sat on the ground with a puff. He was out of breath.

Both of them were exhausted. They couldn't do anything to each other.

"You can't kill..AllNovelF(ull).Com!" The Cthulhu King, who was out of breath, said fiercely. He leaned on the stone pillar with all his might, trying to maintain the original image of the Cthulhu King. However, the fatigue of his body was like a wave, knocking on his mental state. This weariness was a mental one. It had nothing to do with the body.

Both of them had battled for more than two months. It was an intense battle every single day. There was no chance of relaxing.

Until now, when both of them were in a mentally exhausted state.

Once the Cthulhu King couldn't kill Garen with his strongest move, he knew that he can only drag on the battle against him. After a series of fights, this was the state that they'd ended up in.

"So what?" Garen smiled as he sat on the ground. He didn't care about his image. He seemed much more comfortable than the Cthulhu King.

"I also can't kill you." The Cthulhu King slightly loosened up. However, he didn't move. He wasn't able to muster enough energy. He couldn't even crack the skin of a peak fifth form. "How about we come to a truce?"

"A truce?" Garen's expression was strange.

Wooo!!

Deafening horn cries came again from the sky.

The numerous red flying dragons circled around them. The horned warriors blew their horns, letting out low cries.

"You know what I want. You think we are able to have a truce now?" Garen looked directly at the Cthulhu King and started laughing.

"There are conditions for everything in this world. Tell me your conditions." The Cthulhu King really didn't want to have to die to return.

Translator's Notes

[1] An ancient punishment where all four limbs are chopped off, leaving only the head and the body.

Chapter 506: Humbled 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Black Knights dominated the field with their numbers, while Dual Headed Salamanders blanketed the sky.

The small group of White Knights were surrounded beside a seemingly bottomless pit. Garen and his friend were also surrounded as they stood on a giant stone column at the other side of the pit.

Gulaman was leading the Black Knights, and there was a black-shirted man and a black armored knight standing behind him.

He looked down into the endless pit.

"Where’s the Heirloom?’

"We have searched everywhere but to no avail. I believe those two have taken it away and the current situation is because of the Heirloom." The man said in a cold tone.

"Take it from them!" Gulaman reached out his hand and the knight beside him respectfully passed him a black spear.

He took the spear, waved it and an almost innumerable amount of densely packed black symbols appeared.

"Hand over the Heirloom! Follow my orders and become my slave or lose your life!!" Gulaman shouted towards the Black stone column far away.

At the edge of the pit.

The White Knights remained group together with an adamant will. Blood stains covered their white armor, and some were armors were fully soaked with blood.

The weapons on their hands were either broken or blunt. There were no injured knights, as those who were injured had already died. When a knight sustains a wound, it meant that their totem light was broken, and without the protection of the totem light, a simple stab or the partner’s sputtered light could cause death under the chaotic battle.

None of the White Knights made a noise, but some of them were either hyperventilating, wiping off the blood that was about to enter their eyes or comforting the horses that might not last for another minute. Some of them were even whispering among themselves and no one could hear them clearly.

The leader of the White Knights had Princess Larain in his arms as he held a silver double-edged greatsword four meters long with one hand. The sword was filled with dried blood, and on top of the caked blood was fresh, still dripping crimson blood.

The white horse that he was on was also covered in white armor, but it was already ragged and each wound on its body was not a light one.

The aberrated horse had reached its limit. One of its eyes was stabbed blind, leaving behind a hole filled with blood. However, it stood strong on the ground and carried the two of them.

"Uncle White Sky, are we able to survive this? …" Larain was flabbergasted as she confided in the white knight leader while in his arms, her voice coarse from wear.

"I’m not sure." The leader of the white knight said calmly.

He looked far at the black stone column and noticed those two on top were in serious trouble.

**************

At the edge of the black stone column.

"Aren’t you clear about my terms?"

The Black Knight’s voice traveled within the noise from the aberrated horse and dual headed salamanders, but both of them ignored him.

"I will never pass you the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel." Cthulhu King said coldly. "Other than this, I will accept your conditions."

"It’s very unfortunate, but that is my only condition." Garen smiled cunningly.

In an instant, his body disappeared slowly.

An afterimage!

The Cthulhu King immediately raised up his hand and shot out a red beam few meters away from him to his left.

He didn’t even look at the result and immediately stomped his leg and straightened his hands to hit onto something.

Boom!!

A black figure appeared as it collided with his arm. However, the black figure didn’t even slow down at all. In fact, it used its momentum to fly towards the big group of Black Knights.

"Don’t even think about it!!" The Cthulhu King thought of one possibility and immediately chased after the black figure and tried to block its path. He then shot out streams of red lights from his hands, legs, mouth and eyes.

One would immediately vaporize if one were to come in contact with the Light of Destruction. However, as it was highly condensed, it didn’t spread out everywhere and the red lights that were shot out formed into countless of red dots and returned back to the Cthulhu King, becoming the source of the next attack.

The black figure kept colliding with the red lights a few hundred times a second in the sky. Every time it was in contact with the red dot, a booming sound was produced. The others could only hear a buzzing sound from the collision.

"Retreat!!" The Cthulhu tried to delay Garen, as a melee battle was not his strength. He had no choice but to shout at the Black Knights in rage.

Both of them flew in the sky, and some Dual Headed Salamanders which were grazed instantly exploded and turned into black fluid.

"Hehe!!"

Garen laughed softly as his right hand transformed into black fluid, and instantly solidified into a black giant dragon head, at least ten meters long and five to six meters wide.

Roar!! Fuh!!

The red beam pierced through the dragon head that just appeared, and it had no choice but to revert back to Garen’s right arm.

The black figure tried to dive from the sky, but each time it was being obstructed by the red beam.

The crowd of Black Knights started to expand and the quantity of Dual Headed Salamander in the sky increased as well.

Thousands of totem light force fields had surrounded both of them.

Gulman’s expression had become dimmer by the second.

He raised up his black rifle.

"How dare you challenge the prestige Atria Alliance’s green field!!"

"Kill them!!" The black knights around him suddenly roared.

"Kill!!""Kill!!"

"Long live the Atria Alliance!!"

The black knights and the Bullhorn Warrior who were on the flying dragon’s back started to roar.

Suddenly, countless of dual-headed salamanders rushed towards those two in the sky. They were holding onto weapons with totem light and some of them released black arrows from their hands whereas the others were releasing some green powder, covering the whole sky with a semi-transparent green plant.

In that instant, tens of dual-headed salamanders rushed towards, and the two of them and engaged battle with them. It looked like a dark red ball from afar.

"They came here on their own. You can’t blame me for that!" Garen suddenly laughed loudly in the sky.

"Light of ten thousand… Uff!!"

The Cthulhu King was suddenly muted.

A red figure came out from the red ball and landed on the ground with great force, creating a huge amount of dust in the process.

Then, a huge amount of black smoke started to rush out from the red ball which the flying dragon surrounded.

It was as if the black smoke was alive, as it started forming into a giant salamander dragon head. It was at least thirty meters long and cast a giant shadow onto the ground.

The dragon opened its mouth, to the point where its cheeks started to tear apart from the edge of its mouth to its ears. It was as if half of the brain was completely split into half.

"What… What is that!!??" Gulaman released the spear in his hand without realizing, and it landed onto the floor. He raised his head as he stared mindlessly at the black smoke dragon head in fear.

This intense intimidation had completely covered everyone in the field. Thousands of totem users and salamanders stood still, rooted to where they were.

The dark green field was slowly covered by red blood, drenching the four legs of all battle horses.

Everyone, including both the Black Knights and White Knights, looked up at the sky.

The giant dragon head had blocked off all the sunlight. It was like a natural disaster opening its mouth.

Puff!

The sky suddenly went silent.

In an instant, at least two hundred dual headed salamanders were bitten in half. Those who had surrounded the red ball had completely disappeared, including the people riding them.

There were people who pulled half of their bodies out from the side of the dragon’s mouth. However, they were immediately sucked back in and didn’t even have the chance to scream for help.

"It’s my win, Cthulhu King." A voice reverberated in the sky.

"Mon… Monster…"

It was as if a single drop of water was dropped into a bowl of boiling oil. The whole team of Black Knights were devastated.

"Monster!!""Ah!!""Kill him!!"

"Kill!!""Long live the Atria Alliance!!"

Some shouted in involuntary fear.

There were even more people started to retreat, keeping their heads down as if their lives depended on it. Everyone ran away without raising their head at all.

There were even people who rode the flying dragon and rushed towards him with tears in their eyes. Immediately, they were swallowed by it, and not a single drop of blood was left behind.

Any attack launched instantly melted and became part of the black smoke the moment they entered it.

"The… The Holy Lord will never forgive you!!" Gulaman said as his voice trembled. His legs were completely immersed in a blood-like fluid, and he started to tremble in fear. It sapped every ounce of his energy, sucking away his ability to move.

Two of the leaders behind him was also glued by the plasma-like fluid and couldn't move at all. It was as if their bodies weren’t theirs.

The black smoke surrounded them and binded them like a rope and gently threw them upwards.

The Black Smoke Dragon Head opened its mouth wide and ate them like they were its afternoon snack. It hadn’t even bothered to chew.

The never-ending plasma and black smoke spread across the sky and land, as it captured those Black Knights who couldn’t escape in time and threw them into the dragon’s mouth.

On the other hand, the leader of White Knights released a circle of white light and covered everyone as they hid inside the dark cave. They sought refuge inside the caves while the others ignored them, avoiding a massacre they had no hope to defend against.

"It’s over, Cthulhu King. I have almost cracked the code to you Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel’s workings." Garen’s voice came from the sky.

Within the crater, an ill-looking, bloody figure slowly rose up.

His mask was broken during the battle, revealing a pale, young and handsome face. There were two red circles that were rotating on his pupils and they even had pointers on it as if it were a clock. The left one was moving quickly while the right one was moving slowly.

"If not for these fools you fed on, do you really think you can beat me?!" The Cthulhu King gritted his teeth.

It almost completely seemed like cheating; a fat juicy piece meat landed directly into his mouth just as both of them had almost depleted their strength.

"What a fool of a failure." Garen’s voice appeared once more. "Just admit that you can’t win me. Whatever reasons you have are just excuses."

The Cthulhu King was very angry.

If not for his desire to survive and the group of fools who fed him power at the very last second, even Phiroth wouldn’t dare to humiliate him like that!

As both of them spoke to each other, the Black Knights on the ground and the Salamanders in the sky were almost wiped out. They were either dead, or had escaped.

Four purple figures had stealthily appeared at the edge of the battlefield as they looked at them. They were the four Demon Phoenixes.

Chapter 507: Subdue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Black wind started to blow, drawing black streaks across the air. These lines caressed his face as they blew past.

The dark green field was opened up, either revealing black dirt underneath or pushing all the fresh blood and limbs to the side. There even were some Black Knights and horses left that were squirming around on the ground in pain.

"Don't force my hand!!" The circles in the Cthulhu king's eyes rotated faster, as the saturated red light started to spread to his surroundings. Red cracks started appearing all over his body, as if lava were about to implode from within.

The ground started to tremble…

With Cthulhu King as the epicenter, a humongous, bloody mask slowly appeared.

It had no eyes, its lips were elongated and had no expression. The giant mask was facing the horrifying black smoke dragon head in the sky, and both of them were at least forty meters long.

The four Demon Phoenix on one side looked at the situation from afar, and the Demon Phoenix's mouth curled into an 'O' of awestruck horror.

"Even Osaka from before wasn't this crazy…" A voice of a woman in purple armor trembled.

What they were looking at had broken the limits of the human realm, and transcended into a world that was totally that of ordinary mortals.

The four of them felt the black smoke blowing towards them in the wind, and had no choice but to retreat a few meters away before they could stand firmly again, hiding beside a black pillar. It was then that they were able to properly assess the situation.

The Black Knights and flying dragons were all but eradicated.

The golden rays that rained down from a giant crack in the sky-filled cloud were just slightly larger than the black dragon head and the bloody masked man that were facing each other.

The black smoke and red light interacted with each other within a few hundred meters, but it was obvious that the red light was lacking strength.

"Are you willing to give up this body?" The black dragon head in the sky spoke calmly. A faint growl of a dragon could be heard within his voice, emanating an almost tangible fear and pressure.

The Cthulhu King stood at the bottom, staring at the dragon head coldly. After some time, the lava-like cracks on his body slowly dimmed and disappeared. The bloody mask gradually followed suit.

"You win this time! Just tell me what you want!"

"Let me enter your Secret Technique vault." Without any hesitation, Garen conveyed the demand he had already decided beforehand. Cthulhu's Origins could be exchanged with

Glittering Water, but Secret Techniques, especially the ones in this world, were even more valuable.

He was able to pull ahead of the Cthulhu King as he relied on the Nine-Headed Hydra's incredible recovery rate and the Nine-life Talent mixed together with his potential points.

However, the difference in Secret Technique was too far apart.

Without the additional support from the potential points, a totem user would be completely defenseless against the Cthulhu King, and would have been killed by him in a matter of seconds.

This world was partially separated into ancient ruins and human creations. The Cthulhu King, who stood at the world's pinnacle for thousands of years, must have collected a tremendous amount of Secret Techniques that could only be the best in this world.

"Secret Technique vault?" The Cthulhu King hadn't expected his opponent to demand such a request. He was more or less afraid of Garen; he couldn't kill this guy or run away from him.

As he fought him throughout the battle, he, who had been underestimating him, and started to view him as an equal in combat.

He found it strange that even though the Nine-Headed Hydra had incredible healing capabilities and the ability to substitute death with a dragon head, the ability he had was way too extreme. According to the prediction model of the Forger, its potential should be about nine lives, and Garen had died 9 times during the battle against him…

He decided that he had to research the Nine-Headed Hydra's source of energy in detail once he went back. He had lost so much during this battle.

"It works best with a Secret Technique that suits you. It would be pointless to learn other

Secret Techniques. Are you sure this is what you want?" He started to feel suspicious as he stared at Garen, trying to understand his thinking.

"This is my demand." Garen didn't want to offend him since the Cthulhu King was only teaming up with the Obscuro Society temporarily. Once Hellgate was born, they planned to dispose of the Cthulhu King.

"Secret Techniques are one of the main pillars of requirement in entering form five, it might too late for you to change one now." Cthulhu King suspected that he was trying to change his Secret Technique, as his was of too low level. However, they were at a level where everything revolved around on their Secret Techniques, including the merging of totems and evolution of their bodies. The Secret Techniques were the foundation of everything. It would be impossible to change the Secret Technique now, unless he planned to throw everything away and learn from scratch.

"That's fine, I just want them for reference." Garen didn't mind at all.

"Fine." Since there was a great disparity in their strength, the Cthulhu King didn't deny his request.

Huu…

The black smoke disappeared as the black dragon head slowly dissolved into black clouds and moved to the center, converging into a muscular person.

Golden hair appeared, and the smoke turned into a black cloud carrying a slowly descending figure.

He landed on the ground.

Garen looked around before he fixed his attention onto the Cthulhu King.

The opposing party sat on the ground and crossed his legs. The circles in his eyes slowed down, turned faint and disappeared.

Garen sat down as well, and both of them didn't say a word for some time. There were about ten meters apart from each other.

"Don't worry. As the leader of a society, my words carry the same weight."

The Cthulhu King formed a red screen with one hand and used the other hand as a pencil, writing something on it at great speed.

"At our level, other Secret Techniques don't matter much anymore. No matter how good of a secret technique or totem you possess, it was naught but a good starting point. To us, we have already reached the summit."

In that instance, he had written down a simple paragraph of Secret Techniques with thousands of words. As a talented totem user who stood at the pinnacle of the world, it was natural that his tactic and hand speed were at the top as well. He waved his hand three times each second and three words appeared. His speed of writing far surpassed a typical person.

He gently flicked his finger and the red screen flew towards Garen like a piece of paper.

Slam!

Garen captured the screen with one hand and glanced at it.

He had memorized everything written on it clearly, and his brain started to analyze the legitimacy of the content at great speed for any fundamental flaws in it.

He had obtained a lot of knowledge of the Secret Techniques from the previous world, and he determined, rather easily, that this Secret Technique was not a fake. However, his opponent was also a master in Secret Techniques, who had accumulated so much for so many years. It was laughably easy for him. The Cthulhu King, who was naturally gifted, could easily fake the contents if he wanted to.

At this level, Garen didn't have any trust in his past knowledge, as the men he dealt with were all gifted elites who had lived for many years.

He knew that, if not for these gifted abilities and attribute points, he would not be able to fight against these men. He originally was just a commoner with little capability.

This Secret Technique, Mountain Wheels, was obviously the original version from the ancient ruins. It had a total of three grades, and the highest grade had the strength similar to the peak of a form five. It seemed that it was his best Secret Technique, and this gave Garen a surge of thoughts and inspiration.

"Secret Techniques can be categorized into modern secret techniques and Ancient Endor's Secret Techniques." The Cthulhu King spoke, "This is one of the Secret Techniques that I referred to when I create the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel. I'll pass this to you first."

Garen nodded and crushed the red screen with his hand once he memorized the its contents.

The Cthulhu King hesitated for a moment but continued. "Have you heard of the divides between Secret Techniques?"

"Let's hear it." Garen glanced at the Demon Phoenix who wasn't far from them. She and her party popped their heads out from behind of the black stone pillar and didn't dare come closer.

The Cthulhu King's voice suddenly turned sharp, and only a faint sound traveled directly into

Garen's ear. He was using a combination of a form five Secret Technique's sleight of hand.

Garen had already learned this in the Secret Technique World, called Needle Voice.

"The Secret Techniques are separated into two types, living and dead."

"Living and dead?" Garen was curious. "Secret Techniques can be categorized into live and dead ones?"

"Of course." The Cthulhu King nodded. "The Secret Techniques we learn are called Dead

Secret Techniques. This death doesn't imply death in being alive or dead, but the nature of the Secret technique." He paused for a moment and continued. "Death means that it will never change nor evolve. These kind of Secret Techniques are like a frame. Those who suit it can learn it to a higher level; those who aren't suitable to it can never master it no matter how gifted they are. It already has a specific direction and can never change."

"Then, that means that the Living Secret Technique…?"

"That's correct. The living secret technique has incredible tolerance and adaptability. It is just a foundation, but this foundation is alive. It has multiple directions and suits multiple types of people to learn. The Secret Technique would evolve to adapt the learner's nature as they dive deeper." The Cthulhu King said calmly. "Hence, this kind of Secret Techniques are alive and grow over time. These are a cut above the rest."

Garen's expression changed slightly. He hadn't even heard of such Secret Technique in the world of Secret Techniques. The world the strong ones he interacted with was definitely different.

"Why are you telling me all this?"

"I have discovered that one out of four ancient ruins have Living Secret Techniques. There are three portions, and I can feel that one of them possesses cold type attributes. Although it's not so suitable for your water-based strength, this is a once in a lifetime opportunity. Are you interested?"

"Living Secret Technique…" Garen closed his eyes, as he knew that the opponent definitely had some motives in mind, but then again this opportunity was very hard to reject. "Why are you looking for me? Can't you obtain it with your Cthulhuism Society's strength?"

"There are people from the Western Continent vying for it as well. I am not confident alone."

The Cthulhu King squinted his eyes and said softly. "The Living Secret Technique isn't something anyone can learn. It's much more complicated to reach the peak compared to a Dead Secret Technique. It can't be helped if one is not compatible with it. You have to think this through. Once you've missed this opportunity, you won't know how long it will take for you to find a compatible one after this."

Garen was silent.

The opponent he would face was definitely on the same class as Cthulhu King, if even he needed help. In this period where Hellgate was about to reborn, he wasn't planning on finding more things to do.

He also had to find some time to send messages to the Hawk King Goth and Teacher Emin, so that they would enter the Ultimate Protection if things went sour. It would be a completely wasted effort, though, with Goth's personality.

During this period… But that Living Secret Technique is indeed very tempting.

"One of the major special characteristics of the Living Secret Techniques is its ability to adapt and grow. Only those who are suitable to it can create their own Secret Technique. It will then become the seed of the formation of totem strength. We believe that perhaps this kind of strength is the only thing that can further improve beings like ourselves."

The Cthulhu King opened his mouth once more. "Back then when the Hellgate of the Obscuro Society found a Living Secret Technique that is compatible with him, he shut himself away from the rest of the world to master it."

Chapter 508: Subdue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Hellgate!" Garen was stunned. Perhaps The Cthulhu King wasn't aware of it yet, but the moment the Hellgate was reborn, it meant that it had successfully mastered the Secret Technique. To form the Seed of Strength through fusion of his totem, and to further push it to the limit by using the growing characteristic of the Living Secret Technique, that seemed like a viable option!

"Who are we up against?" Garen closed his eyes to suppress his emotion

"The most powerful force in the Western Continent, the Divine God Palace Master, Rosman Saintwind." The Cthulhu King's face was very serious. "He also has another nickname called the King Of All Beasts. He ranks number one among all the nest masters!"

"It's not human?"

"Of course."

Cthulhu King suddenly laughed.

"Speaking of which, this field, including the hundreds of countries south of here, is dominated by him."

Then, Garen and Cthulhu King began questioning each other repeatedly, and time flew past just like that.

Half an hour later, a red light went up to the sky and arced across the horizon as it left the battleground.

Garen and the four Demon Phoenix stared at the Cthulhu King's ever-diminishing figure.

Both of them had agreed on a time and place to go to the Ancient Ruins. The nickname Divine God Palace Master was obviously an attempt to mimic the organization of the humans. It seemed that the strongest nest master must be very powerful, considering that the Cthulhu King had to request assistance from others.

It would be natural that the people from the Cthulhuism Society had inherited some Secret Techniques from him.

Judging from the looks of it, no matter how many more Dead Secret Technique the Cthulhu King had, it would never amount to the importance of a Living Secret Technique. Even Garen felt that the need of the Dead Secret Techniques had diminished once he learnt about the existence of Living Secret Techniques. As a compensation, Cthulhu King had given him an additional secret regarding the soul.

The Cthulhu Origin that he had obtained was actually a special item that enhanced the soul. Only Cthulhu Origins were able to recover the soul when the Cthulhu King died. At the same time it also acted as a shell during their reincarnation.

Before he went after God Cloud, Garen had hidden one of Cthulhu's Origins, as he was afraid that it would be destroyed before the great war. Hence, the origin was currently not with him, and he had to go back to retrieve it.

Four of the Demon Phoenix had become very honest after they saw the battle between the Cthulhu King and Garen. Compared to the previous battle, they still had such intense strength after fighting for days.

What was important was that Garen's style of eating anything made these few people nervous. He had just swallowed countless Black Knights a while ago, and these few people who were following Garen from behind couldn't help but feel anxious when they got closer to him. They're afraid that he might just take them as a snack and swallow them if he were unhappy.

"What should we do now?" Demon Phoenix asked Garen carefully.

"It's time to go back." Garen glanced at her. This fellow could be considered at the lower tier of form five, but she should be able to increase further due to the seal. However, based on her attributes and physical structure, she should be at the middle tier of form five. The peak wasn't something that was easy to achieve, but then again, how many had done that in the entire history of mankind?

If Demon Phoenix were to attain the peak, she wouldn't have stayed at a corner of a small country.

"Go back? Where to?"

Garen stayed his mouth, too tired to answer.

As the few people from the Demon Phoenix were traumatized by him, they immediately stopped talking in fear that they would really be eaten. Garen's style of eating anything had truly frozen them on the spot.

Garen didn't want to make the move himself, instead letting the people of the Demon Phoenix take action.

Soon, a purple lion with purple wings appeared in front of them. The back of the lion was wide enough to fit about five to six people, which was enough for Garen and the others.

After the past few days of intense battles, Garen laid onto Demon Phoenix's knees as he rested his mind, carefully peeling the white fruits that she had plucked earlier and putting them into his mouth.

One of the other two brothers had transformed into a mount, while the other held up a purple blind film to help Garen to block the wind and sun.

As they were about to fly, Garen flicked his finger at a black hole to his side.

Pew!

A black line shot out, and the surface of the black hole cracked.

Somewhere down below was the faint sound of a girl's scream.

Soon, a white ball about ten meters wide slowly rose up from the hole and gently set itself on the ground.

The film of light dissolved, and inside were the thirty plus White Knights who had escaped earlier. All of them had dried blood stains on them, and were eerily silent. Their eyes carried almost no life. Beside them were their similarly blood-stained horses.

The leader of the White Knights was holding onto a small, tearing girl, with one hand, while his gaze was fixed firmly on Garen.

"Who are you guys?" Garen glanced at the group of White Knights.

"We are the survivors from the White Wind Tribe, oh powerful totem master." The Leader of White Knight lowered his head as he answered. It looked like the opposing party had no intention to devour them at first sight.

"White Wind Tribe?" Garen had never heard of it as he only cared about the existence of fifth form beings. Those who were below this fought with their totems, and post-fifth-forms fought with their Secret Techniques. To stand at the peak meant to master the Secret Techniques that they had. No matter if it were the Cthulhu King, Phiroth or he, they had already arrived at the peak of the totem and Secret Technique world. The rest depended purely on the strength attribute. Not many things couldn't be easily killed by them.

He looked at the White Knights, until his sights were suddenly fixed on the small girl the White Knight was holding.

His head tilted back to the sky and chuckled lightly.

The leader of the White Knight turned his head and looked in the same direction but didn't say anything. His face immediately changed as he could only think of one possible solution.

He immediately kneeled onto the ground.

"My lord, please, bring Princess Larain along with you!!"

Even if he was begging someone, his tone was firm, determined and eager. It was like an underling reporting to his master on a peaceful afternoon.

"Uncle!" The girl's face was caked with dirt, so much so that it obscured her face. She, who was holding onto the White Knight, hesitated for a moment before she kneeled on the ground with her uncle.

Thump!

In an instant, every white knight present had kneeled onto the ground.

The Demon Phoenix started to laugh.

"If we go, I'm afraid the two forces to our flanks won't wait any longer to strike. If the lord doesn't accept them, they're all dead."

"To be honest, I am very generous towards people with good quality." Since he had to fight against the Divine God Palace Master, Garen had gained interest in these people from the White Wind Tribe. They were most likely being hunted by the Black Knights from the Divine God Palace Master. In addition, the leader of White Knight and the small girl had above average attributes, especially the leader of the White Knights.

Garen had made his decision solely because of him.

This fellow's attribute could only be considered excellent, but his determination was even stronger. He was willing to protect his master under such a dire situation. This suggested that he was very loyal Together with the white knights around him, their strength numbered about thirty in total. These people had much loyalty, and would never betray their master.

The Black Swamp Palace currently required manpower, and these people would be useful to him.

Garen was also moved, in fact. The Black Water True Technique required determination first, and other qualities second.

"Bring them along!" He pondered for a moment before he opened his mouth.

The leader of the White Knights could finally relax, and the small girl beside him was ecstatic.

"Get up, the Lord has promised to bring you along." Phantom took out a purple orb from her body and gently threw it out. The orb landed on the ground and immediately transformed into a group of purple uni-horned wolves.

These giant wolves crawled on the ground as they showed respect towards the Demon Phoenix and the party.

"Bring them along." Phantom ordered coldly.

The giant wolves stood up and each of them were at least four meters tall.

The knights relaxed knowing they would survive. None of them wished to die in vain. Now that these few strong people had decided to protect them, they felt relief.

"Get up and ride the giant wolves." Phantom ordered.

The leader of the white knight didn't budge, as if he didn't hear her.

It was then Phantom realized that he had fainted.

The giant wolves carried the white knights and formed a small formation. Garen and the others sat on the back of the lion and flew up slowly as the wolves followed from behind on the ground.

As they left, a black hole appeared in the sky and two golden figures appeared. Two human-shaped beings came out covering themselves with golden cloaks.

"They have been taken away." The tall one said softly.

"That man had noticed us. According to what we know, he should be one of the four major heads of Kovitan, the Nine-Headed Snake Garen." the shorter humanoid said in a sharp male tone. "Why didn't you make any moves? According to the human's categorizations, you should be at the upper tier of form five."

"We are no match for them." The tall one shook his head. "The humans have huge potential in Secret Techniques that we don't possess. We can only rely on the foundation we have. They merge their strength with Secret Techniques and come up with an entirely new strength and it's not something we can face head on. We can still deal with a typical form five but we

are no match for its peak."

"What about the three tailed dragon?"

"It's the same." The tall one explained. "Only we, the nest leaders, can reach the upper tier of form five, and the humans the peak of form five. The upper tier is placed between the middle tier and their peak. We are stronger than middle tier but weaker than the peak."

"So the reason the palace master has been gathering all kinds of Secret Technique was to?"

"You guessed it right. The palace master has already obtained two living secret techniques. Perhaps with a little bit more, he could understand the rationale behind it and come up with a Secret Technique even us nest leaders can learn." the tall one nodded.

Both of them conversed in a standard Ender Kingdom language, as if it were their native tongue. It seemed that they had worked hard for it.

"If it's successful, we nest leaders are able to fight against the human's elites. This world.. Shall be ours!" The tall out said. "We have to let the humans know that we have more quality than our numbers!"

Chapter 509: Suspicion and Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the yellow dirt field, a pack of fish-shaped white wolves were moving as they carried white knights on their back. The pack numbered fifty to sixty strong, and each of them were huge, uni-horned beasts.

There was a purple-black lion with wings flying overhead, Garen sat on his knees as he fidgeted with the Cthulhu’s Origin that he had taken out from the ground with his hand.

There were three Origins rotating slowly within it, forming a small sphere,. They were of the Time God, War God, and Light God respectively, and among the three origins, The Light God’s was a middle-level Origin, and the remaining two were lower-level Origins.

Garen released some black smoke, they smoke rode the wind for some ten kilometers. Not a single living being dared come close to them along the way, ensuring safe passage for the convoy.

He moved his upper body and looked down at the pack of wolves. After three days of rest and journey, the white knights had slightly recovered their spirits.

On the first day when they left the field, the leader of the White Knights had sworn loyalty towards Garen and was now part of the Black Swamp Palace. The leader of the White Knights was called White Sky, and was the foster son of the White Wind Tribe leader. To have been at the spiritualized totem user level at the age of 23, he was considered a very gifted person, even comparing among the countries.

White Sky had his own reason to be able to stand out among the other foster children; he had a very unique gift, which he named Enhancement.

White Sky thought that once lord had heard of his gifted ability, he would definitely nurture him and view him more heavily. However, Garen only nodded his head calmly and that was the end of it. He didn’t know that for Garen, who had arrived at the end of the path, only viewed his gift as nothing more than a good starting point. No matter how gifted he was, Garen wouldn’t pay his attention towards him if he didn’t grow along his journey.

Garen had a lot of issues to handle. After he understood how the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel worked, although the Secret Technique wasn’t compatible with him, his original objective was to learn it to absorb the Cthulhu’s Origin.

White Sky’s talent, Enhancement, was an ability to enhance his totem or tactic by one time within a short amount of time. All he had to sacrifice was half of his strength and energy.

This ability was terrifying in the later stages as the stronger the totem was, the aftereffects of enhancement would be even greater. The most important thing was that this effect could be used to break the defense of a totem user of the same rank. This was also why White Sky was heavily looked up to. If he could reach form four or five, the enhancement effect would be much more horrifying.

Unfortunately, the stronger the gift, the greater the resources required, and it would only increase as it went further and beyond. He had been stuck at the spiritualized level for three years now and there wasn’t any improvement at all.

Garen sat at the back of the flying lion and carefully examined three of the Cthulhu’s Origins in his hand. Each of them gave off a unique color, black, white and red. It seemed rather mysterious as it shone on Garen’s face.

The black lion’s wings cut the wind with a constant howl, thrusting the reasonably steady party along.

Garen focused his attention on the black origin. This black origin was completely black, with some slight silver glittering sand in the middle. It looked like a black concentrated liquid.

Garen gently opened the case of the crystal ball, and gently inserted two fingers into the inner part of the black origin.

Pew!

His body jolted as a red circle appeared around his body and rotated slowly.

The circle was filled with countless half transparent, living tentacles and claws. These tentacles were flailing about, extending and piercing into the crystal ball, and down into the inner part of the Origin.

Gulp! Gulp!

A gulping sound could be heard, as if those tentacles were drinking water while absorbing the origin and transferring it to the red circle.

In an instant, the inner circle shot out four black silver rays of light towards Garen’s body with great precision, forming a perfect cross.

The black cross maintained for at least ten minutes, and Demon Phoenix and her friends were at a loss as to what to do. If Garen hadn’t informed them beforehand, they would have jumped down from the lion and hid on the ground.

The red circle possessed such strength that even Demon Phoenix, a form five, was overwhelmed by it.

After ten minutes, the cross slowly disappeared, and the red circle broke into a sea of shards before disappearing.

Garen opened his eyes and his face was filled with happiness.

"The Cthulhu’s Origin has such an effect!?" He was completely surprised and happy about it.

He started collecting the Cthulhu’s Origin as he wanted to reach for the peak of form five, but ever since he had reached this level, he didn’t view it as importantly as before. He just wanted to absorb it but didn’t expect that by absorbing it through the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel, the Time God’s origin had given him an unexpected result.

He moved his focus onto the light red attribution pane.

The attribute pane’s abilities that did not have any changes for a long time had finally come up with something new.

A dark red symbol appeared at the left side of the attribute pane after he absorbed the Cthulhu’s Origin.

It was a symbol that resembled two Ks stacking back to back together, and the symbol was rotating.

Just like always, Garen knew the meaning of the symbol immediately after he stared at it.

‘Successfully absorbed enhancement object. Enhancing soul limit…’

Garen looked at the attribution pane.

‘Strength 14. Agility 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10.’ It was still the same, but there was a small blinking addition symbol at the end of each attribute.

Ever since he had entered form five, his attributes were getting weaker among the totem users. His body enhancement, even with the addition of the Troll Grip, wasn’t something outstanding compared to the totem users of the same class. Due to the totem’s potential, Garen’s advantage of increasing his attributes had been overwhelmed by other totem users, and in fact it was disadvantageous to his growth.

This was because he couldn’t completely negate the benefits of form five users’ totems by just increasing his physical attributes. It went without saying that they had stronger Secret Techniques as well.

His physical attributes had slowly become obsolete, as it was completely useless when going against a form five totem user with incredible strength. No matter how strong a person was, he would still be weak if put up against a canon. He would die in one shot, and this was a huge hurdle for Garen.

However, he had no choice. He was able to obtain his overwhelming attribute by transplanting the Dual Headed Salamander’s heart. His body’s limit wouldn’t even reach ten points if he had a commoner’s body.

Now, he had finally found a path after absorbing the Cthulhu’s Origin.

As he recalled the Cthulhu King’s explanation before he left, Garen felt happy and at the same time, he had a hypothesis: Perhaps the Cthulhu’s Origin’s effect was to allow people to break through their limit?

The Obscuro Society’s Marshall used the Cthulhu’s Origin to go beyond his limits in the original history as well.

The Time God’s Origin lasted for half an hour, before the blinking symbol at the back of the attribute pane slowly disappeared. There were no changes in the attributes.

However, Garen could faintly feel that his body was able to improve further.

The dark red symbol at the front of the attribute pane had stopped spinning, and changed slightly.

Garen immediately read the notification.

‘Eternal Soul has increased, attribute limit has increased…’

"Eternal Soul has increased?" He recalled the idea he thought of earlier, and recalled the Cthulhu’s explanation regarding the soul, this refined his hypothesis.

"Does that mean that the limit of my attribute is directly related to my soul?"

As he thought of this idea, a new symbol appeared below the attribute pane.

Garen looked at it curiously, and the symbol suddenly expanded and turned into a red screen, showing him his history of him enhancing his attribute.

‘Increasing attribute…’

‘Increasing attribute…’

‘Increasing attribute…’

‘Absorbing additional potential points…’

‘Absorbing additional potential points…’

….

…

The record was shown down to each minute detail.

+Garen was surprised.

"If the limits of my attributes are strongly related to the enhancement of the soul, does that mean transplanting the dragon’s heart and breaking the body’s limit are also related to the soul?"

Thinking back, he could see the Nine-Headed Hydra’s memories when he was at the underground hot spring after he had transplanted the dragon’s heart, he already had some understanding of the overall situation.

He kept swiping up at the screen as he looked further back into the history. The screen moved like an inverted red waterfall.

After swiping for a solid ten minutes, the detailed record appeared in front of Garen.

"Successfully transplanted the dragon’s heart. Commence merging with the Soul’s will. The soul is unable to reject the effect and the enhancement shall proceed…’

‘Enhancing the limit…’

‘Enhancing the limit…’

…..

Each and every line of enhancement was clearly recorded in the archive.

Garen had finally understood the logic behind the increment in his attribute.

The limit of the body and the upper limit of increasing the attribute via potential points was directly related to the strength of the soul.

As he saw it, he felt slightly afraid. If not for the Dual Headed Salamander non-resistance and its inherent loyalty since the beginning, in addition to his luck and strong will, he would have failed miserably. Back then, he didn’t know that there was a soul category and purely believed that he just had to increase his body’s organs to go further. He didn’t expect that the essence of the organs combined and countless of living beings’ wills -- the soul, was the most important key.

According to his experience in absorbing the Cthulhu’s Origin and the Cthulhu King’s explanation, the soul was most likely a unique energy source within the living flesh. It was so perfect that it had become a completely independent force field.

The body was just like a huge factory, Excluding the consumption of energy that kept the body alive, it produced a huge amount of electric energy, and when combined together, it formed a complicated energy field. This field in turn would affect the behavior of the body as it would react to the body’s signals as well as those outside of the body.

Garen combined the Cthulhu King’s theory together with his own experience and the knowledge he had learnt on Earth, and barely had a full explanation of the soul.

The soul was deemed as the most mysterious item on every world. The Cthulhu King was someone whose soul was so strong that it could temporarily leave its physical body, hence, he was immortal.

To be born in the flesh and surpass it. The intrinsic quality of the Cthulhu King’s body was very likely made out of an energy field. Compared to a living being’s body, the cells, flesh and blood were just stored energy, ready to be converted to other forms of energy.

After clearing up the system, Garen started to absorb the remaining two Cthulhu’s Origin.

Chapter 510: Suspicion and Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He chose the Light God’s Origin as his second.

He spent at least an hour absorbing it, and another two hours waiting for the addition symbol to finish blinking.

The third origin from the War God’s Origin was not effective at all. Garen didn’t feel anything after absorbing it, neither did the red symbol rotate or the addition symbol appear.

He could sense that the effect of the origin could only push him this far.

Techniques to increase the soul’s limit were very rare. He had transplanted the Dragon’s Heart and was barely able to remove the will of the Nine-Headed Hydra. In addition, he wasn’t sure if there were any hidden side effects from the transplant. Since he had too little knowledge regarding the soul, Garen wasn’t sure if he had completely eliminated all the side effects, and he could only deal with it if and when it appeared.

As he finished absorbing the third Origin, Garen looked at the blinking addition symbol disappearing, and looked at his potential points.

‘Strength 14. Agility 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10. Potential 16744%. Possess the qualifications of a Luminarist.’

He had obtained 167 points worth of potential from the deaths of all the creatures and the Black Knights. The points he had amassed from before were spent dry in the fight against the Cthulhu King.

"Let’s see how much higher it goes."

The more attribute points he had, the more points he needed to increase it further.

At the very beginning, he only required 1 potential point to increase 0.1 points of any attribute. Once his attributes reached 5 points, it would require 20.

Now he was at 10 points. If he wanted to add more…

Garen skimmed through all of his attributes. Although his intuition told him that the attributes could be increased further, he was still uncertain. This wasn’t just an issue of increasing his attributes, though. This would also provide evidence for his hypothesis.

Ultimately, he set his sights onto vitality.

He was in decent shape in terms of strength and speed, as the Nine-Headed Hydra had boosted his strength. His current weakness was his defense; his skin’s defense wasn’t up to par.

A large chunk of his flesh was disintegrated the moment the Cthulhu King’s red beam grazed him. If not for the fact that potential points could act as a supplement to his Nine-life Talent, he would have died a long time ago when going against Cthulhu King.

Vitality was directly related to his defense and resistance. This had already been proven in the Secret Technique world.

The only caveat was that, even though his vitality was only at 10 points, his body’s characteristics had transcended into another level from the enhancements from his Secret Techniques. He couldn’t be sure how many potential points he needed to increase them.

Garen stared at Vitality for three full seconds.

In an instant, ping!

A soft ring came out, and a full hundred potential points were deducted.

His Vitality, which originally sat at 10 points, had gradually increased to 11.

Garen could still feel that there was more space for his body to be enhanced further. With one point’s increase in Vitality, a warm feeling entered his body, into his muscles, before finally being absorbed by them and returning to their original, uneventful state. Garen could only feel that his body was slightly fuller, buffer, but that was it.

"One hundred potential points.. All for a single point of Vitality.." Garen was rather unhappy. This meant that in one or two years, even he were to kill countless totems and nest leaders, he wouldn’t be able to go against a Form Five. There just weren’t enough elites for him to kill. There were. In fact, countless creatures roaming about, but no one could know how many potential points he would require to bump his attributes further up.

Perhaps it would require two hundred potential points to increase another attribute point. Perhaps it was three hundred, or even a thousand points.

According to Garen’s hypothesis, he would require every attribute to be at 30 points to go up against a peak Form Five. To grow to that point, he might really need an unfathomable amount of potential points.

Furthermore, he had to work around the limits of his body.

"That’s too bad..." Garen sighed, and the shoved the issue with the Cthulhu’s Origin to the back of his head.

He had originally planned to immediately return to the Black Swamp Palace, as nowhere would be safe the moment Hellgate was resurrected. However, in the Ultimate Protection, he could buy some time to think of how to deal with him in the relevant safety it provided.

Although, he was genuinely tempted by the Cthulhu King’s invitation.

The Living Secret Technique was a Secret Technique that, in theory, was much stronger than the Secret Techniques that he had encountered thus far. This kind of Living Technique was something only the demon king in folklore could invent.

A Secret Technique that could grow alongside with the practitioner was complete nonsense to Garen.

If he could obtain a Living Secret Technique that was compatible with him… This was something that Garen would tempt Garen greatly.

The Cthulhu King said that he was very sure that there would be a total of three Living Secret Technique in the Ancient Ruins. One of them was an ice type, and even though it wasn’t that compatible to Garen, it was something that couldn’t be obtained elsewhere. He had no space to complain, as encountering one that he could even use was something very good.

Garen was sure that the water and poison types were the most compatible with him. Although ice was slightly incompatible, a Living Secret Technique was very rare. Hence, he planned to return to the Black Swamp Palace to settle some things, and then head towards the place to meet up with the Cthulhu King.

There was also the number one ranking nest leader, Divine God Palace Master, who decided to come to the surface to try and obtain the resource in the ancient ruins instead of fighting the Elder Parliament underground. Up until now, there was still no movement from the Elder Parliament’s elites.

This made Garen feel unease. Although the Cthulhu King hadn’t mentioned anything about it, he could feel a sense of urgency from the Cthulhu King’s words.

"I wonder what rushed him this badly? According to the original history, the Elder Parliament would cease activity once Hellgate is born. Perhaps…" Garen suddenly thought of one possible scenario.

"Perhaps the Elder Parliament had been completely annihilated underground!?"

Why was the Divine God Palace Master was in a hurry to search for a Living Secret Technique? Why would Cthulhu King place his grudge aside and invite Garen to obtain the Secret Technique? Knowing the Cthulhu King’s arrogance, he had chosen to endure and lower his head instead of fighting him to the death.

Garen started to piece the puzzle together, and an uncomfortable feeling rose up in his gut.

It was very possible that Hellgate had already come out for some time and had eliminated the Elder Parliament underground, injuring the nest leaders along the way, which then lead to the current situation.

Furthermore, the two nest leaders who suddenly came to the Eastern Continent were in a hurry to recruit the creatures here. They had even only occupied a small area of a few hundred southern countries. Based on this strange behavior, it’s very likely that Hellgate had already made his move underground, since the nest leaders wouldn’t try to recruit creatures for no reason…

The more Garen thought of it, the more likely it got. Based on this, he started to feel excited and eager to know how much stronger Hellgate had become.

He had no fear or desperation. Garen was very confident in his regeneration, even if he couldn’t fight against him. Furthermore, to challenge the peak was in the true nature of a martial artist.

He also needed to find the secret to him transmigrating to this world, and figure out the mysterious source of his gifted abilities. Perhaps he would even try chasing his most desired wish in the future.

He had to, by all means, not die in this world!

For the next few days, he sat on the lion’s back and he listened to the news from the radio, all the while directing the path for the winged lion as they flew to the Ultimate Protection in Kovitan.

The radio kept spitting news incessantly.

The Enderian King had decided to challenge the world’s strongest totem user. He had used the three of the country’s Stone Statues and half of its national treasure as the reward when held the King of Totem conference.

The location was his newly built Eternal Night Palace. As long as the last victor was able to defeat him, he would be rewarded with the wealth along with three of the strongest Stone Statues. One would be rewarded based on their ranks, even if he wasn’t ranked first.

As Garen heard this news from the radio, he immediately knew that countless of totem users who’d done the same would rush towards the Ender Kingdom.

A great calm had set on after the great war. The world was much more peaceful compared to before, after the nest leaders had recruited a great amount of high-level creatures. The individuals with power were all busy training themselves and collecting resources, so that they would be able to further develop themselves when they won. It was an opportunity that mustn’t be missed.

Even if they couldn’t obtain the number one spot, they hoped to be at least be placed in the top 100. Perhaps ninety percent of the totem users would like to think so.

Garen knew from the very start that this was a trap and ignored him. He decided to inform the core totem users in the Black Swamp Palace. It would be none of his business if they didn’t listen to him. It also served as a good opportunity to simplify the rather complicated Black Swamp Palace.

Excluding the King of Totem Conference, news regarding all types of schools kept appearing. As the Obscuro Society had dominated most of the strongest schools, the Terraflor Society had lost their battle and went into hiding in the dark. The remaining relatively large schools became the Obscuro Society’s pawns, as they went around the area to dominate the middle sized and small sized schools. Among these middle and small sized schools, the Tasura Academy, which was under teacher Emin’s management, had retreated after they obtained the news earlier. Along with Garen’s arrangement, at least half of the Tasura Academy’s members had safely avoided this storm.

As Garen arrived at the border of the Kovitan Empire. Excluding the few hidden academies, the whole of the Eastern Continent’s Tactic Academy was dominated by the Obscuro Society. Every academy on this land united and formed into one, humongous, unprecedented academy.

Hellgate seemed to be very generous towards the Terraflor Society. Ever since the death of Sisley, he promised that the Terraflor Society would not be harmed for the next century.

Garen, as one of the big four, was recognized by the Ultimate Protection, and he opened up an entrance with ease and brought these people into the Ultimate Protection.

As they were getting closer to the capital of the Kovitan Empire, the land started to become uneven and began to rise. Hills slowly appeared, and would become bigger and taller and soon they turned into full yellow mountains.

The mountains started to appear after the hills, and their colors changed from yellow, to dark green, to grey, and then to black.

Finally, the black Kingdom at the peak of the mountain cluster slowly appeared, at the peak of the highest mountain. The pitch black city looked like ancient ruins from afar.

The Kingdom had advanced a lot compared to when Garen left; black and white dots could be seen flying and landing, and the whole kingdom had split into three parts on the mountain. One could see the road was now filled with carriages pulled by cows, horses and aberrated creatures on the mountain.

The foot of the mountain was filled with farms, villages, windmills and waterwheels. The green fields rustled in the blowing wind, and the tiny figures of the farmers could faintly be seen within them. The atmosphere was one of peace.

Compared to the cruel and bloody world outside, this was many times better.

Countless of villages were spread about at the foot of the mountain, with the capital at the epicenter. Villages were already in the midst of construction in the nearby mountains, and most of the mountainsides had turned into fields. The kingdom had totally changed during the time he was absent.

Chapter 511: Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen got the black lion to fly towards the foot of the mountain in the Kingdom directly, while the group on wolf-back were following slowly behind him.

The herd of giant wolves were one of the several monster tribes that Demon Phoenix and the others had taken over during the sealing period, their leader was a huge wolf with golden fur, it had fought the Crescent Marks for thousands of years, and was considered an old enemy.

Sitting on the black lion's back, Garen looked down.

There were some normal people and members of the procession looking up from below, their expressions full of awe and surprise. Others didn't notice him at all, their heads lowered as they did their own thing.

The farmers were still working their crops in the field, the medicine-gatherers carried their baskets on their backs as they wove through the rocks at the bottoms and sides of the mountains, while occasionally there were several flying creatures carrying riders as they crossed underneath him, some flying towards the outskirts of the Kingdom, others flying from outside towards the Kingdom.

When they were several hundred meters from the Kingdom, at the foot of the mountain on the road going around the mountain, there was already a large crowd of figures dressed in black, looking towards Garen's direction from afar. The surroundings had also been cleared out temporarily, and those who wanted to go up the mountain had their path temporarily blocked. There were already some people gathering outside the team cordoning off the area, as though there out of curiosity.

Out of the black-robed people waiting at the foot of the mountain, two of them were leading the group, and most of the rest were young people, there were a few guards in black armor around them as well, their faces unclear under the helmet.

As soon as they saw the huge black lion's body falling slowly, the leaders of these people instantly raised their hands. With a whoosh, they released a white carpet that shot out flying. It landed precisely underneath the black lion's paws.

The white carpet, up to a hundred meters long, was unnaturally eye-catching in mid-air, as was the huge attention-catching black lion. More and more people began watching out of curiosity, and some of the people flying in mid-air also stayed behind to see what the commotion was.

"It's been a long time, Elder Blizzard." Garen instantly recognized the two people in the lead, one was Blizzard, and the other Wukang. It was just that Wukang wore a face veil, blocking half of his face, and the part of his face hidden under the veil looked rather green in the nose and swollen in the face.

"Palace Master, you have finally returned." Blizzard greeted him, laughing heartily.

Bam!

The black lion landed heavily on the white carpet.

His black-clothed disciples all bent their backs in a bow, yelling in unison,

"Welcome back, Palace Master!"

Their voices were deafening, their aura powerful.

More than a hundred people yelling at once, greeting someone in a line, such a scene instantly created whispers among the onlookers. In just that short while, there were already several hundred people gathered and blocking the road up the mountain, many of them were merchant groups entering and leaving the Kingdom to do their peddling and delivering their wares, there were also noble processions coming and going, as well as members from the other powers, but the majority of them were still normal civilians.

Most of them were farmers going to the Kingdom market to sell ingredients, meat and vegetables in the morning, as well as bull carts sending daily necessities.

There were four entrances into the Kingdom, and this was only one of them, but there was a surprising amount of traffic here, it had been less than ten minutes, but there were already several hundred people stuck here, and there seemed to be more traffic coming from behind.

Compared to the hundred thousand people coming and leaving every day, a congregation of a hundred like this was like a small wave in the ocean.

After receiving Garen, the black-robed people hurriedly led the wolf steeds onto the road, and all the passersby opened a path of their own accord, there were two civilians who rushed up to try and lodge their complaints, but they were blocked by the black-armored guards outside.

The appearance and leaving of this group was only a small ripple in the huge crowd of the Kingdom.

Among the crowd, the scouts from each of the three other giants powers also quickly spread the news of Garen's return back to the other higher-ups in the Kingdom.

There were more and more people gathered in the Kingdom, the changes in the outside world once causing a large influx of regular civilians into the area of Ultimate Protection.

Blizzard and Wukang accompanied Garen back to the Palace District, and then they bid him farewell, leaving to handle other matters, while Lala, who had already been waiting at the palace doors, was in charge of receiving him and other trivial matters.

Ivycius, who had been sealed away with his training, also came out to greet him, followed by the whole host of the Palace's higher-ups and Elders, the Elders Angel, Skyharp, and Spellmaster were all there, followed by many of the Palace's core researchers. The three Master-level disciples Garen had recruited were there too, as well as a young man in white lined next to them, the four of them were followed by the Four Directions Sky Warriors and the black-armored guards, and then there were the many other researchers and disciples, as well as the teams from the Technique Hall.

It was a huge procession of several hundred people, surrounding Garen as he returned to the Palace District's Black Swamp Grand Hall.

Sitting in the Black Swamp Grand Hall's main throne, Garen glanced at the two rows of elders on either side of him.

The two rows of elders were all there, sitting at his two sides, their own disciples and students standing behind them, the seats after that were the four core disciples, the Four Directions Sky Warriors, and there were no more seats after that, just the next-rate disciples standing in two lines. All this was according to rank, and not carelessly ordered.

All of them wore pitch-black clothes, but their insignias were different, they all had silver Nine-Headed Dragon badges, those who could come to the Grand Hall were at least Five Dragon Heads and above. The elders each had Eight Dragon Heads, but only Garen himself was at the Nine Dragon Heads level.

Garen sat in the top seat, Demon Phoenix and his three subordinates standing behind him. This was the arrangement he had settled himself, Demon Phoenix and the others had basically been utterly psychologically traumatized by his defeating them, so out of everyone in the whole Palace, only he could make them submit, so they became something of an independent third faction. Other than the two powers led by Ivycius and Blizzard respectively, now he had a more convenient third party for balance.

"When I was at Daniela, did anything strange and serious happen in the Palace?" Garen glanced at the whole area, he was now Form Five, and didn't have the huge presence he did before, now he seemed like a completely normal person, peaceful and calm, so that no one could tell that he had a high position and tremendous power.

The Seven Night Tower Elders exchanged hidden glances, and didn't say anything. During this time, they had begun to enjoy the benefits, with the power of the Black Swamp Palace's ever-increasing power, if they wanted anything, they just needed to say the word, and countless powers would stretch out and help them find it, it was that much more convenient than when they had to look for it themselves. Although they had to fulfill their duties while they enjoyed the benefits, those duties only included easily showing off a bit when needed to scare off outsiders, the time and energy needed were basically negligible.

Especially Angel of the Night, she was basically indulging in hedonism every night, having purchased a large mansion with a garden in the Kingdom, she kept more than ten beautiful men dogs and pretty boy slaves by the dozens, mixing together with the other women of higher society and messing around all day, lost in their pleasures and rampaging in their nights.

Blizzard, on the other hand, would run off to Grand Duke Benoc's side every so often to exchange experiences with the expert fighters there, recently that side had also recruited several powerful totem users, add that to the peak-level totem users Benoc already had, and that meant Blizzard managed to find some rare opponents, so now he rarely stayed at the Black Swamp Palace.

As for Spellmaster Anjiad, he was obsessed with discussing things with the Technique Hall's technical members and forgers, he had an unnatural interest in creature modification, before this he didn't have the time and energy, but after joining the Black Swamp Palace, he wasn't lacking in anything, and instead he had plenty of time to research his interest and hobbies. He had even chosen some disciples from among the many researchers who had similar passions in modification to become his assistants.

Ivycius was still fusing his totem, so he meditated slightly with his eyes closed as he sat on his seat, still holding that long white sword to his chest, but his aura was slowly approaching that feeling of Form Five fusion power. Garen could tell with a glance, as long as he could go past this fusion doorstep, the White Rose Sword Sage would be able to enter Form Five.

It was just that totem users took different amounts of time to overcome this doorstep, and there were several reasons Garen himself could overcome it so easily.

One was that the Nine-Headed Dragon didn't have much potential, so it was much easier to level up and fuse.

Secondly, his own condition had coincidentally improved by one level, achieving something similar to Phiros. He called it the Dragon Mirror level, taken half from the Nine-Headed Dragon and half from a clear mirror.

After levelling up, the Flash Screen became rather less useful, in his battle with the Cthulhu King, he had activated the Flash Screen, but it only lasted an instant, and then it was destroyed by the violent red light, if he had not pulled it back so quickly, the Heirloom would probably have been utterly destroyed by now.

Although the thing looked like it had no upper limit, but it was still only at the Form Five middle level, back when he had first gotten it he had thought it was very suitable for self-defense during the fusion period, but now that that was over, it was no longer very useful.

"The other three sides of the Parliament had all made drastic moves, should we the Black Swamp Palace also…?" Skyharp glanced at the rest, but since nobody spoke, she began first.

"Drastic moves?" Garen laughed, now that he had achieved Form Five, he was already standing at the peak of the whole East Continent. He was no longer that concerned with the actions of the other three giants. "Forget about them, we do what we need to. How many people are there in the Palace now?"

"Other than the guards and miscellaneous workers, there are 2315 people in total in the Black Swamp Palace, these are the newest surveyed numbers. Of these, about 2000 of them are scholars. Most of them were recruited in extra batches after you left, Palace Master, and also, the most recent researcher rankings are…" Lala stood behind Garen, reporting softly.

Garen nodded slowly as he listened, and had more or less gotten a new understanding of the happenings within the Palace since he had left.

The governance plans in the Kingdom had seen many successes and achievements, developing the agriculture and production industries, encouraging birth rates, treating the people well, increasing trade and diplomacy. The whole Kingdom had also spawned many hunting teams, setting out to hunt edible Aberrated creatures for meat, while others were studying ways to tame the Aberrated creatures as livestock. Without the destruction brought on by wars and monsters, the development of the Kingdom seemed to be heading up and up.

A few days ago, the First Princess had gathered some strong totem users from among the civilians and the refugee nobles, creating an organization called the Pearl Party. The party's mission was to create a truly borderless world where men and women were equal. It was very successful in attracting many female totem users and forgers.

And the Fourth Prince decisively reacted by starting the National Development Society, taking on the responsibility to develop Kovitan and make it prosper, pulling in many wandering totem users.

The two sides fought like fire and oil, each starting their own activities to duke it out. Stuff like hunting strong Aberrated monsters, gathering precious plants and minerals, organizing mock battles and other such activities.

The third party, the Alliance of the many Guilds kept swaying between the two sides, earning benefits from both the monarchs-in-waiting who wanted to control Kovitan's true inheritance rights.

While they were wreaking havoc over there with their battles, the Black Swamp Palace's side only made one small move in the very beginning when they went out to catch the Poison Hag, and after that they made no more drastic moves, either resting and conserving their energy, or training their researchers and disciples. The maintenance of the entire Black Swamp Palace depended on the profits from the auction business and the many shops, their main commodity for sale being the results of the Technique Hall's creations and the things their scholars brought back from their outside excursions and trainings.

"By that you mean, that the system I wanted has been successfully created?" Garen asked in a deep voice.

"That is right." The person-in-charge of the Technique Hall, Master Calingan, replied, "I named it the Nine Snakes System, and completed the Palace Master's previous requests with extreme precision, after testing it many times, it has no problem whatsoever, and is now under partial trial."

"Nine Snakes? Not bad. We here at the Palace encourage our researchers and disciples to go out and gain experiences, and also we can accept hiring requests from outside powers, if the Palace's Elders have any troublesome needs, they can also set up a quest on the system, providing their own rewards. This platform system can be used as an optimal tool for communicate and distribute resources." Gare nodded.

After more and less understanding their recent developments, Garen's gaze moved to the scholars and disciples.

"The top three of the previous ranking competition, show yourselves."

Chapter 512: Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Instantly, the atmosphere in the hall seemed to have changed somewhat, the various Elders all looked rather interested, and even Ivycius, who had his eyes closed before, opened them now, looking at the three disciples who stepped out of the line.

The first two were the two masters that Garen had recruited as his disciples before, and the other was a young guy of about fifteen or sixteen. Unlike the polite respect of the other two, this young fellow respected him but tried hard to keep his head up, meeting Garen's gaze head-on, even if this determination made his whole body tremble, and slightly more than ten seconds was enough to cover his head with a cold sweat. But he still clenched his teeth and held in there.

"Who's Ansapello?" Garen asked calmly, but his gaze was already fixed on the young man whose face was growing paler and paler.

"It's that little idiot who just refuses to bend his head." Amidst the Elders, Wukang couldn't help but laugh. Instantly, the whole hall burst into fond laughter.

"I heard that you meditated under my statue, and said you would surpass me?" Garen was not laughing in the slightest, though. His tone instantly affected the atmosphere in the whole Grand Hall, and the other Elders' laughter also slowly quieted down.

The pale young man still held his head stubbornly high, his originally short brown hair soaked with sweat and plastered onto his forehead, while there were visible sweat stains on his clothes, but he still had no intention of lowering his head.

"Yes…!" He forced the word out of clenched teeth, under the pressure of Garen's gaze, even though Garen did not mean to pressure him at all, he was born with an innate and acute sensitivity towards danger, this was a talent, and this talent allowed him to travel thousands of miles, escaping death countless times, finally arriving at Kovitan and entering the Black Swamp Palace.

Right now, this talent had instead become his biggest burden, this sensitivity towards danger was making him shake like a leaf, his body and heart on the brink of collapse, as though he was at the bottom of the water, trying to float upwards to obtain oxygen, but there were seaweed and whirlpools holding his feet down.

This unbelievably overwhelming sense of suffocation made him almost want to lower his head and give in.

Whoosh…

The young man seemed to hear the sound of the tide retreating, the pressure all over him suddenly disappearing, his whole body shook slightly and he just nearly fell to the ground. His senior brother beside him held him up secretly, finally helping him steady his footing.

Evidently Garen had discovered the reason why he was shaking, and had taken the initiative to pull back the aura and energy emitting from his body, which finally let the young fellow return to normal.

"Good… very good!!" Everyone could see the smile on Garen's face clearly. His eyes showed his appreciation of the young man without hesitation. "The fourth level of the Black Water True Technique, you'll need to trade for it using quest badges, the Black Swamp Palace won't teach it to you for free, the first three levels are the most basic benefits for disciples and scholars, but after enjoying the privileges, you would naturally have duties you need to fulfill. For the fourth level, you'll need to complete a certain number of quests to obtain quest points yourselves, only then will you obtain it, and you are not allowed to teach it to each other privately. There's no problem, is there?"

"Of course!" The young man replied loudly, and panted once. "If we want to get something, we need to give something equal in return, that's what you're trying to tell us!"

"Go down and rest." Garen waved his hand, and there were instantly maids coming up to help the young man stand, bringing him down.

Garen's attitude had affected the attitudes of all the Black Swamp Palace higher-ups to some extent, and most of the Elders still looked friendly, only the Seven Night Tower's Angel looked slightly displeased, though she did not say anything, that young fellow had probably offended her at some point.

Garen did not bother with her, the Palace was not one fixed entity, there would be some slight conflicts between members, and he would ignore those, as long as they did not cross a certain line, everything could be considered the obstacles and trainings between Palace members.

After that, it was the Four Directions Sky Warriors in charge of various matters who came up to report on their respective areas, although these conditions had already been summarized and given to Lala for organization, now they reported to him again in detail, in a way to fill up the details.

The Four Directions Sky Warriors were peak-level fighting geniuses chosen from outside, after testing their qualifications and endurance, in the two short months since Garen left, two of these four positions had been challenged by outsiders, and the people in the positions changed. The challengers were from the prodigy training camps, these camps included the cream of the crop from among the competition of many normal scholars, and these elite members were once more divided into the possible candidates for the Four Directions Sky Generals as well the core scholars and disciples.

The whole Black Swamp Palace had formed a complete system, albeit one in the early stages.

The whole Black Swamp Palace was divided into five levels.

The first level was the Palace Master.

The second level included three powers: the Elders, the head manager Lala, and the Technique Hall, each of these was equal in power.

The third level had the core scholars, the Four Directions Sky Warriors, the prodigy training camp's instructor totem users, and the managers of the outside businesses.

The fourth level had the prodigy scholars.

The fifth level was the lowest level, and included the normal scholars, they were just one level higher than the regular maids and servants, or the domestic help.

Of these five levels, just in the fourth level itself, the Black Swamp Palace's prodigy scholars already had countless connections to the outside world, the higher-ranked scholars had already become future investment targets from many of the large and small factions outside, and these scholars had gathered many powers, some more and some less, big and small, behind them.

The power of the entire Black Swamp Palace was like a giant spider web, covering the whole Kingdom, and rapidly spreading to cover the entire Protection area.

This had already become a huge economic group with the Black Swamp Palace in the middle, and Garen at the very top.

The Four Directions Sky Generals came up to report on their different missions, the black-armored guards had been renamed from the Black Fire Guards from before to the Black Swamp Guards now, these Black Swamp Guards were more powerful than before, and the Four Directions Sky Warriors' powers combined, added to the power they had under their control, was more than capable of matching four peak-level Form Four totem users. Although this was the effect of using all sorts of methods, and disregarding all costs, but from here the terrifying power of the Green Vine Sphere was made evident, it was enough to make a normal person achieve the level of a peak-level fighter, as expected of the Green Vine Sphere, the heights of Vanderman's achievements throughout his lifetime.

Garen listened carefully from above, the Four Directions Sky Warriors were in charge of their relations with outside martial powers, they had two hundred members, and added to the totem users they had recruited from outside, they were now approaching eight hundred people, and were the Black Swamp Palace's most populated division.

These people were also in charge of the safety of the Black Swamp Palace's property, going out to hunt and gather all sorts of ingredients and Aberrated monsters, patrolling the perimeter, punishing intruders, performing troublesome tasks and the like, they were basically the whole Black Swamp Palace's cornerstone.

This power was also the one Garen had the most faith in, because the Green Vine Sphere only recognized him alone, all the power of these Black Swamp Guards came from the Green Vine Sphere, so this was also the largest inheritance left for him by Vanderman.

One by one, the Four Directions Sky Warriors reported their situations, and soon enough, the third West Sky General came up.

"Regarding that Poison Hag totem user from the Secret Service that we had apprehended, may we know how we should deal with her?" The West Sky General's voice was clear and crisp, it was actually a young woman, and she was also a prodigy scholar who had just successfully challenged the seat.

"The Poison Hag?" Garen touched his chin, he had also remembered that poison expert from the Secret Service who had messed around and tried to poison him to death, back at the headquarters, she sure was cocky, but now that the Black Swamp Guard had caught her, even she couldn't do anything. This was especially because the innate ability to resist poison increased as one's level of training in the Black Water True Technique increased, after all, this was based on the veins and blood transport pathways inside the Nine-Headed Dragon's body, although it had been adjusted to suit human use, that still did not mean that it had lost all of its initial usefulness.

Although it would not grant near immunity to poison like Garen had, it was still enough to attain an extremely high resistance to poison. To a poison-element totem user like the Poison Hag, this was basically a natural breeding ground for nightmares.

"Is there any news from the Secret Service's side?" Garen still cared more about the attitude of his previous boss who had protected him before.

"The department's vice president sent someone to enquire about the reason for her capture, and then they didn't send anyone else." The West Sky General replied respectfully.

"Then kill her. It'd be best if you can get the totem legacy from her before you do it. Any problems?" Garen nodded.

"I understand." The West Sky General retreated respectfully.

The North Sky General came up next to report.

"I am in charge of the supplies and defense, recently some of our mining veins have shown small-scale depletion, some veins that should still be rich in resources mysteriously went dry, we do not know the reason behind it. I have investigated it before secretly, but came up with nothing."

"Depleting veins?" Garen frowned, "Has anyone else investigated this?"

"There was Elder Skyharp." The North Sky General replied with respect.

Garen looked at Skyharp, who nodded lightly, indicating that she had a certain hold of the situation.

"The Technique Hall will also investigate this, Elder Skyharp, I'll be bothering you with this."

"I should be happy to help. The Nine Snakes System has been up and running for some time now, I'd like to earn some merit points as well." Skyharp smiled.

Garen nodded, the fact that this matter could reach all the way up to him meant that the people underneath had tried many times, and could still make no headway, only then did they present it to him.

"I'll stay in the Palace for some time, all matters will be arranged and handled by Lala, large matters can be decided by Elders Ivycius and Blizzard after discussion, alright, everyone go back to your respective jobs now. Master Calingan, please bring me to see the Nine Snakes System."

"It is my honor." Calingan hurriedly stood up.

Garen got up and left first, Calingan following with two of his apprentices, only then did the rest leave in turn.

The Nine Snakes System was a new generation management system Calingan had created by upgrading and incorporating the previous Palace totem system. It created a new mechanism, with some virtual units called merits as the core to everything.

Anybody who contributes to the Black Swamp Palace would have their contributions recorded down as the corresponding number of merit points, these merit points could be used to exchange anything, be it totems, knowledge, supplies, or information, equipment, techniques, even hiring muscle or buying people.

Of course, there were only things that could be traded in theory, in reality there were not many things that could be traded right now, they were mostly from that huge haul Garen had gotten from the Royal Treasury previously, these items were used as the start-up capital, to attract disciples, scholars, the Elders and the Sky Warriors to constantly contribute to the Palace, any supplies, legacy information or treasures they had gotten from the outside world and was not suitable for their own use could be handed to the Palace to trade for merit points, and then these could be used to exchange for things the Palace did have, things they needed.

This was the optimized organization of supplies, Master Calingan had the people from the Technique Hall organize all the complete totem legacies, and came up with thirteen high-level legacy systems, these being one of the Black Swamp Palace's bases.

"Thirteen types of totem legacies?" Garen was thoughtful. "That's good too, after activating their totem user qualifications by achieving the fourth level of the Black Water True Technique, the scholars need to choose the legacies suited to them and continue training, organizing the systems like this won't only increase our knowledge about totems, there will also be information about the supplies needed for all sorts of evolutions, while also increasing the detailed technical experiences. As expected of Master Calingan, you really have set the strongest foundations for the entire Black Swamp Palace."

Calingan hastily waved his hand.

"You flatter, Palace Master, if it weren't for your generosity, bringing out all of the legacies in your personal treasury to become the start-up capital, the Nine Snakes System might not be able to move so smoothly. I'm just doing what I should."

"Let's go, let's see the Nine Snakes' core." Garen nodded.

Chapter 513: Trace 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Going through the black stone palace halls, surrounded by the others, Garen quickly arrived at an isolated side hall.

There was an empty cemetery-like space between the side hall and the main hall, with several gravestones scattered around, there were no bricks laid out here, only yellow-black mud.

There was the occasional chirping of tunneling insects in the earth.

When Garen and the others walked onto this piece of ground, the earth on the ground instantly began moving, countless black-yellow earthworm-like insects breaking out of the ground, they had bodies like earthworms, but their mouths were jagged saws as they poked their heads out of the earth, as though smelling some delicious delicacies, they crawled towards Garen and his procession, rushing to surround them at high speeds.

"Close!" Master Calingan quickly drew a tactic gesture with one hand, the gesture was extremely complicated, and disappeared from the air after a flash.

All the earthworm insects on the surrounding ground paused in unison, their bodies stiffening, and then they all burrowed back into the earth, vanishing.

"These are the special aphids I raised here as a defense system, they might seem weak individually, but their largest advantage lies in their numbers, when they encounter a totem user’s invasion, they will fly up, and cover the surface of any Totem Light completely, tearing, biting, and absorbing the Totem Light, and only purely physical attacks can clear away these critters." Master Calingan explained as he walked.

Garen nodded, seeing the fear and apprehension on the others’ faces, he bet these people had all suffered the wrath of these insects before.

The group of five or six people went across the empty land and walked into the side hall, it was completely dark inside the hall, and utterly empty.

Psst…

All of a sudden, countless black air currents gathered in the center of the hall, these currents flew around in a circle, and then gathered rapidly gathered, forming a human shape with blurred facial features.

The silhouette was completely black, and bowed slightly at the group.

"Nine Snakes System, at your service." The voice was that of the sweetest, gentlest lady.

Garen walked up, and went around this blurred human shape as he looked at it carefully.

The silhouette seemed to be made of countless clouds of vapor, it had no material substance, and it did not move or act embarrassed under Garen’s scrutiny. It just stood there, quietly.

Garen observed it from a closer distance, reaching out his hand to touch its face lightly. It was cold and icy to the touch, without any real substance, as though putting his hand into a cloud of moist and cold air.

"This is just an outer appearance materialized by the Nine Snakes System, it has no use other than to communicate." Master Calingan explained from behind him. He walked up to a wall on one side of the hall, and patted the wall lightly.

"Are all the preparations complete?" Prepare to transfer the core control rights."

"All preparations complete." Nine Snakes replied softly.

After a moment, Garen walked out of the side hall, went across the empty land, and headed towards his own bedchambers.

After eating dinner, he did not bother with any other Palace matters either, he had already handed the fourth and fifth levels of the Black Water True Technique to the Nine Snakes System, as the barter item for merit points, it was just that more points were required.

After dinner, he found Demon Phoenix, who had already opened up completely to Island Master Skyharp, after making simple arrangements for Demon Phoenix and company to be visiting Elders in the Palace, Garen took Lala directly and walked out of the Palace.

Outside the Palace, a six-horse carriage had already been prepared, the drivers and guard teams all decorated rather extravagantly, they were basically magnificent carriages made of black crystal and sapphires.

Pulling the carriage were six handsome black Aberrated horses that looked like unicorns, they were powerful, capable of flight, and when necessary, could even dive into water.

Garen and Lala got onto the carriage, and flew from the Palace District, headed straight out of the Kingdom.

In the South East of the Kingdom, within the confines of the Ultimate Protection area, there was a mountain there that Garen had won over and handed over to the Tasura Academy led by his teacher Emin. This excursion of his was also to check on the Tasura Academy’s condition.

The carriage’s six unihorn horses grew black wings, and after several flaps, they easily carried the carriage up into the air with tremendous power.

There were also more than ten Black Swamp Guards escorting them on all sides, also riding black unihorn horses.

The entire group was extremely eye-catching in the middle of the sky, all the flying animals and beasts had to avoid them and make way.

Garen sat inside the carriage, resting with his eyes closed, when suddenly there was a man’s voice from outside.

"When did Palace Master Garen return? Why didn’t you inform everyone so we can have a welcoming party?"

The voice was very familiar, it was Grand Duke Cody, that old guy at the same level as Grand Duke Benoc, back then he had surrounded God Cloud, but was slightly injured due to the Distorted Beads, to think he had recovered so quickly.

Pulling open the carriage curtains, he saw another golden carriage cabin pulled by a three-headed green bird, also floating in mid-air just opposite Garen’s carriage. Grand Duke Cody’s cherubic face appeared at the entrance to the carriage, and he smiled as he looked this way.

"So it’s Grand Duke Cody, may I know if there is some urgent reason that you’re blocking my way?" Garen asked calmly.

"The Kingdom has been split into four, now that Your Excellency Garen has returned this time, you should govern your disobedient subordinates this time, otherwise a careless mistake might lead to disastrous consequences."

"Disastrous consequences? What disasters could happen in the Kingdom?" Garen was still looking at the other party calmly, "Or could it be, that the Grand Duke is warning me?"

"It’s up to you to interpret it however you want, I’ll just leave it at that." Cody let down the curtain, his carriage making a turn and flying towards the Grand Duke’s mansion.

Garen’s expression was sardonic, and then he suddenly blew out a breath of black air.

The black air shot away, growing larger and larger, fainter and fainter, and in an instant it had become a black wind, whistling towards Grand Duke Cody’s carriage.

The three-headed green bird pulling the carriage instantly fell into a panic, screeching, while inside the cabin, Cody snorted coldly, and a layer of faint golden light emanated from the cabin, blocking the black wind and keeping it outside.

"What do you mean by that, Palace Master Garen?!!" he howled from inside the cabin.

"Nothing in particular, I just thought your pet seemed rather cute, so I wanted to greet it."

Garen chuckled lightly, his carriage going past Cody’s from the side, and soon disappearing into the distant sky.

Just then, the three-headed green bird pulling Cody’s carriage gave a piercing shriek, and at the same time began to melt away, in just that instant, it melted into three mounds of black liquid, just like a candle, and began to rapidly evaporate, turning into clouds of black air that rose and vanished.

Only Cody maintained his golden light, forcefully keeping the carriage steady and floating in mid-air.

Inside the cabin, Cody’s round face was dark.

"Form Five…! I never thought…"

He murmured, while that little red girl in her red dress sat on his right, her fair legs swinging back and forth underneath the carriage seat.

"You can’t beat him now." The little girl’s childish voice rang out in the carriage cabin.

"It’s gotten slightly troublesome, do you want to hide out for a bit?" Cody looked at the little girl, his tone strangely as though he was talking to an equal with power as strong as his.

"It’s okay." The little girl shook her head, "You just be careful."

Cody nodded, and didn’t say anything else.

"The people from the Black Swamp Palace are growing more and more arrogant, it is true that the subordinates follow the Palace Master’s behavior. Looks like I have no choice but to join forces with the people on that side?"

"Join forces? Do you want to open up the Ultimate Protection?" The little girl asked curiously from the side.

Cody did not reply, but his expression darkened.

********************

At night, on a somewhat shorter mountain near the Kingdom, amidst the long line of fortresses covering the mountain peaks, there were many clear and bright lights, illuminating the peaks into a bright white land.

The highest of these was a newly-built white mansion.

In the wide and large hall, the milk-white stone walls were printed with many carvings of Great White Bear, Black Panthers and Sabertooth Tigers, these three different creatures were seen in many different images and carvings, representing the three creature totems that formed the three largest branches at the very core of the Tasura Academy, and the drawings on the walls showed many different types of development directions, there were Great White Bears with wings, some had a long and thick tentacle instead of a right arm, some had four eyes, and the same went for the Black Panthers and Sabertooth Tigers, each showing a different area of development.

The hall was brightly lit inside, a piano band slowly playing by the wall, the slow and comforting music emanating gently through the hall, and even wafting into the darkness outside the window past the fluttering curtains.

There was also a long rectangular table by the right side of the hall, with platters of fruits and other dishes on it, provided for the guests’ consumption.

The guests participating in the gathering were all dressed extravagantly, the men in fancy collars and the women in swaying skirts, but no matter what status these guests had, the key reason for their attending this banquet was either to see the Black Swamp Palace Master, whose reputation had skyrocketed recently, or to meet and talk to one another, building a sufficiently large web of connections.

Just then, Garen was standing with several white-haired old men, playing with an intricate crystal glass in his hand as he listened to the old men’s low conversations carefully. He wore a black-red suit, his figure long and slender, his golden hair falling over his shoulders, his jade-perfect skin the secret object of envy for all the women present.

This world only had tuxedos previously, but Garen had decisively chopped the tails off the tuxedos, adjusting it slightly to become an Earth-like suit, and he instantly felt a lot more at home in it.

He listened to what his teacher Emin was saying carefully, his face the picture of concentration. All around him were the highest-level elders of the Tasura Academy, the leaders of some smaller academies that were friendly with Tasura, as well as some grassroots leaders and upper-level nobles who had come to the Kingdom to join this banquet. Other than a very select few, the most of them were fairly old, at the very least in their forties.

Garen was especially eye-catching amidst such a crowd. The higher-ups all stood together here, while the people in most of the other places were mainly the elite scholars of these academies and the higher-level nobles from the Kingdom.

The important characters stood in one place, the younger generations and less important people stood in one circle, the division was obvious, and there was only the occasional moment when the important figures called some of their young ones over to be introduced to their peers.

Although the younger ones all formed their own little circles, they would still steal envious glances at the upper-level circle, with Garen at the center.

"In the blink of an eye, three years have passed, thinking back on everything that had happened these past few years, it still feels like a dream." Emin drank the fragrant wine, his gaze a mix of complicated sadness.

"Teacher, you always like sighing about things, the Academy has been rebuilt and completely unified, wasn’t that your biggest wish?" Garen said softly.

"People are greedy by nature, or maybe it’s precisely because my biggest wish and goals have been fulfilled, that’s why I’m feeling rather empty inside." Emin shook his head, and said self-deprecatingly, "You’re the hottest topic right now, even in the East Continent you are among the best of the best, to have taught you back then, truly was my biggest pride and joy."

"You exaggerate." Garen laughed, "There are still many things that I don’t know, and I need you to teach me."

"Don’t say such modest things, you have surpassed me long ago, to be frank, I was only slightly useful to you when setting the foundations, the rest of it was all your own hard work." Emin waved his hand.

"I bet that back then, when the Palace Master was learning the foundations, he had already demonstrated his immense talent, right?" One of the elderly members of the Academy asked with a laugh.

"Speaking of which, as for how the Palace Master used to be, perhaps only Big Brother Emin knows best."

Some of the elders started asking as well.

Emin just chose some of Garen’s stories from back then, he still felt vaguely awed until now.

Back then, Garen had only shown extraordinary talent in tactics, but unfortunately, even though he had the talent, he did not want to walk the path of tactics, and insisted on specializing in totem evolution. As for using tactics to fight, that method did not suit Garen at all.

Emin had felt quite sorry about that for some time. Mentioning that, he began to discuss some trivial matters from back then with the few elders enthusiastically.

Garen just stood at the side and listened quietly, smiling occasionally.

After listening for some time, he excused himself by saying he needed the washroom, leaving alone to go to the nighttime balcony outside the hall. Standing in front of the semicircular banister, he looked down into the distance, the little smattering of lights from the villages at the bottom of the mountain were like the many stars in the night sky, bunching together in constellations. The night breeze blew on his face, coolly, and with a hint of fragrance.

Garen sniffed lightly, the fragrance seemed to come from an extreme distance, barely there and sometimes not, but even he could not tell what flowering plant it was.

Chapter 514: Trace 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Holding the banister with his hand, the smooth and cool wooden handrail was soft, and soon began to grow warmer under his fingers. It was rare for him to find time to relax, Garen stood there on the balcony, and fell into a slight silence.

After some time.

"Lucian, why did you run all the way here?" The balcony one floor beneath him just happened to face the second floor, and a young man's crisp and clear voice came from below.

"I just wanted to calm down a bit by myself." Another calm and cool man's voice spoke, his tone was not particularly icy, but it gave one a feeling of cool distance.

"Bales and the others are here, as are Violet and Corin, aren't you going out to meet them?" The clear young man's voice asked softly.

The other person did not reply.

"Don't be so shy, won't ya?"

"..."

"It's so rare to see so much good food, normally it's hard to get even a bite, if it weren't for you bringing us in here, we probably still wouldn't be able to touch such goods stuff, come on, join us." The clear young man seemed to be yanking him now.

"Good food? You guys won't really let yourselves go and eat…" This time the cold young man finally seemed to express some emotion. "Did you think I worked so hard to get four invitations just so you could come in here and eat?"

"Don't be so petty, we're all partners through thick and thin." The clear young man patted the other person's shoulder, "We can't match the important guys on the second floor, in that case, wouldn't the good food on the table be more practical?"

"Lucian, your old man's asking you to go to the second floor." Suddenly there was a clear voice cutting through the hustle and bustle of the first-floor hall, it was a sweet young girl's voice.

And then on the first floor, Lucian covered his face with his hand. The people on the first floor fell silent for a second, and then burst into laughter. Those who could make it here were either well-bred nobles or merchants with a considerable background, or eminent scholars, but under the presence of Garen and the Black Swamp Palace, everyone acted completely proper, so in such a high-level noble banquet, Lucian instantly became famous.

His old man was also an upper-level noble, with considerable power, and Lucian had been a model among the original Kovitan nobles of his age, he was handsome and dashing, with extraordinary powers, and his snow-white skin earned him the nickname 'Snow Prince'. When he was escaping to the Kingdom from his territory, he had made friends with some common folk from the villages, and this story had been the popular gossip among the nobles for some time now.

To think he even dared to bring some village bumpkins to such an upper-class banquet, and his father allowed him to mess around like that.

Listening to the commotion from the hall downstairs, Garen could not keep his lips from curving upwards. These people reminded him of his life back then in Vanderman's estate, although that life was short, it was unprecedentedly peaceful, just like the Secret Technique World.

"Why are you here alone?" A mild young girl's voice came from behind him.

Garen did not reply, he merely continued to look at the distant scene of the mountains at night, enjoying his rare bit of peace.

The girl behind him walked up to his side of her own accord, and also put her hands on the banister.

"Could it be that even someone as powerful as Lord Garen has troubles that he cannot solve?" The girl stood on Garen's right, wearing a long white dress that showed off her small waist, full breasts, long and slender legs, her soft body fragrance, and her fiery-red waist-length hair cascading behind her, tied with a white hairband in the middle.

This was a very pretty and confident young girl, no more than seventeen or eighteen years in age, in the middle of her most glorious age.

"I'm human too, I will also have common worries and troubles, is that very strange?" Garen said calmly.

He turned his head to glance at the girl.

"Your heart is beating very fast."

The girl's face stiffened slightly, and she tried her best to smile naturally.

"I'm just slightly excited to see my idol."

She was confident that she had the purest appearance out of everyone in the banquet, she had investigated before, Garen should be fondest of this type, pure, cute, and understanding.

This was her chance to make it big, as long as she caught hold of this opportunity, her ailing family would instantly be resurrected from the dead, she was an ambitious woman, as long as she could make it with the Black Swamp Palace Master, no matter what price she had to pay, she was mentally prepared for it.

But seeing Garen's clear gaze and mild attitude, she was beginning to suspect if something had gone wrong with her attractiveness.

"You're still young, there are many paths in life, don't bet everything you have before you can see everything clearly." Garen looked at the girl in front of him, for some reason he suddenly thought of his younger sister from the Secret Technique World, Ying Er, abruptly he noticed that other than their hair color and their personalities, the two of them were eerily similar in their appearances and their auras.

I will go back there.

He decided in his heart, it had only been three years since he transmigrated to this world, he still had a chance. He just needed to discover the secret of the Black Smoke Pot.

If he could settle the threat posed by Hellgate, after that, he could truly start investigating the mysteries of the Black Smoke Pot.

Garen reached out his hand and patted the girl's hair.

"Go back."

A gentle power pushed the girl away lightly, rendering her speechless.

The girl's face was slightly pale, after looking at Garen's back, she eventually decided to turn around and return to the hall.

Not long later, a familiar figure walked onto the balcony. She wore a black evening gown with a corset, it was a clean and pretty long-legged woman, with legs unnaturally long, especially when compared to a normal woman's proportions, her long brown hair tied into a ponytail that gave her a handsome look.

"Master." The woman stood behind Garen, and spoke softly."

"Sylvia, how are things on Sofea's side? Is Jenny(1) still okay?" Garen turned around and asked softly.

Since Sylvia was given to Garen by the First Princess, and the parasite in her body was removed, Garen arranged her to stay by his cousin Hathaway's side, returning to her previous life, it was just that her job changed from the Palace District to Garen's subordinate. She constantly updated Garen about his cousin's safety on that side.

"Everything is okay on Miss Sofea's side, and Miss Jenny has entered the White Phoenix Forest Academy, and is a lot more reserved now." Sylvia was staying next door to Hathaway now, so they were more or less neighbors.

"That's good, about the First Princess…"

"The First Princess has cut all connections with me." Sylvia had been sold to the First Princess as a slave back then, and now that she had been passed on to Garen, she had become Garen's female slave, but thankfully Garen did not make any terrible requests of her. After some time without seeing him, if Manager Lala had not suddenly summoned her, she would have more or less forgotten that she was a slave after all.

"Alright, that's all." Garen nodded his head to show he understood. "Oh, yeah, call Lala in here."

Sylvia bowed and retreated. Soon enough, Lala walked onto the balcony, dressed in a long white dress with silver trimmings.

"Have you found the person I asked you to find?"

"Not yet…" Lala frowned and lowered her head, "Sorry, milord, but according to the way Lord Leila acted when he left, it didn't seem like he was returning to Obscuro."

Garen mused, "Continue putting people to it, inform me immediately once you find him."

"Understood."

"Also, get Kid to come here."

"Kid?" Lala was slightly confused, but she quickly realized what he meant, and smiled bitterly. "Understood." Kid was always mysterious in his appearances and disappearances, and it would not be easy to find him in such a short time, but since the boss had already asked for him, the people underneath would naturally have to work harder.

Upon returning this time, Garen had handed the job of exchanging the Glittering Water with the Cthulhu King for Cthulhu's Origins to the other people in the Black Swamp Palace, Lala was in charge of sending specific people, to secretly head towards the Cthulhuism Society's base to meet with them. He no longer needed to handle this matter personally. The remaining time was to be spent researching the secrets of Kid and that little girl in red next to Cody once more.

Just thinking about that strange little girl with her snake-like tongue, for some reason, Garen's heart felt mysteriously uncomfortable.

After Lala left, the hall behind him began to slowly quiet down for some reason.

The time ticked by, and after goodness knows how long, Garen suddenly frowned, and turned around slowly.

Just then, on the ground by the entrance into the hall, there was a small black cat with red eyes. It sat crouched on the floor, licking its lips occasionally, its large red eyes staring at Garen curiously.

"How did you get in here?' Garen stared at the red-eyed black cat, frowning as he asked.

Meow~~

The black cat meowed adorably.

"Stop pretending!" Garen frowned even deeper, and a black wind rose out of nowhere, blowing onto the black cat with a whoosh.

Amidst the splashing sound of water, the black cat suddenly stiffened, and its body actually started to melt within the next few seconds, like a candle baked at high heat. In an instant, it had become a puddle of black water on the floor.

"It hurts…" A clear little's girl's voice came from the black water.

Garen narrowed his eyes, and saw that before he knew it, a pair of bright red lips had formed in the black water, and that was where the voice was coming from.

From the small mouth, it was as though the black water reversed in time, going back one step at a time, to form blood, bones and flesh from the black water, finally forming a completely naked, pure white little girl.

The little girl wore nothing at all, her pale red hair falling over her shoulders, her height about half of Garen's, her slightly developed body particularly child-like and tempting. She was not embarrassed in the slightest, however, and just stared at Garen curiously with her blood-red eyes.

"Your existence makes me feel very uncomfortable." Garen grasped his right hand.

Bam!

The little girl instantly exploded into countless bits of minced meat and blood, spraying all over the floor.

Strangely, the countless minced meat gathered together again, once more forming the little girl's body, and she walked towards Garen, one step at a time.

Garen's eyes flashed vaguely with the violence and bloodlust of the Nine-Headed Dragon, a faint black mist appearing around his body.

He did not know how this little girl found him, but it was very likely to do with his meeting Cody that morning. Now it looked like she was trying to give him a warning? Or was she here to test his strength and attitude?

The surroundings around him seemed to have become an illusion, but it did not feel like an illusion at all, rather than calling it an illusion, it seemed to be a sort of separation, a spatial separation.

"Why?" The little girl looked at him curiously. "Why don't you like my body? Aren't you guys all like this?"

"Did Cody send you here?" Garen asked in a low voice. "You do look somewhat strange, but why did you come looking for me?"

"Have you seen the Door to Heaven?" The little girl did not reply to his question, and instead asked another strange one of her own.

"The Door to Heaven?"

Translator's Note:

He keeps saying 珍妮, but I'm pretty sure he means Dani...

Chapter 515: Seed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Wooo~~~

There seemed to be a strange howling in the air, like the siren of a faraway train, or like the roar of a certain creature.

Garen turned his head to the side, and suddenly looked at the night sky outside the balcony.

He did not know when it started, but there were many giant silver metal rings hanging in the sky, these rings as though suspended in mid-air, the top half piercing into space, hanging in the night sky without moving in the slightest.

The countless silver rings were all over the sky, scattered into many smatterings, extending all the way into the unseen distance. Each metal ring was more than ten meters in diameter, more than a meter in thickness, unnaturally clear.

The moonlight fell down evenly, reflecting a faint silver light off these silver rings.

"Did you say the Door to Heaven?" Garen turned around, once more looking at the red-eyed girl who had mysteriously appeared.

"That is the very first origin." The girl widened her blood-red eyes. "Only Listeners can see it."

Garen looked at the little girl in front of him, and suddenly felt some bone-piercing chill on the back of his right hand. He raised his hand, and saw an eye-catching red dot on the back of his right hand, just like a red mole.

He remembered, this was the Imprint of the Listener that Kid had given him back then, at the time Grand Duke Cody had even asked him a strange question, whether or not Garen could show him his Imprint, but Garen had rejected him.

"Then what is this?" He raised his hand, and waved his Imprint at the girl opposite him.

"That is your qualifications, the qualifications you earned." The little girl walked up to Garen, and also raised her head to look at the night sky outside.

"Only with these qualifications, can you truly see this world." The little girl said, somewhat dazedly.

For a moment, neither of them spoke, they just looked at the scene in the sky quietly, the countless silver round rings hanging in the sky, as though it was just a strange painting.

Garen seemed to be looking at the scene in the sky, but at the same time part of his attention was spent on staying aware of the girl’s movements.

He had not been able to kill her each of those times just now, this strange phenomenon made his heart waver slightly, it would be understandable if just like him, she had a natural talent such as Nine Lives, but strangely, his five senses or his spiritual sensitivity had vaguely noticed that the girl’s true body seemed to be in some unknown space, and her body out here seemed to only be the shadow she was projecting outside, no matter how many times he killed it, he would not harm the actual body at all. It was like using the light to destroy a shadow, no matter how many times you did it, there was no way you could harm somebody like that.

"Don’t you want to go and see?" The girl laughed suddenly, "Entering this world for the first time, a world that only we Listeners could ever enter before."

"What is your aim?" Garen glanced at her.

"Aim? Of course." It was as though the girl only then remembered her reason for coming, "Let me think… What was my aim for coming here?" She massaged her forehead, acting troubled.

By now Garen had sort of noticed, this fella seemed to be slightly crazy, there was something wrong with her brain, her words and actions followed the changes in her emotions completely, and even her emotions were completely impossible to grasp.

"The Listeners’ world, is it a real world?" he asked again.

"That’s right… This place is a strange existence, me, Kid, and more, there are ten other people in total, we were all born here." The little girl’s memories were awakened by Garen’s words, and her attention diverted.

"Once, several thousand years ago, you humans were still fighting to the death over the Listener’s Imprint, but hilariously, now barely a few people know about this world’s existence…"

"What are the benefits of this place?" Garen stared at the little girl as he continued asking.

"Benefits?" The girl tapped her lips, "The things you find here, you can bring them out to the other side, but only the Imprinted can take them out. Hmm… there’s also the Door to Heaven, you can find the existence of the Door to Heaven here, isn’t the ring on your hand an item from this place as well?"

Her gaze fell on the Troll Grip that Garen was wearing.

"Ring?" Garen touched the Troll Grip instinctively, this ring was the gift given to him by the city troll, why would it be a product of this place?

"The City Troll, I met it before, it’s really tall, and travels around everywhere, only creatures that give him enough water and food with get this ring as a present." The girl seems to know everything, suddenly she turned her head slightly, as though listening to something.

"How did you know…" Garen was interrupted before he could finish.

Shh~~

The girl held a finger to her lips, and continued posing as though she was listening to something.

"It’s coming…"

"What?" Garen frowned, staring at her.

"It’s that big tortoise. Come, I’ll show you something cool!" The girl suddenly pulled Garen’s hand, leaping lightly out the balcony.

Whoosh…

The two of them actually jumped straight out of the balcony, landing directly on the ground.

Bam!

They crashed hard onto the ground, and the girl dragged Garen into a run without any further words.

Garen did not know what she was planning either, but he did not resist, because he could not feel any ill intent from the girl. It was as though after they chatted for a while, the feeling of discomfort she gave him grew thinner and fainter.

The little girl pulled him and ran, leaving the mansion altogether, dashing straight down the mountain.

At such high speeds, Garen turned around to look at the mansion, the place was still brightly illuminated, and there were still many people gathered inside, it was just that they were all frozen on the spot, motionless, as though time had stopped at that moment.

Some people held their wine glasses and were about to sip from it, the wine inside tilting and almost about to drip out from the corners of their mouths. Some people were waving their hands with a smile, their arms suspended in mid-air. Others were turning and tilting their bodies to the music.

The band’s musician had plucked one of the strings, and the silk string bent at a slight angle, but it showed no signs of straightening out again. At the main entrance, a young man had been tripped by the door frame, and was about to fall, his body slanting in mid-air, but he just did not fall.

Everything and everyone, all the people and creatures seemed to have had their bodies and wills frozen, only Garen and the little girl could move.

The two of them wove through the forest, the Nightlight Moths frozen in mid-air like insects stuck in amber, embedded into the air, without moving an inch.

As he passed by, Garen simply pulled with one hand, and with a tear, the moth’s wing was torn down, the faint poison powder scattering everywhere, just like a small cloud of black dust.

"Did you see that? This world has countless times that flow at different speeds, the world you usually see is just a level that flows at a slower-than-average speed. And once the time is at extremely slow speeds or even stops completely, these creatures moving at high-speeds will all be revealed, that is when you can truly see what they look like." The girl seemed to be talking to herself, or perhaps she was explaining to Garen.

As the girl spoke, the scenes around them moved faster and faster, and grew more and more blurred.

At first he could still sort of see that they were still in the Ultimate Protection area, but by the end everything had turned into blurred shadows that could not be identified.

Garen could only be dragged by the little girl around, turning left and right as they moved at lightning speeds.

He did not know how much time had passed, when suddenly the girl stopped abruptly.

"Look…" The girl’s voice came from beside his ear.

The view around him suddenly focused into vision.

This seemed to be a grey-black wasteland, they were surrounded by grey hills and dunes, with a smattering of black plants and moss growing on them.

The ground was completely bald, there was not a bit of green to be seen, occasionally there would be a few tombstones stuck in the earth, but the words on them were already utterly worn off.

Garen looked up.

There was no moon in the sky, only countless pale blue stars scattering their faint light. The faint white cloud vapor was vaguely there, but seemed not to move at all.

"See… This is the truest view of the world…" The little girl released Garen’s hand, smiling brilliantly.

Bam!

There was a deep knocking sound from far away.

Bam!

And another.

Bam!

The third sound.

The sounds kept coming, one after the other, like footsteps, as though there was some heavy creature rushing towards here, one step at a time.

Garen looked at that direction from a distance.

Between the black hills, he saw a huge black tortoise crawling over to them.

There was a small piece of grassy land on the tortoise’s back, several tombstones stuck on it, slantingly, forming a small arch-shaped graveyard. From a distance, this small graveyard was actually its shell.

The tortoise’s limbs were four dried-out, branching tree roots, thick and grey-black, every time they were lifted and put down again, they would make a deep crashing noise on the ground.

Garen stared hard at the tortoise, his wariness raised to the highest. The whole tortoise was more than ten meters tall, and as it got closer, its huge body also became clearer.

But what surprised Garen the most was not that, it was the things behind the tortoise.

There was actually a veritable crowd of pale blue silhouettes following behind the tortoise, these humanoid shapes floated and glowed slightly, translucent like ghosts, with men and women, young and old among them, they all wore different clothing, and had no legs underneath their bodies, having instead a cloud of blue light.

"What is that?" Garen asked in a murmur, although he had already experienced many miraculous things in the Totem World, but this huge creature here and the meaning of the people behind him could not help but make Garen’s heart stiffen.

"That is the Giant Tortoise." The girl replied, "Normally it only exists for an instant… Mm, according to your units of time, about a hundred-and-ninety-thousandth of a second. But in this world, we can see its actions clearly."

"And these things behind it are…?" Garen watched the giant tortoise walk past him, carrying the large crowds of pale blue figures behind it.

"These?" The girl followed Garen’s gaze, and instantly understood that he was asking about that long line of pale blue figures. "They’re spirits~~"

"Spirits?"

"The souls of people after they die, duh." The little girl explained casually. "Aren’t you scared?" She seemed to be slightly surprised, at first she had come to see Garen out of curiosity, to find out what was so special about this young man that her host was so wary of. But the more she got to know him now, the more she felt that Garen was different from the rest.

"You just came with me like that, aren’t you scared I’ll hurt you?" The little girl finally couldn’t help but ask.

"You can’t hurt me." Garen laughed. Everything in front of him now, seemed to be slowly merging with the Ancient Endor legends from the Secret Technique World.

This world, had been mentioned before in the Ancient Endor legends.

The legendary world where everything stopped, the great hero Helra had fought here with the Serpent of Fate, and although he managed to kill the Serpent of Fate in the end, he also sacrificed an arm that stayed here forever.

Only creatures with the same Imprint can harm each other, and that was also why the Great Sages who gave the heroes their Imprints could not fight themselves, so they had to trick the hero Helra into acting.

Even the great Earth Mother admitted that she could not interfere with the matters here.

But what intrigued Garen was that the legend had evidently been passed down in the Secret Technique World, and yet there was such a scene in the Totem World. The two worlds seemed to have countless connections.

The girl was still recovering from her surprise at Garen’s words, and just then, the huge graveyard tortoise had walked past them on the right, the countless blue silhouettes gathering behind it, like a blue neon-colored river, twisting and turning into oblivion.

The humanoid spirits in the river were all dazed and lost-looking, as though they had utterly lost their self-awareness, and was just floating stupidly behind the Giant Tortoise.

Garen couldn’t help but think of the Underworld Carriage. In the library of the ruined city, that Underworld Carriage he had encountered seemed to have some strange connection to this Giant Tortoise.

"Back when Cody was still small, I brought him to see the Giant Tortoise, and he was scared half to the death. Why don’t you have any reaction at all?" The little girl’s expression was full of confusion. "Don’t you want to know where the Giant Tortoise will bring all these spirits?"

Chapter 516: Seed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen smiled, but remained silent. According to the myths, this Giant Tortoise was the guide to the underworld, and the world that it was heading to was not a place living creatures could get involved with. Even merely looking would cause blindness.

"It’s heading towards the underworld. Don’t you want to take a look?"

"Is it?" Garen only smiled, but did not fall for her tricks at all.

The little girl’s eyes darted around.

"Weren’t you looking for Kid? I know where he is now."

"Oh?" Garen looked at her with a faintly shocked expression. "You heard the things I said earlier?"

"That guy Kid has constantly been hanging one at one place recently, so it would be really easy to find him." The girl had a sly look in her eyes. "He seems heartbroken."

"Heartbroken?" Garen never thought that Kid would be so grown up.

"Let’s go, I’ll take you there!" The little girl pulled Garen’s hand again, before their surroundings became blurry suddenly, while countless images flashed around constantly amidst the blurriness.

After an unknown amount of time, their surroundings stopped moving and became clear again.

Garen stood up steadily and took in his surroundings.

He and the little girl stood in a vast farm that was filled with sporadic clusters of large yellow pumpkins.

Most of the pumpkins were hollowed out, and although they were some solid ones, only a few of them were left.

The ground below his feet was pitch-black, as if it were lifeless, scorched earth.

In the furthest and deepest end of the farm stood a wooden house. The faint sound of what sounded like Kid's voice could be heard from within, singing to a tune.

Garen glanced at the little girl, but realized that she had disappeared suddenly, leaving him by himself at their original spot.

He furrowed his eyebrows, and walked towards the house on the far end of the farm.

As the distance between them closed, and the sound of Kid’s singing became clearer.

"...if you plant a girl in spring, you’ll reap many girls in autumn…"

Garen’s words were caught in his throat; when he came closer, he suddenly saw a small piece of empty land in front of the house, where Kid stood watering something with a kettle in his hands.

The empty piece of land was merely an area made up of black dirt, planted in the clearing was an enlarged egg; the bottom half of the egg was stuck inside the dirt, while the top half was being watered by the kettle.

As if he had heard something, Kid raised his head and turned towards Garen’s position.

"Nineheads Boss?"

"What are you doing?" Garen walked towards Kid.

"I’m sowing seeds," Kid answered simply. "If I plant them in spring, I’ll have a wife in autumn."

Garen patted Kid’s head, unsure of what to say.

That little girl had a mysterious attitude. At first she seemed to harbor malicious intent towards Garen, but later realized that he was an interesting plaything and ended up playing with him later. Finally, her attitude changed again, and she sent him to Kid voluntarily. No one knew what she was actually thinking about.

"What is this place exactly? That little girl brought me here," Garen finally asked in a low voice.

When Kid heard him say ‘little girl’, his body shivered suddenly, as if he were scared somehow. "This is the True World, the real world, that we Listeners can come into contact with. All of the appearances that we are usually unaware of, they will all show up here. And since time has stopped here, even if one spends an eternity in here, only a few seconds would have passed outside."

"True World?" Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

"Yes, relatively speaking. Boss, the place where you used to be was the opposite, Normal World, a place where you were unable to see the truth directly," explained Kid elaborately. "It’s rumored that the strongest Totem User can touch the borders of this world, possessing the qualifications to enter this place. In other words, things in the Normal World, they're present here, while the things that are absent in the Normal World would still be present here. The Normal World is an extension of the what appears in the True World, except that it’s just a part of its outer ring. The relationship between both of them, when loosely described as a simile, can be likened to an egg; the egg white is the Normal World, while the egg yolk is the True World."

"So what does the Door to Heaven mean then?"

"The True World is a visualization of all truths and all sources, while the Door to Heaven is the door to all of the sources in this world. I’m unsure about it myself, but perhaps there are deeper layers of the True World inside, where deeper levels of truth and sources may be seen. Or maybe it’s a whole different thing. No one has went in before, because no one can open it." Kid was honest as usual, answering everything that he was asked.

But Garen had been thrown into this world mysteriously, and still had some doubts in his heart. Even though he had received some explanations from Kid, these uncertainties had not disappeared yet.

"My guess is that someone wanted to open the Door to Heaven, so that girl dragged Boss here, perhaps to use Boss’s powers to stop that person," Kid held the kettle and pondered. "After all, her parasitic strength isn’t strong enough."

He paused. "Or maybe, she’s thinking of changing parasites…"

"Whatever, just send me back first," Garen exhaled.

"Alright," Kid nodded, before pulling Garen’s hand, and leaping a step forward gently.

Tch!

Their surroundings flashed in a blur once again, and a loud noise echoed beside their ears, before the sound of a band slowly filled their ears.

Garen’s vision turned black and lit up again, before he realized that he was standing on the balcony as before, his hands still rested on the railing as he looked into the faraway distance. Meanwhile, Kid was standing beside him.

"You said that she may have been looking for me because she wanted to change her parasite?" Garen merely transferred his thoughts to Kid, no longer having to open his mouth to speak to him directly.

"Yes, that’s very likely, the Door to Heaven exists within the True World, but there was once an Imprinted madman that used some unknown measures to merge a part of the True World with the real world. Now, many strange occurrences are the result of this mergence," answered Kid while nodding.

Garen thought of Hellgate suddenly, and using unknown measures, Obscuro caused the Great Turmoil. The black copper was also part of their doing, and after the Great Turmoil, various weird occurrences also followed. The likeliest person to be this madman, was undoubtedly and certainly Hellgate.

"Thus, since parts of both worlds have merged, the Door to Heaven will probably be revealed in reality," Kid continued to explain. "She came looking for you because she probably saw the changes that would happen afterwards. When the Door to Heaven finally appears and that Imprinted madman wants to push it open, he would definitely choose to do it in the True World where he would not be disturbed by anyone, and since time stops there, only other Imprinted individuals would be able to intervene. His threats would be very much smaller."

"So she was making preemptive damage control measures?" Garen said immediately. "Why don’t you want the Door to Heaven to be pushed open?"

Kid became silent at once.

After some time, he finally opened his mouth to speak again.

"The Door to Heaven is the source of everything in the True World, but once it’s pushed open… We Listeners all have bad feelings about that."

Garen had a vague feeling that it was likely the Door to Heaven had a certain link to the Black Smoke Pot that he passed through in the beginning.

When he returned this time, he truly came into contact with the mysterious world that Kid inhabited. His heart simply defined the True World as the inner world, while reality was defined as the outer world, making everything clearer.

Now he had grasped more than half of everything, and he was certain that the person who had plans with the inner world’s Door to Heaven, was almost certainly Hellgate.

Hellgate got out for his own goals, and he had also integrated all of the resistance forces in an attempt to uncover the true secrets of the world. Was this the true insights and thinking after achieving the peak of Form 5?

Unfortunately, according to the original historia, he fell short in the end, and what lay behind the Door to Heaven was still something that eluded the world. However, the preparation and work underwent to open the Door to Heaven caused serious injuries, and even death to befall the people of the outer world, and although mankind’s violent counter attacks that followed were enough to exceed Hellgate’s limits, it eventually ended up in hatred and grief.

"What do we need to do to open the Door to Heaven?" Garen inhaled deeply, before asking in a low voice.

Kid fell silent again for a moment, but answered regardless.

"The Door to Heaven is the foundation of the sources of the world, the symbol of all of the rules of truth. In order to open it… One can only observe it continuously and investigate its shifts."

"Shifts?"

"Yes," Kid nodded. "Every time the world undergoes major shifts, shifts enough to affect the rules of changes, the Door to Heaven will undergo changes as well."

"Major changes…" Garen seemed to understand the basic reasoning for Hellgate to unleash the Great Turmoil. If it was merely the doing of a mad scientist for the sake of research…

Suddenly, he remembered that this planet was merely one of the countless planets in the universe, thus, did the inner world of this planet, exist on other planets as well?

Suddenly, he realized, that if the Secret Technique World also existed inside the inner world, then, those myths, those relics…

Except that the inner world was a wasteland, and there were too many strange occurrences inside, and most of them were derived from fixed rules which would not allow normal life forms to step in at all, but perhaps he would be able to find certain clues about Warlocks from there.

Garen could now feel that he was currently walking on the path that countless Warlocks had crossed before.

However, he was not using normal means. Besides the fact that he had crossed through the Secret Technique World, he was also carrying talents, attributes, and abilities that had no relation to Warlocks at all. Although the Black Smoke Pot’s startup and pass-through was merely an accident, if the explosion of the nuclear bomb and the volcano had not happened at the same time to amplify and activate a specific power, or if the self defense necklace that Old Man had given him hadn’t worked; he would have not been able to come to this world if even one of these conditions were lacking.

Garen had a feeling that he was an illegal immigrant that had accidentally arrived on the planet where Warlocks once walked. He had initially hoped to walk on the path of the Warlocks, but because of the possibilities of his attributes and talents, in a short span of time he was able to achieve the progress that others would only reach in decades, and this terrifying rate of growth allowed him to walk in the direction of self-exploration.

However, this speed was too fast, and did not allow him to brake at all, instantly going over his head instead.

Earth’s knowledge systems combined abilities and talents, and Garen had now walked onto a path that only belonged to himself.

When he thought of this, Garen became aware and squeezed the railing. At this moment, Kid’s voice continued to ring out beside him.

"There was once a parasite that deduced something about the Door to Heaven, saying that it was an entrance that separated everything, that it was the door of life, and also the door of death. The inside of the entrance was chaotic, random. At the same time, it was also the source of all of the rules. Perhaps that sentence was also the reason that influence people’s desires to open it."

After listening to that sentence, for unknown reasons, Garen suddenly remembered the lonely period of time that he endured while traveling to this planet.

Within the darkness, there seemed to be a large river that pushed him along, and now thinking back upon it, there were countless different powers that dragged him along at that time. When the Black Smoke Pot’s surge of power broke through everything, it decided upon a determined force that instantly brought him to this planet.

When the memory began to really come back to him, the Warlock’s power was not the true catalyst that brought him to the Totem World. They did not drag him here, but among the countless powers that had been pulling him along, he merely pushed one of them gently, picking the direction that was best suited to himself.

"At that time, what would happen if I had picked a different direction to fly in?" Garen could not help but consider this thought, and even though this thought flashed through his mind quickly, it was still deeply embedded in his head.

Chapter 517: War 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After chatting with Kid on the balcony for awhile, Garen received an invitation from Tasura Academy’s Old Man, before he quickly returned to the hall on the second floor. Some of the old elders had taken the opportunity to use their titles to bring their successors in front of Garen, to ensure that he would be familiar with them.

Garen dealt with them while remembering the strange incidents that happened when he came in contact with the little girl earlier.

Kid had once said that only Listeners could kill other Listeners He used to think that this had a different meaning, but he had never expected to experience it firsthand today.

That little girl had been instantly and continuously destroyed because of the Black Water True Technique’s powers many times, but was not affected by it fully and was able to heal completely, Even Garen could feel that he was unable to truly touch his opponent’s body, giving him a sense of curiosity towards the characteristics of Listeners.

However, he was merely curious, as he knew that although Listeners were strange and knew many hidden secrets, it was obvious that they would not be able to affect the existence of someone of his level In the end, Kid also said that they had no way to increase their powers as all of their strengths were inherent, and would never change. No existing training methods could upgrade them, therefore, if they were undefeatable, they would always be undefeatable. Unless, they managed to swallow other Listeners.

However, they would only receive minor upgrades from this, and even then, Form 4 was their limit; it was impossible for them to be as strong as a Form 5.

After the banquet ended, Garen rode the flying carriage back to the Kingdom’s inner palace. In the duration that followed, among the scholars of the Black Swamp Palace, those who had achieved level two and above of the Black Water True Technique were allowed to train outside, and within the Nine Snakes System, some special, minor danger quests had also started to be releasedThese quests were released by people outside the palace with large sums of money, and although the prices were slightly lower than those of the Luminarist Guild, there were still good opportunities for the scholars that were hard pressed for funds to earn some money.

The disciples who had achieved level two of the Black Water True Technique and above already possessed a certain amount of strength and speed, and although they lacked an activated Totem Power, their extremely powerful anti-toxin abilities and their sensitivity towards liquid and water sources allowed them to quickly uncover various methods of using them.

For instance, these included detecting various valuable Aberrated Creatures with sufficient water content, memorizing special moisture smells and collecting specific valuable plants, locating precious underground water sources, and even predicting the weather in advance. Plus, they could also explore the terrain in areas that were filled with poisonous mist, among other things.

The Black Water True Technique’s strong anti-toxin abilities gave the scholars immunity when they encountered low level poison. They also possessed strong resistance towards middle level poison as well, and a lot of outsiders and even hunting groups hired Black Swamp Palace disciples to use them as air breathability testers and water source detectors, and the results were extremely positive.

Through the ten percent commission that they received from the quests, after more than a month of operations, the Black Swamp Palace’s Nine Snakes System finally received its first income from the quests of its scholars.

Within this month, Garen stayed inside the palace daily, only coming out occasionally to guide his three core disciples. The White Knights that he saved had gradually integrated into the environment of the inner palace, while the crybaby, the little princess from the White Wind Tribe had also systematically joined the Black Swamp Palace as well. After undergoing the tests and participating in the prodigy training camps, although her Appraisal was good, her resolve and other factors still needed to be considered.

Most of the White Knights had also passed the tests to join the groups of scholars inside the palace, and since they were already elites with excellent talent, after they participate in the Black Swamp Palace’s training camps and teamed up with one another, their progress improved quickly, especially their battle training, which soon exceeded most of the normal scholars.

Time continued to pass day by day, and the operations of the entire Black Swamp Palace had also started to become more organized.

***********************

Amidst the continuous rolling red mountains, a tower-like stone building pierced through the clouds, bright white light beams shots out of the top into infinity,, straight into the sky, releasing soft humming noises.

The light beam resembled white cylinders that pierced through the layers of clouds, extending into faraway, unknown places.

The afternoon sky was a light red, and gold-red rays of sunlight lingered on the horizon while a flock of white feathered birds, with lumps of flesh on their foreheads sailed past, sharp ear-piercing cries echoed from afar.

At the entrance at the bottom of the tower-shaped building, a narrow stream of people could vaguely be seen entering and leaving continuously, and all of these people seemed to be dressed in long black robes and tights. Most of them wore black veils on their faces, regardless if they were men or women.

The minaret was situated on a disc-shaped mountaintop. Other than the tower-shaped building on top of the mountain, there were also houses of various sizes that were scattered around. During the evening, the insides of the houses were lit up with dots of orange-red colored light.

Throughout the surroundings of the red mountains were long stretches of red plains, and currently on the far end of the plains, near the horizon, large, light green waves had vaguely appeared.

These waves were silent, and from afar, they resembled real flowing water that flowed slowly, but surely, towards the direction of the minaret. The entire wave was apparently made up of countless Green Armored Knights.

These knights were all clad in green vine armor from head to toe and rode on giant green snails, while the position of the rider was fitted nicely in the empty space between the snail’s head and its shell.

These snails were more than five meters tall each, with fearsome faces and humanlike bodies that included two arms that held a gigantic steel pitchfork. They were also silent when they crawled, their bodies were shrouded in light green air currents, resembling continuously flowing wind.

Other than these snail riders, there were also many Red Flame Snail People who stood upright within the wave, each of them was more than ten meters tall, stood out of the crowd and had smaller red shells on their backs, extremely muscular bodies, and used their evolved legs to walk. They held gigantic bloodied axes in their hands, while their two large nostrils occasionally breathed out fiery sulfur fumes. They glanced from left to right occasionally, and their gaze was extremely fearsome, as if they were constantly looking for a fight with their opponents.

Countless snail knights charged towards the minaret slowly and silently, and even though there were bloody-eyed, surveillance birds flying around the minaret in the sky, they did not see the army below them, and continued drawing lines to mark the safe zones as usual.

Slowly, as the wave came nearer, the faint smell of sulfur filled the air, and the people inside the minaret finally realized that something was not right.

At this moment, the wave finally tore open their camouflage and began their charge towards the minaret on the mountain frantically.

Roar!! The loud roars of the Snail People echoed throughout the ground.

The Green Armored Knights roared loudly and charged forward as well, while the green snail riders leapt into the sky , flying in large herds towards the minaret with much haste.From afar, they resembled flying green meteors, forming large clouds of meteor rain.

"Obscuro!! Obscuro!! Obscuro!!!"

Angry, low sounding roars could be heard from the minaret. Both sides of the minaret were filled with tall red mountains and incomparably huge stalagmites, forming a forest of spikes shielding the assassins that were now moving out slowly.

On top of the sharp stalagmite filled mountain peak, many ten meters tall Stone Giants walked out suddenly, coming out of their rock and soil camouflage, leaving large human-shaped pits on the surface of the mountain peak.

On top of two of the tallest mountain peaks, a loud crashing noise could be heard. Four limbs grew out with a tearing noise, while the hundred meter tall mountain peaks quickly transformed into two incomparably large Stone Giants.

Their entire bodies were blood-red, and they guarded both sides of the minaret, They roared silently in the direction of the green meteor army.

"Hellgate! I’m going to break your limbs today!! Hahaha…" Maniacal, loud laughter echoed down from the faraway sky, and each noise resembled endless dull crashes of thunder.

"Phiroth’s lap dog!" At the entrance of the minaret, a large group of black robed Totem Users flew upwards, following the Stone Giants while they charged at the falling green meteor army. A figure that was completely shrouded in black mist was ambushed by more than ten black robes, before they raised their hands and looked at the red clouds rolling across the sky.

The black misty figure raised a single hand, releasing shrouds of black mist, forming a pitch-black mist whirlpool in front of himself.

Suddenly, a loud cry that sounded like an elephant’s trumpet echoed out of the middle of the whirlpool.A black Strange Bird the colour of ink flew out of the whirlpool instantly. With a gentle beat of its two pairs of wings, , it charged towards the sky like a rocket.

Quickly, more Strange Birds flew out of the black whirlpool endlessly.After ten seconds, more than a hundred black Strange Birds had flown out of the whirlpool.

"Black Sky’s empowered Four Winged Birds? I’ll experience them for myself today!" The thunderous noise echoed throughout the sky.

The black misty figure sneered before leaping upwards, and turning into a shroud of black mist that flew towards the sky.

On top of the mountain peak, a round transparent shield had vaguely formed around the surroundings of the minaret, and when the green meteors fell on top, they formed transparent circular ripples, before sliding downwards.

On the ground, countless Green Armored Knights surrounded and slaughtered the Stone Giants.The violent Snail People charged towards the incomparably large mountain Giants, but the hundred meter tall Giants merely stomped on them before they heavily injured and even killed many of the violent snails, sending a frenzy of severed limbs resembling an odd, blended tomato juice everywhere, However, every time a violent snail was stomped to death, they would burst open, forming more pits of various sizes that were each ten meters deep beside both of the mountain Giants.

The green waves and meteors surrounded the minaret closely for a seemingly endless amount of time.

A crash could be heard throughout the sky, sending green ripples spreading out in a flash,, dispersing all of the red clouds and pushing them away, exposing the clear red sky..

A long, white, snake-like beast struggled and turned in the sky, and on its head, a smaller-sized green spider monster was biting its face furiously while countless layers of spider webs were entangled around the long white snake.

The two monsters possessed terrifying body sizes of over a hundred meters, and looked abnormally scary. Once the long white snake could not persevere anymore, it struggled for a moment, before finally falling from the sky.

"The President will avenge me!!"

A sharp, maniacal voice echoed from the snake’s body.

"Too weak! Too weak! Black Sky, is this your colossal Secret Technique? I’m disappointed!" The spider released the white snake and turned around, before floating in the sky, exposing a muscular, green haired man in its abdomen. The man’s body had fused with the spider, and the vital parts of his body were covered with white bone armor. Both of his eyes were filled with green hellfire, making him look unusually strange.

Boom!

The large white snake fell on top of the minaret violently, smashing into and toppling it.

The white light beam flashed for a few moments, before finally breaking off completely and extinguishing.

******************

Kovitan, Ultimate Protection

The evening sky had faintly turned blue-black. White clouds drifted past slowly while rays of golden evening sunlight cascaded downwards, making it somewhat warm.

At the back of the right side of the palace area, on a square shaped plaza.

The surroundings of the plaza were connected by brown-yellow colored Palace buildings, while a square shaped pond in the middle clearly reflected the clouds that were drifting past in the sky. The remaining ground was covered in light green grass that had been trimmed neatly.

Between the pond and the buildings was a light yellow lane that twisted and turned. It had black street lights throughout the road, faintly illuminating it with light yellow light.

A few little children chased each other around the pond noisily, holding wooden toy swords in their hands, playing a game that involved beautiful girls saving princes.

Beside the road, clusters of people engaged in their after-dinner leisure strolls. .

Garen sat on the bench beside the pond with his arms outstretched against the back of the seat, clad in a well-fitted, pitch-black outfit that showed off his well-built physique.

The button on the tight-fitted black shirt that he wore was open, exposing his muscular, pale chest, and the exquisite red crystal necklace that he wore on his neck.. His golden, shoulder-length hair had now been cut short, and his dark red eyes were now drooping lazily, as if he were watching the little children play on the side while resting sleepily.

"You ran all the way here again," said a clear, cold male voice, echoing behind Garen.

Garen tilted his head upwards, looking behind himself.

"Ivy? What’s wrong?"

Chapter 518: War 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The approaching man wore a plain white suit with a torn open collar and a white rose stuck in front of his chest, while the faint scent of alcohol lingered on his body.

"When you returned, you brought a female Demon Phoenix with you, what level is she?"

"You didn’t try her?" Garen smiled.

"She gave me a really weird feeling," said Ivy while he furrowed his eyebrows. He stood behind the bench, while standing up steadily with both of his hands on the back of the seats.

"I wouldn’t be able to explain it clearly even in an hour and a half, so you’ll just have to touch it slowly to find out." Garen was uninterested in saying too much; this would involve a lot of trouble, and it was also difficult to explain. Plus, while having slightly hidden strengths could also be used as another trump card to stay alive.

"It’s fine if you don’t want to talk about it, but the latest news that traveled from Daniela is that the war between Daniela and Obscuro Society started today, and this afternoon, one of Obscuro Society’s valuable Black Sky bases were completely destroyed. Black Sky is nowhere to be found, while the information and research results that Obscuro Society accumulated over the course of many years was wiped out by Phiroth," explained Ivycius , furrowing his eyebrows. "What are your plans?"

"They’ve finally started the war, huh?" Garen did not seem surprised. "They’ll fight their own war, and it’s unlikely that the winners and losers will be decided within an hour and a half. No need to rush. That’s right, how are the operations inside the palace?"

"Shouldn’t you be asking Lala that?" Despite saying that, Ivy reported the latest changes anyway. "The operations are fine. After the outside training was completed, although some of the scholars died from their injuries, they were others who took the opportunity to break through to level four, two of them actually, while three others broke through level three. Skyharp is already working on the preparations to activate the observation programs. Also, I’m marrying Skyharp in a month, interested in coming?"

"Wedding?" Garen was slightly taken aback, as he never expected Skyharp to take measures into her own hands so quickly, tying Ivy down in a such a short while.

"Yes," Ivy’s expression remained flat, without any signs of compulsion. "After so many years, it would have been difficult for her alone…"

Garen’s expression was strange. He was at a loss for words, as this woman Skyharp apparently had such an image in Ivycius’s heart. He related it to the chat that he once had with Skyharp.

Apparently… A cultured female hoodlum would not be as frightening anymore.

"Speaking of which, what about you and your fiance? You’re not young anymore, do you still plan on dragging it further?" Ivy changed the subject to Garen.

"There’s no rush, I still have some unfinished business…" Garen exhaled. The things he pursued, his goals, should not leave deep marks in this world as these were not Hathaway’s responsibilities. However, as he said, there were some things, that needed to be done regardless.

Continuing the Trejons bloodline was still a responsibility that his current body would not be able to reject, and perhaps once everything was done, assuming that he was still alive, he would go and marry Hathaway then.

"During this period of time, I’m planning to leave for a trip. If anything happens and you can’t handle it, just go look for Demon Phoenix."

"Understood," nodded Ivycius. When he returned this time around, he could no longer see through Garen, and vaguely guessed that the other man had broken through already. But if he had broken through, it was strange how Garen’s aura had become weaker, and more hidden. Ivycius himself had not broken through completely, and even if he had broken through, he was unclear regarding the great difference between regular Form 5 and peak Form 5.

He relied on normal Form 5 auras to judge and measure, but judgments like these were ultimately meaningless.

Both of them began shooting the breeze, and after understanding the main situation, they resumed their conversation by talking about the problems of Secret Technique practices. While Ivy asked most of the questions, Garen would answer, and as one of Garen’s Dragon Demons, Ivycius could share a part of Garen’s Swallowed Lives and recovery abilities. His powers were slightly stronger than before, and since he was also progressing to fuse, the questions that he asked were much clearer and were all related to the key aspects of breaking through to Form 5.

This also allowed Garen to understand his rate of progress, and it was certain that Ivy would break through soon, within the next few days.

The sky became darker, and the glow of the streetlights gradually replaced the remaining evening light.

Garen and Ivy were discussing a key problem of Form 5 fusion, suddenly, a dull crashing noise echoed from the further end of the palace. The Nine Snakes Defense inside the palace had been disturbed while it was showering.

Red light flashed from the red crystal necklace in front of Garen’s chest, shooting out a round, translucent, dim red screen, projecting it in front of Garen.

The scene of three Three Snake scholars surrounding one Four Snake scholar floated up on the round screen. Having three snakes meant that their Black Water True Technique was at least level three, as the number of these snake heads represented the level of their Secret Technique.

Three level threes ambushed a single level four. Since they were low level Secret Technique practitioners, although the difference between levels was not huge, level four was the limit of activated Totem Powers. The conclusion was obvious.

As expected, the three Three Snake scholars were knocked down on the ground, while the single Four Snake scholar was an indifferent young girl with short hair, blue eyes, white skin, and an average face, resembling a regular girl without any special traits. However, her attack move that knocked down three others made Garen’s face light up faintly.

That was not a battle skill of the Black Water True Technique, but an attack move of a completely different style.

As if she were a psychic, the girl knew the attacks of the three others like the back of her hand, allowing her to evade them calmly, and regardless of the complexity of the attacks. She dodged all of them easily, before retaliating instantly with her own attack when they missed.

"This is the girl who got rid of the top prodigy, Ansapello, and the second person who entered into level four," explained Ivycius on the sidelines. "She’s called Pefalia, has no surname, and was born to common people. She initially only fluctuated between level two, but after going out for training once, she broke through to level four a short while after returning, activating her Totem Power."

"Not bad, not bad, she seems to be around fifteen years old, right? Very good potential," Garen smiled.

"She returned with a brand new battle skill tactic, saying she found it from a relic that others had already flipped through, and after it went through the Nine Snakes System’s assessment, it was evaluated to be of Five Snakes-level."

The rankings of battle skill tactics, treasures, messages, and other things were based on the degree of their values, from one to nine, separating them into nine different levels. The higher the level, the more valuable its rank. Complete legacy types like the Black Water True Technique could sometimes achieve rankings as high as Form 5 Secret Techniques, which were equivalent to the highest Nine Snakes level.

Meanwhile, Ivycius’s legacy could achieve the highest ranking of peak Form 4, which was evaluated as Eight Snakes. By this understanding, the maximum legacy for middle level Form 4 was Seven Snakes.

The Five Snakes level was already an extremely high assessment level, and since it was an incomplete legacy, it was placed outside, and its value was equivalent to peak Form 3 Totem nurturing legacies. Those with less than ten thousand gold rumbs could not even dream of buying them.

"Besides that, when the scholars returned from their training outside, they brought back different Totem nurturing methods and battle skill attack moves, and two more even confirmed the intelligence information regarding suitable locations to practice the Black Water True Technique." As Garen’s Dragon Demon, it was natural for Ivycius to help him attend to these important matters.

"

Sending them out was truly a wise decision. What about Ansapello? Where is that guy now?" Garen suddenly thought of the arrogant guy who was brimming with talent.

"Hasn’t returned yet, after he broke through, he joined a hunting group and went out."

"What Totem did he choose?"

"Should be a Silver Crown Tiger, his talents are still unknown, that guy hides them very well," Ivycius shook his head. He admired this talented disciple highly, as he had great and wild ambitions, and a power that could still be strengthened. Although he was arrogant towards his teachers, he still possessed a required amount of respect.

For Garen and the others, the establishment of the Black Swamp Palace and the appearance of stronger prodigy disciples meant even better things for them. Regardless of which aspect was being looked at, from the outsider’s perspective, the more talented Ansapello became and the stronger he grew, he would always be a part of the Black Swamp Palace, and by extension, a part of the Black Swamp Palace’s strength as well.

As for his judgements, Garen could not think of a more suitable place to practice the Black Water True Technique than here. Leaving the Black Swamp Palace would make it harder for the disciples to progress even if they were prodigies, and from the moment he started practicing the Black Water True Technique, this path had already been decided.

"Observe him slowly," Garen instructed softly. "Besides that, list the Snowy Mountain in the Northern Region as one of the training ranges, you can discuss this with Blizzard and the others, there should be no problems."

"Alright."

Garen had already rearranged the Black Water True Technique again earlier, separating it into levels according to the Totem levels, meaning that level four would officially become equivalent to the Form 1 Totem level, level five would become Form 2, level six would become Form 3, level seven would become Form 4, level eight would become Form 5, and level nine would become peak Form 5.

The minor levels that were constantly forming because of the fusions would all be placed in level seven.

All seven levels of the Black Water True Technique were placed into the Nine Snakes System, but the Secret Techniques remained as Secret Techniques, and although the stronger Secret Techniques were only placed slightly higher, how many people could truly achieve all of them?

Countless people practiced Secret Techniques in the Secret Technique World, and there were many first rate exercises, but those who could truly become the King of the Century were limited to only two people; Cayduran, and Garen himself.

Even after placing the Black Water True Technique into the system as an achievement-based exchange item, in this manner, how many people would be able to enter Form 5?

Not even Form 5, but Form 4, how many of them were there? According to Garen’s estimates, even if he managed to get one out of a hundred of these disciple scholars, that would be considerably good.

As for Form 5, no one understood it fully. Even for the most prodigious disciples with great potential, how long would it take for them to truly become strong? Changes in their state of mind, the course of nurturing Totems, and the countless risks and dangers that they would encounter, were all unknown.

Garen’s plan for his household, and himself, was to leave a sort of foundation. Perhaps he would leave one day, but if he returned, all of the Totem Users that practiced the Black Water True Technique would become his greatest support. Not because of others, but because of the Black Water True Technique’s natural characteristics; the higher level Secret Technique Users would be able to suppress the lower level Secret Technique Users easily.

At the same time, using liquid type battle Secret Techniques like the Black Water True Technique at high levels would allow one to suppress the lower levels completely, blocking them from using even half of their powers.

Moreover, the most important point was that even if other people managed to practice it to the peak of level nine and broke through to Form 5, the Black Water True Technique was based on the Nine-Headed Hydra’s blood flow. The only person that possessed the Nine-Headed Hydra

Totem, which was Garen, would be able to suppress the peak Secret Technique Users regardless of the fact that they had broken through Form 5.

This was the only advantage, and it was the final advantage of the evolved Salamander that he had strengthened through his talents and abilities, and since there would neither be a second person with his attribute points and talents, nor a second person who would be able to fuse a dragon’s heart, or activate the will of the Nine-Headed Hydra’s bloodline, no one would ever be able to surpass him.

These were the conclusions that Garen had come up with over the past few days, and other than himself, the remaining practitioners of the Black Water True Technique were all modeled on the flow Nine-Headed Hydra’s bloodline, while he was the only person to truly possess this bloodline. Those who possessed this bloodline, were realistically able to greatly suppress the existence of the Black Water True Technique Secret Users that belonged to a level higher than themselves, stripping their opponent of the source of their power.

Chapter 519: World 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

During the time period after that, Garen recouped his strength in the Kingdom for three whole months. During this time, while Cthulhu King left and went outside, Daniela that was currently wielded by Phiroth took the opportunity to quickly mobilize their large-scale forces to massacre Obscuro Society.

Phiroth sent out two semi-detached clone-like subordinates to defeat a few of Obscuro Society’s main bases. Then, war broke out.

Meanwhile, the Secret Technique stone slabs that Cthulhu King agreed to send had all arrived as well, and five Cthulhus had escorted and sent them personally. Garen received them himself as well, and after he had memorized all of them, he sealed them inside the Black Swamp Palace’s secret book cellar.

Seated inside the palace study, Garen looked at the faint, constantly changing dark light screen in front of him. While screens with information from faraway lands were displayed, some of the screens that showed scenes of war, making him Garen furrow his eyebrows slightly.

His fingers tapped against the armrest of his seat gently and rhythmically.

Inside the study, other than himself, Lala and Demon Phoenix were also present.

"Therefore, Phiroth plans to focus on the frontlines in a decisive battle with Obscuro Society?" Garen had thought of the possibility that it would quickly develop to this stage, but he never expected it to happen so soon. Clearly, both Phiroth and Obscuro Society were trying to speed up the war.

Perhaps everyone still thought that Obscuro Society’s Hellgate was still the same peak Form 5 from before, and although the Terraflor Society couple had died in battle, their powers were still mysterious, and unknown to many people. Therefore, it was difficult for outsiders to know the true extent of Hellgate’s powers.

Only Garen knew that Hellgate had now definitely surpassed his limits, achieving unprecedented heights.

That was the peak that no one else had ever achieved before.

He rubbed his temples, the thoughts in his head were still somewhat complicated.

"According to the analysis of the current information, both parties are proceeding with final battle preparations.Nothing is out of the ordinary, and within three days, it will erupt," Lala reported the situation calmly, and no emotional distress could be heard in her voice. Understandably, with the presence of the Ultimate Protection, perhaps all of the inhabitants of the Kovitan protected area possessed the same unfazed attitude.

Garen glanced at her, but did not say anything.

"Then, your subordinate will take her leave." When Lala saw that Garen had not opened his mouth anymore, she bowed and withdrew herself. She had been coming over to report on the situation of the war every day during these past few days.

"Get ready, I’m going to go out for a trip soon," Garen’s voice echoed behind her.

"Yes," replied Lala quickly.

After the room door was closed gently, the study returned to its serene state again.

Seated on the side, Demon Phoenix yawned lazily, and since that person had been sealed for more than a thousand years, she had acquired the habit of sleeping as a method to pass time. Garen guessed that it was the primary reason why her intelligence had not developed all this while.

"Follow me out on my trip. For a few days," said Garen.

"No problem!" quickly answered the Demon Phoenix spiritedly. "Spending the whole day here is really getting boring, no tributes, no sacrifices, nothing at all…" After seeing that Garen’s expression had darkened slightly, she decided not to continue.

This person’s temper had been completely suppressed by Garen, and after a short period of time, she was already mentally used to listening to Garen’s will. From a certain perspective, she was a useful pet and battle power.

****************

Sniff… Hoo…

Sniff… Hoo…

Within the flying carriage in the sky, noises that sounded like the breathing of a terrifying large beast echoed throughout the sky endlessly.

Black mist and waves constantly rippled near the black carriage like living creatures, that surrounding the carriage, and dancing around it.

Within the blue sky, with the carriage as the center, a large black shadow drifted in the surrounding area, like a drop of ink that had spilled into a blue lake, drawing a thick line in the sky.

Inside the carriage, Garen sat in the center, while Demon Phoenix and Phantom guarded the sides, holding water bottle-like narrow-neck bottles in their hands, tipping them sideways occasionally, pouring out a clear sticky liquid.

This liquid dripped on the floor of the carriage, and quickly flowed towards Garen who sat in the center, gathering there.

Garen inhaled large gusts of air into his nostrils constantly, before exhaling again, forming air cyclones of different sizes, while his loud breathing noises drifted out of the carriage.

Within a radius of more than ten kilometers in the sky, all of the creatures were scared off by the terrifying breathing noises, making them too afraid to stop within that space.

On the ground below the path of the carriage, within the thick forest, many dark green Giant Lizards crouched down on the ground slowly, releasing frightened humming noises. The Aberrated Giant Hawk and Giant Python that were hunting left at the same time as well, as if they were scared rabbits that were escaping far away.

A few green-skinned humanoid monsters with large protruding bellies raised their heads towards the sky, howling in awe.

After an unknown period of time passed, the sky darkened gradually.

Demon Phoenix and Phantom poured the last drop of liquid out of their bottles, before taking a few steps back, quietly waiting for Garen to receive his power.

The loud breathing noises slowly became quieter, and softer, before disappearing completely.

Garen’s eyes burst open suddenly, and his eyes were like black holes that were pure darkness.

But soon, the darkness disappeared quickly, before his pupils returned to their original light red state.

"I never thought that Skyharp would be able to mix such an effective poisonous solution. It’s really quite amazing…" Garen felt a new poisonous layer forming on his body, while a faint look of satisfaction appeared on his face.

"These two bottles of Colourless Water were made by Big Sister Skyharp with the Three Colored Leaf as its core, and were mixed with nineteen different types of first-rate poisons. Twelve of those poisons came from Snowy Mountain, and the core Three Colored Leaf was a poisonous drug that one of the scholars obtained from the relics. It received a Seven Snake assessment from the system. Truly amazing."

Phantom explained softly.

Demon Phoenix and the others had adapted to the environment of the Black Swamp Palace quickly. After being sealed inside a small corner with no way to get out for more than a thousand years consecutively, they had no way of finding other fellows of the same level to have exchanges with, but now, the moment they encountered a fellow professional of the same level to converse with, their new lives were suddenly like heaven in comparison to their past.

Neither did they have to calculate risks here, nor did they have to worry about being sealed, and anything they wanted would be sent over immediately. Most importantly, once they were aware of the existence of everything else that was stronger than themselves in this world, the mentalities of Demon Phoenix and the others were gradually corrected.

"It’s true that the effect is satisfactory, and it will also benefit our Black Water True Technique practitioners greatly," Garen nodded. "The Colourless Water’s poison had completely fused into the effect of my previous poison, so the Black Water True Technique practitioners, from lower to higher levels, will be able to slowly use the Colourless Waters of different dilutions to train and cleanse themselves. They can use these poisons for their own benefit."

Poisons were another one of the Black Water True Technique’s special killing methods, and would be able to get rid of one’s enemies silently when mixed with activated poison mist, without having to worry about large-scale enemy attacks. Garen could foresee, perhaps in the near future, that these specialized poisons would become the strongest symbols Black Swamp Palace’s strength.

"These poisons could trick the Totem Light’s defense systems as they were originally harmless towards living creatures, but once it integrated with certain substances that grew inside the creature’s body, it would form the most life-threatening and terrifying poison. This was a poison that grew inside living beings, and had no effect on inanimate objects," Phantom explained.

"Living creature poisons?" Garen nodded. "Since it’s like this, my simple poisonous effects will be able to reach new heights." Originally, poisonous corrosion was only effective towards Spiritualized levels and below, but with this current poisonous mix, even Form 4’s would fall victim to this if they were not on guard. Poisonous Spirit Light diffusions were no longer mere decorations.

"Demon Phoenix." Garen remembered something suddenly, and looked towards Demon Phoenix who was daydreaming.

"What?" This person came to her senses quickly.

"You can start preparing your Spirit Light. I’m thinking I'll need it in a short while." Garen instructed.

All existence that had undergone Spiritualization possessed their own special Spirit Light abilities, and Demon Phoenix’s ability was demonizing puppets. Any creature that died within the range of her Spirit Light would stand up again, and after being corroded by her Demon Cloud, would become Demon Phoenix’s puppet subordinates.

Unlike Garen’s simple poison and corrosive Spirit Light, this Spirit Light possessed a terrifying effect that would become stronger as it was used, and this was especially apparent after the Demon Cloud Puppets were corroded, as their powers would be slightly stronger than before, therefore, although it could only corrode creatures that were Form 4 and below, it was still a frightening ability. This battle method seemed truly evil, and perhaps this was why no one knew the true reason the Great Sage sealed Demon Phoenix in the past.

"How long do you want the Spirit Light to be on standby?"

"Just keep it ready for now, since your Demon Cloud Spirit Light can be charged, wait until we reach our destination and look at the situation before making any moves. What is its longest continuous duration?" Garen asked carefully.

"It depends on the degree of its strength, if the puppets only need to return to their normal level before they died, it can be sustained for a week or so. If you want to strengthen them by fifty percent, they can only last for two consecutive days," answered Demon Phoenix honestly.

"Two days, then." After he spoke, Garen closed his eyes again.

***********

Outside the borders between Daniela and Ender, inside a vast, primitive forest.

Large twisted trees formed long stretches of shade. Within the forest were many tall moss-covered boulders, stacked up against each other and of various sizes, tangled with the roots of the large trees.

Somewhere inside the forest, large greenish boulders and large thick tree roots intertwined with one another, forming a large, round arch, and within the shadows of the arch was a square stone door that was filled with rough old patterns.

A slender figure dressed in a dark green cloak stood beside the stone door with both of his arms wrapped around his chest, while the corner of a dark green longbow was exposed behind his back. His entire face was covered by a green hood, and the top half of his body was hidden within the shadows of the arch, making it difficult to see his face clearly. Only the dark green veil that he wore on his face could be seen, barely exposing two falcon-like green eyes.

The figure leaned against the left side of the stone door, waiting for something.

The noontime sun shone down from the sky, shining through the leaves and falling onto the floor of the forest, occasionally moving slowly while the faint winds blew.

On both sides outside the stone door, were two ashen toad creature stone carvings, both of which had large opened mouths and bulging eyes, as if they were about to spit something out in front of them. A spot of golden light fell on top of the left toad’s head coincidentally.

As time passed, this spot of light moved slowly as well.

The dark green figure’s eyes glared at the spot, as if he were judging the passing of time itself.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, the part of the forest near the front of the stone door was whooshed open by the wind.

At once, the light spot on the forest floor moved continuously, in a slightly chaotic manner. It resembled a sea of golden light spots that were moving.

Soon, the wind noises stopped, and another figure appeared in the forest suddenly. This figure was instead clad in a long red robe and wore a silver mask. Both his sleeves and the hem of his robe made it impossible to see his hands or feet, and his entire body seemed to be moving in the wind. As he floated towards the stone door slowly, only the constant crunching noise of the leaves under his feet confirmed that he was, indeed, walking with his feet.

"You've arrived this early?" The red robed man looked towards the green figure beside the stone door suspiciously, his low raspy voice spoke in perfect Daniela language.

"Just slightly earlier than you," answered the green figure faintly in a low, but clear and bright male voice with tones of coldness. "There’s one more left."

"He should be on the way." The red robed man walked towards the toad stone sculpture beside the stone door, unable to stand still.

Both of them stopped speaking for awhile as the sky became lighter and the forest warmed up. A few tiny flying insects constantly flew in between both of them, trying to find some skin that they could suck blood from, but every time they crawled on their bodies, they would instantly be killed by an invisible force, causing them to fall off at once. Soon, there was a small round pile of dead flying insect bodies below their feet.

Suddenly, the male green figure turned his head slowly, looking in the direction of the right side of the forest. On the empty land there, faint black mist had formed abruptly.

The black mist became thicker and thicker, and turned darker, before the entire forest became blurry.

Within the low visibility, a figure in black clothes walked out behind a tree trunk, taking large strides towards the two people outside the stone door.

"Looks like I’m slightly late, Cthulhu King." The black-clothed figure walked out of the black mist, with a similar black mask on his face, clad in a black shirt and long pants that clearly showed his muscular and well-built body, while a round silver buckle was used to fasten his black silk cloak, concealing every trace of his breath.

Chapter 520: World 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Nine-headed Snake?" The green figure that was leaning against the wall this whole time was now slightly surprised.

"This is our first time meeting each other, right? Divine God Palace Master." Garen’s bright gold hair reflected blinding golden light under the sun, and his vision was focused accurately on the position of the green male figure.

His opponent looked agile and tranquil, as if he had become one with the forest. At first glance he resembled a regular forest ranger, and did not fit the title of Divine God Palace Master. He was once assumed to be an impressive force, an incomparably terrifying dictator-like character, but now, there was actually a huge difference between his true image and the one that had been visualized.

"Wasn’t the original plan to get Phiroth?" Divine God Palace Master raised his eyebrows slightly while looking at Cthulhu King.

"Are you saying I’m not qualified?" A cold smile appeared on Garen’s face behind his mask. Suddenly, both of his eyes seemed as if they had been dyed black by ink, completely turning into two pitch-black demon’s eyes. Dark red mist drifted out from his body silently.

He took long strides and walked towards Divine God Palace Master, and every time he raised his feet, fragrant black smoke wafted out of the footprints that he left behind. The stones and tree branches on his footprints would melt into sticky black liquid in less than a second.

Every step he took would leave a black smoke footprint on the ground, and poisonous fumes would waft out of it slowly, like burning smoke.

"Enough." Divine God Palace Master narrowed his eyes and waved his right hand gently, before a green seed shot out, landing beside Garen’s feet accurately. The seed seemed as if it had fallen into water, as it formed green ripples on the floor where it landed, before disappearing completely.

Garen was slightly shocked and turned his head, before noticing that his own poisonous footprints had suddenly disappeared completely, while the tree branches and stones that melted earlier had returned to their original states as well.

He narrowed his eyes slightly, as his mind had started to gain more knowledge about Divine God Palace Master’s power. When he voluntarily released his poisons earlier, he was merely testing the waters, and did not expect that his opponent’s previously unconcerned reaction would lead to him displaying a part of his powers.

Garen glanced at Cthulhu King who stood beside the stone carvings, before both of them exchanged glances quickly.

Cthulhu King was unable to defeat Divine God Palace Master, and thus he wanted him to form an alliance with him. He even let go of his grudge against Garen that spanned over ten thousand kilometers because of this. It was clear that Divine God Palace Master had left a deep impression on him.

"Alright, prepare to enter." Divine God Palace Master stood up immediately, and turned to walk towards the front of the stone door.

He stretched his hand out and pushed gently.

Ka-ka…

The stone door was pushed inwards easily, exposing a dark passage inside, while dust and a strong moldy smell wafted out.

Divine God Palace Master walked in without any hesitation, before his figure disappeared quickly.

Cthulhu King followed behind quickly, while Garen turned his head and scanned his surroundings, as the last person to walk into the stone door.

Behind the door was a dark, black hall. It was square, and there was a deep square pit in the middle of it, with by a seven-or-eight meter tall ashen stone sculpture inside.

The stone sculpture depicted a beautiful girl in chiffon garments, with loose long hair, posing with both her hands carrying something, but the strangest part, was that an extra eye had been carved on her forehead.

White mist wafted inside the hall, mixing with the dust, and making everything blurry.

The three people entered the ruins together, before the stone door closed itself behind them slowly.

Standing in front of the large stone sculpture, Divine God Palace Master turned around to face both of the others.

"According to the previous exploration, the Living Secret Technique should be located at the bottom of the third level of the ruins. However, we weren’t able to find the right method to enter the second level last time."

"Why can’t we just use force to break through and enter the ruins?" Garen interrupted and asked.

"This place imprisons all forms of extraordinary force. But you can try," replied Cthulhu King simply.

Garen’s expression darkened slightly, as he reached his hand out, laid his palm flat, before the Black Water True Technique’s water vapor mobilization ability started flowing suddenly.

But his palm did not move at all.

"No wonder this place was well preserved…" He could not help but laugh softly, and did not question any further.

Divine God Palace Master remained indifferent, and continued speaking. "The way to enter the second level is to secure all three stone switches at the same time, not allowing any of them to close up again. The three of us will concentrate on one switch each, as the switches require sufficient amounts of fused Form 5 powers."

He stopped speaking and looked at Cthulhu King.

The latter nodded, removed a black fibrous paper scroll from his arms, opening it slowly, exposing a pitch-black sheet completely devoid of anything else. But as it was opened, white coordinate dots floated up and slowly appeared on the paper. These coordinates began to move, clearly forming multiple white lines, before a complete map was quickly drawn on the paper.

Cthulhu King waited until the coordinates had almost disappeared once they had finished drawing before passing the map to Garen, while the latter glanced across it carefully, then passing it to Divine God Palace Master.

"The terrain here changes on its own every time, but this map originated from this place, thus it is able to sense the changes and form a corresponding map automatically every time it enters. Therefore, we need to remember the new map everytime we enter," explained Cthulhu King.

"There are three roads, and because the terrain here is extremely vast, according to my estimations, the entire first level of the ruins probably has an area of over ten thousand square kilometers, moreover we can only enter the ruins through the entrance, and if we were to dig underground from the outside, it would be impossible for us to find the existence of the underground palace." Cthulhu King had obviously done a sufficient amount of investigative work. "Therefore each of the three roads will require a certain amount of time, in order to avoid any risks."

He immediately took out three blood red button-like things, each of which had been engraved with maggot-sized red symbols.

He distributed the little things to the other two, giving one to each of them.

"Divine God Palace Master has used this before, so I won’t say too much." He looked at Garen immediately. "This is the only tool that will not be imprisoned that I managed to find after searching for a long time in the outside world. Its functions are very simple, and there’s only one: color changing. Once you’ve reached a switch point, and you’ve opened it, please press this button five times consecutively within two seconds, so that a green road will appear automatically. A green road will also appear from our own buttons as well. Similarly, once our switches have been activated, just like before, you will be able to see our progress through this thing."

"Within ten days, if we find the switches successfully, we should be able to enter the second level. The dangers on the first level have been cleared completely, and should not be an obstacle," Divine God Palace Master interrupted and said. "Let’s go."

He was the first one to walk towards the only pitch-black passage in front of the hall.

Garen and Cthulhu King followed behind him closely, and all three of their figures completely disappeared in the darkness.

*********************

Time passed day by day…

Due to Cthulhu King’s absence and the shrinking of the Cthulhuism Society’s forces on all fronts, the conflict between Daniela’s royal family and Obscuro Society grew fiercer. The support of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists became stronger as well.

No one anticipated Obscuro Society’s fearsome tenacity that led to the formation of Totem seas, made up of many Silver Totems constantly battling against Daniela’s armies, killing them.

High level individuals from both sides suffered serious injuries. These were unavoidable casualties of war, and would continue until the war was over.

On the fifth day after Garen entered the ruins.

Obscuro Society’s terrifying powers finally broke out, and Hellgate attacked personally, causing two of Daniela’s largest core armies to collapse immediately, while the allied forces of the three territories slaughtered countless army generals before pressing forward to the Ancestral God Grounds.

All of Daniela’s strength collapsed completely at once.

The War of Destinies has begun.

********************

On top of the tall Ancestral God Tree, Phiroth stood on the largest branch, looking at the black shadow that floated in the sky from afar. That was Hellgate’s Secret Technique illusion. The large, black robed that resembled the God of Death, held a decaying red sickle in its hand that looked as if it would break any moment. It was actually a terrifying weapon of war that had destroyed countless armies, and more than ten thousand allied troops within three days.

Countless transparent bubbles flew around the Ancestral God Tree, but no one was inside anymore.

The battle between the two strongest people from each faction had already eliminated everyone else, leaving only the both of them.

The winner would live, the loser would die.

Nothing more.

The evening sky was dyed red and gold by the sunset. Countless clouds resembled waves that floated their merry way along.

Phiroth looked up at the sky.

"Really, I haven’t seen a sunset like this in so long…" Traces of a smile formed at the corners of his mouth.

"How unfortunate, just give me a little more time…"

Boom!!

The sky darkened immediately, as countless dark clouds gathered over. The sky turned from golden-red to black, almost as black as the dark, nighttime sky.

The countless rolling clouds soon resembled boiling water that bubbled up continuously.

Phiroth straightened his body and waved his right hand in the empty space, before a dark green, three-pronged pitchfork appeared in his hand.

All of the Ancestral God Trees on the Ancestral God Grounds lit up, as if they were stars that were suddenly illuminated.

Boom!

Green light gathered below his feet into a pillar of light that shot upwards, piercing through the sky.

The rays of green light gathered and formed an incomparably large, green human-like figure that also held a three-pronged pitchfork in its hand. Its thousand meters tall body resembled the giants from the ancient legends.

"Only one can be the strongest!"

Phiroth could not help but laugh maniacally, even though fresh blood was constantly gushing out of his eyes, ears, nose, and mouth.

Kachak!!

A lightning bolt flashed past, before the giant human figure raised its three-pronged pitchfork suddenly, piercing it towards the sky.

Kachak!

A crunching noise could be heard, and somewhere in Daniela’s deep underground area, a young man fell on the ground, choking with sobs while looking at the Life Gem that had cracked open in front of him.

Singing noises could be heard floating down from the sky occasionally.

"~~ Faraway dreams, when will you let me awaken. O’ king, forget all your dreams, when will you finally awaken… There was never a time, when the sky looked so pretty. There was never a time, when your eyes looked at me with such happiness…"

Within the ruins.

Garen’s body jolted suddenly. He raised his head, as if he had heard that singing noise. The senses from the Seed of the Ancestral God allowed him to see Daniela’s final scene.

The Ancestral God Grounds turned into a bottomless, pitch-black abyss-like crack.

Daniela’s First Concubine was holding Phiroth’s corpse, her silk garments resembling the wings of a butterfly as she leapt into the abyss.

"Daniela, gone."

Garen closed his eyes.

At the same time, the two other people inside the ruins stopped in their tracks as well. The songs that transcended everything accompanied the collapse of the Ancestral God’s powers, spreading out towards every corner of the entire East Continent.

Following Phiroth’s death in battle, the Ancestral God Grounds’ destruction was complete, and the previous Ancestral Gods ceased to exist along with it. The gloomy shadows that originated from Hellgate hung like dark clouds, covering the skies of the whole world.

Chapter 521: Ancient Ruins Expedition 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen took a deep breath, Phiroth’s death in the fight was beyond his expectations. According to the original timeline, the battle between Hellgate and Phiroth should have lasted a little while longer. He didn’t expect it to end this quick.

Phiroth was a king stronger Cthulhu King, and was a king that was closer to exceeding his limits. One could say that aside from Hellgate, he was the strongest in the world. At least that was what shown in the original timeline.

It’s not that Garen had never thought about working with him, unfortunately, the plan was to be executed after he found the Living Secret Technique, but he didn’t expect Hellgate to push his actions forward by this much.

"Now everything can no longer be referenced off the original timeline, the changes are getting more drastic…" Garen made new estimates in his heart.

Coming back, there was still a dark archaeological site in front of him, after separating with the other two people, he then wandered to his right alone.

There was a faint blue light in the air within the site.

Garen stood in the middle of a narrow, cuboid tunnel. Darkness enveloped him and the front and back of the class; all around him were black walls that had a slightly rough texture.

After touching the wall on his right, an ice cold, coarse sensation travelled from his fingers.

Garen frowned slightly. His faint red iris turned black suddenly, and the fusion power in his body started circulating. He tried to accumulate some water to be spread around for reconnaissance, but once the large fusion power hit the outside word, it immediately dispersed, as though it never happened.

"Indeed, fusion power is limited here. Then, Nine-Headed Hydra ability is obviously suppressed too, not having nine lives is indeed troublesome. What about this?"

He started circulating his vital energy quickly. His skin turned blood red and diminished in an instant.

"My aura is also suppressed, looks like we can only use my normal physical power."

Garen knew his advantages. He had possessed special abilities, and his body had already reached its limits. He is much stronger and quicker than a newly advanced Form 5.

However,, Divine God Palace Master and Cthulhu King have always been slowly strengthening themselves through fusion through the years, they had also have reached their body’s limits. Compared to them, this wasn’t an advantage, but something to level the playing fields.

Whereas Divine God Palace Master, who was not human, would very likely to have even stronger physique. Even though he looked like someone who focused on agility, he needed to remain prepared.

In an instant, Garen had prepared for the subsequent scenarios, and he continued advancing.

He did not intend to mask his footsteps.

His crisp footfalls kept revertabrating throughout the faint blue tunnel, echoing back and forth.

It was just as foggy ahead of him. Garen couldn’t see anything, but he didn’t have the need to. Just by the sound, he could clearly judge the rough topography ahead of him.

As he walked straight ahead, Garen detected the slight downward inclination of the tunnel. As he continued walking down, he would most likely reach underground.

***********

A few days went by.

In the dark corridor, Garen rested by leaning against the wall, a white hand extended beneath the black robe, eating the wheat biscuits with meat bit by bit.

He ate quickly, it only took ten-odd seconds for him to gobble down a palm-sized biscuit. After three of them, Garen took out a black metal bottle, and gulped a large gulp of water, then took out a tissue to clean his mouth and sweep away the crumbs to the ground.

"It’s been eight days…" Garen mumbled, he took out a red button, the dark red on top of it now had green patterns. He then carefully kept it again. He then tidied his garments and then continued walking.

His footsteps continued bouncing off the hallway, and this sound had been his only company for days.

A left cornering appeared in front of him. Garen walked along it, and the path widened after the curve.

An arched round hall appeared before him.

The hall was empty, and the walls on both sides were covered with coarse, blurred paintings. Its contents could not be determined; all that was left was a blueish-black smudge.

Directly opposite the tunnel was a giant black arched wall, on top of it was an image of a man, alongside many crescent moons, surrounded by a blood-colored frame.

The entire hall seemed simple, but Garen’s face showed a hint of relaxation.

"I’m finally here."

He walked into the hall and headed for the wall ahead of him and gently touched it.

Bzzz…..

A strong vibration was transmitted from his hand onto the crescent moon on the wall, Garen’s eyes turned black, and the fusion power of his Form 5 surged into the moon like tidal waves.

Time seemed to pass by slowly. After half an hour, Garen released his hands.

With a crisp tap, a small stone drawer bounced out from beneath the crescent moon, and there was a hexagonal button inside it.

Garen slapped the drawer with force.

Pap!

The drawer went into the wall again.

Garen’s eyes had also quickly returned its original red hue. He took out the button and tapped it a few times, a third green pattern appeared on it.

"Then, I should take the original route." he turned around and began walking as he followed the plan.

Upon leaving the hall and reentering the tunnel, Garen suddenly realized that at the original corner, there appeared an additional junction.

It was originally a cornering, but now it became a T-junction. Leading into the right tunnel was nothing but darkness, not even the faint blue light.

Garen stopped, then walked directly into it.

That tunnel was even flatter, except the environment was much dustier, making it slightly hard to breathe.

Garen touched his way down this tunnel, hence his speed was severely impacted. As he just entered, a strong feeling of purity could be felt in the atmosphere.

This feeling was very odd, it was as though the air he usually breathed in was impeccably polluted.

Comparatively; the air here was much cleaner, even though it was full of dust particles.

After walking in the dark for an unknown amount of time, and even though he couldn’t see anything, the echoes off the wall allowed him to regained some speed.

Pap!

Suddenly, Garen stopped moving.

Roar… Suddenly, a deep roar similar to a canine’s preemptive attack can be heard.

Fuu!

Suddenly, a strong gust was blown.

In the dark, a large shadow pounced towards Garen, this shadow nearly filled the entirety of the tunnel, standing at almost 3 meters tall and about 4 meters wide, and it had a clear roar.

Garen did not move. With his palm flexed into a knife-hand, he met the attack directly. His knife clashed with the shadow violently, and both of them fell back one step.

Bam!

A deep voice reverberated across the tunnel, then came back with an echo.

Garen was shocked and took two steps back, only regaining his balance with his hind leg stepping on a protrusion on the ground.

He looked serious, and were warily sensing the environment around him.

"Such strong force…"

The shadow disappeared, only the echo of the clash remained.

Garen only felt that as he chopped the opponent, it felt like hitting a piece of sturdy wood. It should have injured part of the opponent’s body severely.

He stood in the middle of the tunnel and waited for a while, only relaxing when he felt no movement, and that the opponent seemed to have retreated.

As he squatted to check the floor, there were no signs of the beast at all. The floor still had a thick layer of dust, and it was impossible that any large sized entity had pounced forward.

There were no marks on the floor, nor were there any sigs on the walls surrounding it.

Garen remained unfazed, he stood up and continued walking forward.

He believed that so long as he kept moving, the opponent will surely reappear.

As time passed, he could no longer distinguish the night and day as the tunnel was completely pitch black at all times.

Garen did not light his torch, as this environment did not cause any difficulty to his senses. Instead, the light from the torch would have caused the dark areas to brighten.

Even if the opponent had been living in darkness for an extended period, it is very possible that it’s a special sensing ability, he also didn’t plan to occupy one arm to bear the torch.

As he walked forward step by step, the second layer was different from the first layer, this place was not explored by Cthulhu King and Divine God Palace Master, hence there was a high danger risk.

A place which stored the Living Secret Technique was definitely not easy to explore

As he advanced warily, Garen did not notice two slim black needles ahead of him at all, they were dangling mid-air, aimed straight at his eyes, if he kept moving, they would no doubt pierce his pupils.

The black needles got closer and closer to Garen’s eyes.

Pap!

Garen suddenly stopped moving forward, and remained at his position. The black needles were no more than ten centimeters away from his eyes, but he hadn’t noticed at all, as though he were blind.

Suddenly, a large hand slapped the needles away, and carried a force equivalent from before before it was hammered into Garen’s face.

Bam!

Garen got hammered and hit back several meters. He was knocked onto an angled wall and hugged his head while his right hand firmly grabbed onto the two needles. The tip of the needle was moments away from stabbing him blind.

Roar!

A deafening howl similar to a wolf’s can be heard, a large black silhouette pounced towards Garen once again, this time with a gust even more violent, as though a rolling boulder came crashing towards Garen.

The entire tunnel quaked alongside the howl, the floor rattled lightly, the dust in the tunnel got thicker as well. The dust gathered into a thick dust fog due to the quake.

The giant shadow was extremely agile, just as the sound came to him, it almost got within a half metre from Garen, seemingly able to pounced on Garen instantaneously.

At this time, Garen lifted his right leg and sidestepped, his other leg spun and drew out a curve, and

Accurately sailed towards the top of the shadow.

Both his legs connected.

The entire shadow was clamped by Garen’s legs, and with that Garen pulled them back with force, through his waist, hips, palm, and then his palms, it then hit onto the rock walls on the tunnel.

Bam!

The rock walls then got imprinted with two palms.

Garen used both hands as a leverage, both his legs clamped the shadow that felt like an ice cold wire gauze. He scoffed, and then unleashed his full power, the limit on the body’s power then exploded, and smashed the shadow down violently.

Bam! Bam! Bam Bam!

With four continuous smashing, the shadow let out a painful moan. It then disappeared, turning into a cold breeze of air and dispersed.

Chapter 522: Ancient Ruins Expedition 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After he somersaulted and landed, Garen stood steadily, he then felt like he just came out of a brawl.

"At least 15 points of power, that was terrifying.." he mumbled, the first clash with the shadow was actually a minor scuff, whereas the second time was its full power. Luckily Garen had familiarized himself with Secret Techniques and other martial arts, so that even if he could not use his unique abilities, as a Master-level Secret Technique user comparable to the King of the Century, all the high leveled power leveraging techniques came gushing, and were still similarly strong.

Five times the power for one unit of strength, under the use of strong combat Secret Techniques, it was as though multiplying your own power by five against an opponent which is all brawn. This is the peak efficiency of the King of the Century. Let alone the fact that Garen actually surpassed that realm, he ha completely understood the Secret Techniques and himself, and has almost reached a level of complete transparency.

The reason it was "almost", was because there was one final point which he had not completely understood yet, which was the talent pane in his brain.

After defeating the shadow, Garen took out a match and torch from a bag in his robe. He lit up the match, and its tangerine-yellow spark fell on the torch, kindling the cotton cloth doused in oil.

This torch was specially made, with its handle hollow, within it was a large amount of fuel. It bore a similar concept to an alcohol lamp, which could burn for an extended period, until the oil in the torch completely ran out.

The bright light then illuminated a radius of four to five meters, and a faint smoke similar to that of a kitchen gas stove had since traveled further.

Garen checked the surrounding stone walls while holding the torch; there were no signs of combat either, even the black needles in his hands had suddenly disappeared.

"Since Cthulhu King has invited me in here, there should be a high possibility of meeting up at the end, walking further in should bear some results." Even though he didn’t find any remains of the shadow, he had a rough estimation in his thoughts.

This shadow was very strong, in this environment which suppressed unnatural powers, only with the body of form 5 which endured many years of fusion power was he strong enough to handle it.

If it were any other regular totem user, they would probably be shredded into pieces with the initial "greeting". However, Garen had his doubts, even if he could not use his unnatural powers, he might be able to tame some mutant creature, or use Obscuro’s derivator to forcefully control the larger mutants, and bring those in to fight the shadow.

As to why Cthulhu King and Divine God Palace Master were not doing this, perhaps there were other reasons.

Torch in hand, he continued advancing.

The tunnel ahead of him gradually became wider, and the atmosphere was once again filled with the faint blue mist. His surroundings cleared up again.

Garen extinguished the torch. With his eyesight, the blue light sufficed to provide a clear field of vision.

After an unknown period of time, Garen stopped twice midway and ate three times before the tunnel’s topography finally had some change.

The blue mist turned pitch black once again, the tunnel was thrown into darkness.

Bam!

A large shadow pounced again, this time from behind Garen. Like a large pile of black mud, it didn’t make any sound, much like an inanimate material being splashed onto Garen.

Without hesitation, Garen did a back spin kick. This time he did not reserve any power, all the raging power in his body was leveraged. With a ferocious spin, the tip of his leg conjured deafening howl, similar to lightning.

Bam!

The speed of the shadow was obviously of no match for Garen. Even its ambush was instinctively countered by Garen with a kick. In that split second, it was smashed against the wall on the right like a cannonball, smashing the abnormally sturdy walls into smithereens.

The shadow gradually disappeared, the tunnel returned to its previous calm. Only the rumbling of the debris from the wall was present.

Garen gasped for a while. Obviously the regenerative properties of the NIne-Headed Hydra had been suppressed. This one explosive display of power had left the usually strong Garen fatigued.

"Looks like my body’s endurance is mainly dependant on Nine-Headed Hydra’s vitality…. Without the unique powers, these immensely explosive moves seem to be unsuitable…"

It was like a mixture of steel and cement, together they could sustain huge loads, but the steel within was removed, the remaining cement would be much more brittle.

Likewise, the Nine-Headed Hydra’s unique power was the steel of the cement in its genes.

As the capacity of the body had been drastically reduced, coupled with the consistent use of such explosive moves, there would naturally be a large load on the body.

As Garen thought about this, he couldn’t help but to think about the other two people. Divine God Palace Master may still be fine, he already possessed strong and balanced build, but it may be tough for Cthulhu King.

With such extreme suppression of unnatural power, that’s obviously his strongest handicap.

Under this environment,, his abilities will be drastically lowered, making it extremely though for him, perhaps even worse. Of course, one cannot assume he didn’t have a workaround.

Following the shadow’s destruction, the tunnel quickly returned to its light blue state. By the looks of it, the tunnel will only turn dark when the shadow was attacking.

As usual, Garen checked the surrounding for traces, but there weren’t any.

He tidied himself and continued the journey.

As he passed through two arched halls that he had seen before, the tunnel became more and more inclined. Now it was obvious enough to feel that he was descending.

Soon, the darkness engulfed the tunnel again, the tunnel was absent of light.

Garen focused, waiting for the possible ambush

Fuu!

Suddenly, a flame was lit head of him. A tangerine-yellow flame, bright and scorching.

Garen suddenly realized he was facing a man in front of him. A man who had his head on flames.

He donned a black shirt, and only his head were exposed. It was clear that this was a young man. His eyes were unfocused, but he was gazing directly at Garen. His head had black curly hair, and his skin was visibly pale from the lack of exposure to sunlight.

Oddly enough, the man’s facial skin was burning along with the flame, and it quickly turned burnt yellow, and then black. Drops of human fatty oil started dripping from the burn, hitting the ground after gliding along the face.

The man shouted, and quickly flew towards Garen.

Bam!!

A ball of blinding flame burst and formed a crimson red fireball, and flying through the air.

Garen was thrown backwards due to the explosion. Both his legs tried hard to anchor him to the ground, his boots were instantaneously torn apart from the tremendous impact, and the soles even started smoking.

Garen’s hands shot up to protect his chest. His senses told him something was off at that moment, and he instinctively covered his head and torso.

The explosion dissipated in an instant, leaving only an incessant ringing in his ears.

Garen put down his smoking arms and examined his injuries; the outer layer of his arms were completely roasted, his skin was burnt to a hard crisp, and there were even some hints of plasma fluid oozing.

Guu….

"Compared to before, this one’s got faster speed…" Garen took a long sigh, the man’s suicide bombing charge was unavoidable for Garen. He could only hold up his hands to defend himself, and it ended after the explosion.

The explosion was very strong, but compared to the surrounding rock walls, Garen’s body was stronger. The surrounding walls lost an entire layer, but only Garen’s arms were hurt. This place suppresses unnatural powers, and the Nine-Headed Hydra lost its monstrous regenerative abilities, but the basic biological regenerative abilities of his genes was also a league above normal creatures.

This kind of injuries only needed a few days before it fully recovered.

As he felt the intense pain on his arms, Garen carefully observed his surroundings, the light blue mist came back, obviously the ambush this time had ended.

He sat down with his legs crossed. The surrounding stone walls were made from an unknown material, and extremely hardy, such a strong explosion only resulted in the destruction of about a knuckle’s depth of material.

He dared not advance further; he didn’t know how many suicide bombers lay ahead. If there were a lot of them, this journey would then require a better plan, and would have to redo his preparations.

In this situation without unnatural powers, it was very cumbersome to face this kind of

adversary.

Jiii….. Jii ….

There was a hopeful ringing sound in his pocket.

He quickly took out the dark red button, and gently tapped both sides of the button’s protrusion.

"Something happened over at your side?" Cthulhu King’s voice crackled across.

"You felt that?" Garen was surprised.

"A large explosion right? It was faint on my side." Cthulhu King replied coldly.

"I faced three of them before you."

"So what’s the situation now?"

"Really bad, most of my abilities were suppressed. Or perhaps not, they felt more like they were completely wiped away, disappeared completely. This situation is troublesome." Cthulhu King sounded anxious, his situation over there was much worse than he had estimated.

"Can we use gunpowder here?"

"Yes, so long as you’re not using unnatural powers, or anything involving totem’s power or mutated bronze’s pollution. All of those will be completely suppressed. Buy normal items are not being limited here." Cthulhu King immediately understood Garen’s plan. "You mean you want to use gunpowder? Guns?"

"We could try." Garen came from Earth, so he understood the tremendous power of gunpowder in its later stages, he emphasized a lot more on gunpowder compared to the people of this world.

"Let’s plan it outside." Cthulhu King fell silent for a while and then said.

"Self-destructing men? I have already passed that stage." a calm man’s voice suddenly came in, it was Divine God Palace Master. "After the fire man, there will be a type of shadow bearing a blade. It’s humanoid, with a black blade on his arm. He is strong, I am being blocked here."

Garen and Cthulhu King’s heart sank, Divine God Palace Master Actually passed the self-destructing men and reached a deeper level, Single Bladed shadow? There was actually something even more troublesome.

"Let’s meet up and plan it out at first floor, I will get my subordinates to send over something" Cthulhu King muttered.

"Okay."

After Garen left a marking on the walls, he immediately left.

He had to be careful when he came in, observing every detail, so his progress was slow, but it was much faster when he returned, under his full speed, he was leaps and bounds faster than his advancement previously.

Chapter 523: Ancient Ruins Expedition 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the previous floor with the goddess, the two were already waiting as Garen walked out of the tunnel.

On Divine God Palace Master was a green silk robe that looked as good as new, as though he hadn’t just walked out from a battle. He laid back onto the left side of the statue and had a shuteye.

Cthulhu King looked much worse; burn wounds of different sizes could be seen, his red robe was torn and it showed the red metal armor beneath it. He stood in front of the god’s statue, as though he were observing something.

As they saw Garen coming out, both of them diverted their gaze towards him.

Garen wasn’t in much better shape than Cthulhu King. Even though he wasn’t really hurt elsewhere, his arms were completely charred, it was apparent that the injuries were concentrated.

"We are more familiar with the topography than you, so we’d arrive first." Cthulhu King nodded, "I have already ordered my subordinates for some gunpowder, anything else you need would need to be requested now, on the third floor after the second, the Living Secret Technique should have the stronger guardian, we would need to cooperate to get it."

"Gunpowder may not work." Garen said softly, "After the fire men and single blade shadows, who knows what other troublesome characters are there. We need to prepare the best defensive equipment."

"I got them to bring some fire extinguishers, perhaps that would work." Cthulhu King had obviously given it some thought. Unlike Divine God Palace Master, they were obviously in different leagues. If he couldn’t even go against the firemen, then single blade shadows were out of the question.

"Perhaps we can head out together." Garen suggested,

"We don’t know which tunnel would the Living Secret Technique will be in. The Three tunnels were split into three different directions, plus, there’s more than just Living Secret Techniques in this ancient ruin…" Cthulhu King snickered.

"Let’s wait for a while."Divine God Palace Master decided, and then the three no longer said a word.

Garen walked up to the right side of the statue, and rested by leaning against it.

At the same time, his vision went from the hall into the lower parts of his Attribute Pane.

"Strength 14, Agility 10, Vitality 11, Intelligence 10, Potential 54521%"

"545 Points? That many?" Garen’s eyes had a hint of surprise.

After absorbing the Cthulhu's Origin to increase his attributes’ limits, he had always stayed in the kingdom without going anywhere. He actually hadn’t managed to try out his new abilities obtained from the Cthulhu's Origin.

One attribute point would require 100 points. This amount was just staggering, even he couldn’t increase it that much in a short time.

After he left the kingdom for the ruins here, he had not killed mutated creatures on any large scale to increase his potential points, as he needed to avoid detection.

"I didn’t even have 100 points originally, but now it actually reached over 500 points, it’s obvious that I gained these in the tunnel." Garen was thinking, "Just in time to see how much of a limit extension Cthulhu's Origin gave me."

He fixed his gaze upon ‘Vitality’, but his body walked over to a shadowy part of the hall behind the goddess’ statue, blocking himself from the other two person’s field of vision.

As his gaze fixed in place for three seconds, the vitality pane had a sudden jump, and then blurred for a moment. When it reappeared, the number changed from 11 to 12, whereas the potential points dropped to 400-odd points. One hundred points only provided one point of attribute.

Just after his Vitality was upgraded, Garen felt a cold breeze around his body. The burn wounds on his arm were recovering visibly quickly; the charred skin outside fell off like a hard-boiled eggs’ shell, without a sound, and was caught by Garen as it gently fell to the ground.

The previous injuries from the impact with the black shadow had also completely recovered; his body was beyond perfect at this point.

Upgrading vitality actually had the function of regeneration, Garen actually almost forgot about it. However, as he was feeling it, the vitality pane had actually reached its limit, and could no longer be upgraded. He felt that it was a waste. If he played his cards right, this kind of regeneration could perhaps even allow leeway for another life during critical moments.

After adding onto Vitality on top of the one point from before, he deduced out that the Cthulhu's Origin gave around 2 points. As he looked at the remainder of the points, the feeling similar to his vitality increasing occurring again. It was very likely that the two points of his attribute limit were distributed equally.

All this increased his limits by two points.

This should be the function of Cthulhu Origin.

Garen looked at the remaining three hundred odd points, he could add three more attribute points, and this would need careful consideration.

Garen stole a glance at the other two. Cthulhu King fished out a green colored ointment bottle and carefully applied it on himself. He seemed like he was tending to his wounds.

He did not leave the ruins for somewhere more convenient to recover. Garen then looked at Divine God Palace Master, his face had a calm, unfazed expression to it.

"Don’t be surprised, even if you headed beyond this place, you still couldn’t use unnatural powers to heal these wounds.." Cthulu King noticed Garen’s gaze and explained promptly. He then suddenly glanced at Garen’s arms. "Your arms?"

Garen shook his arms.

"The injuries weren’t deep to begin with, it was just the surface that’s charred black." The lie was as natural as it could be.

"Let’s prepare, the gunpowder is here, as well as three reinforced shields.." Cthulhu King nodded and announced.

Soon, a buzzing sound could be heard from the entrance of the forest, as though it were the howl of a tornado. Suddenly, a ray of white light descended upon the tunnel entrance for a few seconds. The white light slowly dispersed. Many bags of gunpowder appeared on the floor, as well as dark red inverted-triangle shields. The shields were unusually thick, and were actually ten shields stacked and reinforced into one. Its thickness was about the size of an open palm. The shields looked like three dense, heavy metal beams..

"They’re here" Cthulhu King led the way and walked over, he lifted it with one hand and lightly tossed it towards Garen, "Try one for size?"

Garen extended his hands to catch it

Bam!

A shield over a meter in height handed in his arms with a loud thump.

"Forged using the premium metals with anti-fire properties. Sayer Iron has good fire retardancy, as well as extreme defensive powers, albeit being slightly heavier." Cthulhu King said, "They weigh about two tonnes each."

"Two tonnes plus?" Garen meticulously gauged its weight,it’s already considerably light for him, but it was obvious that Cthulhu King made this based on his own specifications and body, a long-range totem user will never be nearly as strong as a close quarter combatant, let alone being in a place that negated all unnatural powers. Without unnatural powers the three of them can only rely on their sheer physical strength to use this shield. They were considerably weaker inside compared to when they were outside.

Without unnatural powers, Garen was also left with his body and Secret Techniques, as well as combat skills. Even those Secret Techniques like the Red Jade Hand, Myriad Water Jasper Technique or Black Water True Technique have devolved into nothing but the worst of the lower class combat skills without unnatural powers.

Without the support of unnatural powers, some techniques and abilities were for nothing but showmanship in the ruins, and were without purpose.

As they carried the shield and distributed the gunpowder, the trio convened closely in minute details about their experiences and the time taken during their journey, and then separated once again into the second floor of the ruins.

Compared to the first time, Garen’s footsteps were much louder and heavier with a two-tonne shield on his hand, he took each step slowly.

He could make up what the tiles were made of. It was actually sturdy enough for it to not leave any footprints even with such a load.

Garen was much faster during his second descent. He was almost running; with the additional point on vitality, there were visible improvements, especially in terms of endurance

With just two days, he had already advanced into the second floor met with the first wave of shadows.

Bam! The giant wolf shadow rammed hard against the shield, and a large portion of the tiny spikes were broken off. The shadow had also been hurt from the spikes, with a painful groan, it seemed to be even more agitated.

It expanded once again, almost taking up the entire space of the tunnel, and furiously rushed towards Garen.

Garen put up the shield and threw it forwards with both hands and all his might.

Fu Fu Fu!!! With deafening sounds of rotations, the shield turned into a high-speed revolving dart, which lodged into the shadow like a blade.

Unsurprisingly, the shield hit dead center and have split the shadow open. It continued to fly for about ten meters before it hit onto a wall of a corner, more than half the shield was lodged in the wall.

The shadow disappeared without a trace, the darkness surrounding it faded and returned to its usual blue hue.

Garen took a long sigh, then he walked over to dislodge the shield with a great heave.

It was a scene of serenity ahead and behind him; the blue mist continued to linger, but visibility was reduced to a ten meter distance..

Garen continued hurrying through his journey while carrying the shield, then it was the second wave of shadows. It was similarly unimpactful beyond the scare, it was clear that having the shield made things easier.

The third one, the fourth one, there were more shadows in this trip, but they were easily manageable.

After half an hour, the man with the burning head appeared again.

The yellow light immediately dashed towards Garen the moment it appeared with extreme speed. Just like an afterimage, it reached Garen in the blink of an eye.

The shield was positioned in front of him while he knelt down with both his hands against the shield.

Bam!!

The tangerine-yellow fireball disappeared after a moment. In the tunnel, Garen was pushed back several meters behind the shield, and the floor was left with a streak of black charred marks.

The shield had emitted white smoke due to its high temperature, and the air had a strong burning stench, just like the smell shorted electrical cables let out..

Garen slowly stood up from behind the shield and saw that the tunnel returned to the usual blue, serene setting. He looked over at the charred shield, but there were minimal dents on it.

"Not bad." he shook the shield, and the soot on top vibrated slightly and the fell out in large pieces, revealing the uneven dent of the dark red metal layer beneath it.

As he continued advancing with the shield, the pitch darkness appeared once again.

In the dark, a black silhouette slowly stood up from the floor, much like a liquid slowly forming a human shape.

Garen could barely make up the opponent’s features. It looked like a shadow that was about the same height as a regular person, its right arm was the shape of a blade, without palms or an arm, only a blade attached.

The shadow charged towards Garen without uttering a word the moment it had its eyes on him; it didn’t even make a sound, as though it were an actual shadow.

Dang!!

The blade hit the shield and left a deep cut in. Sparks flew from the clash in the darkness, brightly illuminating the darkness surrounding it for an instant.

Seeing that one strike was ineffective, the shadow leaped upwards and suddenly disappeared in mid air, it then reappeared behind Garen, and the right arm’s blade was aimed towards Garen’s nape in the next chop.

In that eye-blinking speed, one second hadn’t even passed between the interval of hitting the shield to the ambush from behind.

As the blade cut through the air, even though it didn’t produce any noise, it produced a black streak in front of the blade in the instant before it touched Garen’s skin, as though it completely shredded the air.

Without being able to react, Garen hurled the shield backwards. Blind from behind, his body used the change in momentum from the hurl to move forward.

With a thump, the shield missed any solid objects but got lodged in a wall. As usual, the shield sunk deep, sparking into embers of gold.

The shadow reacted by avoiding it in the last moment, as though it had a premonition. Garen’s speed was slightly faster than it, but before Garen had even begun hurling it, it already moved to avoid the strike, as though it could predict Garen’s attacks ahead of time.

Chapter 524: Ancient Ruins Expedition 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Whoosh…

Garen stood in the tunnel, it was pitch black around him, and he had his guard up.

The black shadow disappeared again.

"So you can predict what my next move will be?" Garen was not surprised in the slightest, he had encountered an enemy like this in the Secret Technique World, back then his opponent had used their judgment regarding blood qi and power principles to predict what his move would be. After all, before somebody moved, there would be some inevitable signs, although these signs were very fast and disappeared in a flash, anyone with fast enough reflexes would still be able to interpret them.

Faced with an opponent like that, Garen naturally had his countermeasures, unlike the locals like the Divine God Palace Master and the others, he had plenty of experience against such opponents.

His speed was faster than the black shadow, so all he had to do was give the opponent no time to predict his moves.

The corners of his mouth splitting apart, Garen stomped down hard on the ground, and the corner of the shield carved sparks and debris out of the wall on his right.

With a swooshing sound, he swept his palm and hit these pieces of debris precisely.

The pieces of debris, as large as a fist, shot into countless tiny stone shards in mid-air, and they did not just come from the front, at the same time, his left hand also scattered the mounds of debris, shooting out more shards.

The whole tunnel was immediately filled with a rain of projectiles, with the patter of stones smashing into everything everywhere, the huge force behind them giving these stones an intensely terrifying speed and momentum. With Garen in the center, the space within more than ten meters of him on either side was completely filled with stones. These stones had the destructive power of bullets, and they actually set alight sparks on the wall furthest to the right.

After smashing the stones, Garen did not hesitate, pulling back his hand and kicking out his leg, shooting out a kick above his head.

The black shadow with its single blade just happened to appear in the one safe spot above Garen's head, and took the full-powered kick head-on.

Even its blade could not block in time, with a bam, the black shadow was forcefully shattered into countless black shards in mid-air, and scattered tracelessly into the air.

His face splitting into a grin, Garen held up the Tower Shield and continued pressing forward.

After ten more minutes, he encountered yet another single-bladed black shadow, after finishing it off in the same manner, Garen had to rest for a moment. Under these circumstances, without his special power, it was something of a burden to him as well to use his full power consecutively. Add that to the long journey on the way here, with his guard up the whole time, and even he had to take a short breather.

For the next whole day, Garen encountered more than ten of these single-bladed black shadows, but while they started off slower than him, they soon began to move at the same speed, and even grew faster than him.

But since their area of action was only in that small area shrouded by darkness, and their own defense was not particularly strong, faced with Garen's wide-area attacks and his method of forcing them into corners, one by one, they still tasted bitter defeat in the end.

If most of his powers had not been limited, just fighting based off his physical qualities now, Garen was perfectly capable of instantly releasing his Black Water Mist against these black shadows, and then they would be dropping like flies.

But without his unnatural powers, his own powers were one or two percent of his abilities outside at most, and the other two were probably in the same situation, so the three of them advanced extremely slowly.

Just as the three of them were continuously exterminating the shadow creatures and moving forth, in the goddess statue hall on the first floor, a man in red robes with completely white eyes suddenly walked in.

"Have they already come in some deep?" The man muttered, he was the Light God, the second strongest person under the Cthulhu King, and he was also the person who first 'discovered' these ruins before reporting them up to the Cthulhu King.

But nobody would have guessed, that these ruins were actually his hometown.

At the very beginning, he had been one of the shadow humanoids that had escaped from this place, possessing a young man's body and finally becoming the Cthulhuism Society's Light Cthulhu after a series of events.

Since he was originally one of the local shadows, he was extremely familiar with the three floors of the whole ruins, and he even some of the memories from an ancient time in his mind, plus he especially familiar with the biggest advantage these ruins had to offer, in fact he knew them like the back of his hand.

Standing in front of the goddess statue, the Light God bowed slightly and prayed fervently, in that short instant as he was bowing, his whole body rapidly turned black, quickly turning into a faint, dream-like, translucent image.

Soundlessly, he split from one into three, and shot like lightning down the tunnels, more than twice as fast as the Cthulhu King and the others.

In just a few hours, he was in three places at once, tailing the three of them closely as they traveled down the corridors and onto the second floor.

In terms of power, in these ruins that limited any unnatural powers, even if he was a shadow humanoid, he still did not have any particular powers, he just had the talent to become a shadow for short periods of time, and he would die in an instant if he faced any of them.

But naturally his aim was not to die in an instant, the reason he had lured the three ultimate fighters into these ruins was so that they could clear the obstructions for him.

Those shadow humanoids blocking the way were beyond his ability to fight, his Light God was just one of weakest shadows from the very beginning, and the gulf between him and those powerful shadows deeper in was far too big. Without anyone else's help, there was no way he could possibly reach the deepest parts.

What nobody knew was that after these shadows died, they would leave their purest essence, the Void Core, in the air. These shadow's cores had huge benefits, they were priceless treasures that could heal wounds, and they also had a certain amount of control over certain parts in the ruins, plus they were secret medicines that could directly increase the strength of one's soul. If you were lucky enough, you might even get the legendary Ancient Endor Heirlooms.

And as one of these shadows, if he swallowed them, he could obtain a third of its power, improving all of his attributes at once.

But the Void Shadow Core was traceless, and extremely hard to detect, it would usually hide itself automatically, sticking to the shadowy corners of the tunnels. If they were not absorbed, these shadows would be revived, and once more gather into guardians. This was also the reason why Garen and the others had not discovered them at all.

According to Light God's plan, the second level should not be too hard for those three, but once the third floor was activated, and that strongest shadow came out from the secret room, it would surely get into a tangle with the three ultimate fighters, and that battle would not end anytime soon. But he knew an alternate path, that could go right around the entrance to the secret room and enter the room, so it was absolutely possible for him to take advantage of the time when the strongest shadow was distracted, to obtain the three Living Secret Techniques and the Shadow Demon Mirror.

Light God had been waiting for this day for a long time. Unfortunately, with his power, he could not even enter the second floor, but now he had a chance, with three meat shields in front of him, he was perfectly able to follow behind safely and reap the rewards. Once he got the Living Secret Techniques, and add the Shadow Demon Mirror to that, he would become the new Master of the Ruins! The Demon Mirror could spawn countless powerful shadows, and control all the shadows in the entire ruins, the strongest of which had Form Five peak-level power, with that kind of power, he would not have to worry about the Cthulhu King and the others coming at him for revenge at all. Using the army of countless shadows to surround them, or activating the other traps in the ruins that had shut down or lost control due to the passing of time, he could easily find enough time to retreat safely through the secret escape tunnel shortcuts.

Behind the tunnel Garen was in, Light God's black shadow abruptly appeared where the first shadow had died, and after turning one circle on the spot, he suddenly crouched to a corner on the left side of the tunnel, picking up a fist-sized stone with one hand while the other hand reached towards the shadow amidst the debris on the ground.

Strangely, the shadow on the ground was just like the surface of water, it had none of the hardness of the stone ground, and his black hand reached in easily, sinking inside, as though searching for something underwater. Amidst the sound of water splashing, he quickly found an irregularly-shaped black crystal from inside the shadow.

Light God cackled, and stuffed the crystal into his mouth directly, actually swallowing it whole.

As soon as the crystal was swallowed, his body seemed to grow slightly more solid. Standing up, Light God continued heading down the tunnel that had been cleared ahead.

At the same time, in the other two tunnels, everywhere a shadow had perished, Light God kept finding more Shadow Cores from the corners, and he kept swallowing them.

Light God's body grew more and more solid, larger and larger. But his aura also became more and more hidden, harder to detect.

*************

Boom!!

Garen bashed in the large-bodied shadow in front of him with his shield, after the single-bladed black shadows vanished, the next type to show up was this sort of large-bodied shadow, these black shadows were about as powerful as the ones before, and their speed was about the same as the fire people, both were slightly stronger than Garen, and even more shamelessly, they were well-versed in close combat, having two hooks instead of palms, so any touch would rip off a large chunk of Garen's flesh.

And yet what troubled Garen the most was not all these, but the fact that these fatties needed to be destroyed three times before they would die for real.

This time he truly experienced how helpless his opponents had felt when they were fighting him back then.

If he did not have an advantage in secret technique battle skills, wherein one-tenth of his power could function like five tenths, this would probably be where he stopped.

The fat black shadow flowed on the ground for a bit, and finally utterly scattered, this thing was stronger than Garen, and faster, without the advantage granted by the secret technique battle skills, he would really have no idea how to deal with it.

Garen panted heavily, lifted the Tower Shield and continued advancing, it had been more than ten days since he entered the second floor, but he still could not see the end ahead, and the countless shadows that emerged were growing stronger and stronger. By now, one fat shadow took him more than ten minutes to finish off, then further on…

Garen licked his lips, took the canteen from his waist and poured its contents into his mouth, with a splash, a mouthful of clean and clear water flowed into his throat. He brought the canteen down and shook it, there was not much water left inside, only one fifth, it seemed.

Although the opponents were growing stronger, he was not growing tired or annoyed in the slightest, and for a simple reason.

Each of these shadows would give him at least 40 potential points, not 40%, but the whole 4000%, 40 potential points.

The number of potential points corresponded with the level of power, in other words, the actual bodies of these shadows actually had power equivalent to Form Four or Five.

No wonder the Cthulhu King had to find two whole fighters at the same level as him before he dared to explore this place. He evidently had more information that he did not divulge.

These past few days, Garen had directly increased all of his attributes to their current maximum.

'Strength 16. Agility 12. Vitality 12. Intelligence 12.'

His Strength had reached 16 points, so he was no longer at a disadvantage in terms of strength when he faced the fatty, and was instead more or less its equal.

After achieving 12 points in Intelligence, he also finally developed a miniscule power. That was Instant Reflexes.

After reaching 12 points, there seemed to be a fundamental change, after increasing his Intelligence, Garen clearly felt a higher increase in his reflex and reaction times.

And the clearest embodiment of this upgrade in his battles was the appearance of a brand new ability -- Doublecast.

He could multitask, his left and right hands using two different secret technique battle attacks at the same time, or using them separately.

But the strongest was when he stacked on two hits for the same attack, this was using them together, and that was the true terror of this technique.

This ability was not simply stacking up two powers, it was a true stack of two Secret Techniques.

For example, there was a Threefold Fist Technique among the Secret Techniques, and with Doublecast, this could let him use the Threefold Fist Technique twice in quick succession, making it Sixfold!

Its effectiveness would reach a terrifying double of the original!

This seemed to match the way Garen had been using his Intelligence, he had never used it on planning or strategy, but put his all into becoming stronger himself, so now that his Intelligence had achieved a fundamental upgrade, it finally created such a terrifying technique.

Rather than calling it a technique, it was more like a natural ability that had been achieved by expanding on his potential.

Extremely powerful and fast reception and reaction, after changing, could finally more or less activate two types of Secret Techniques at once, using his powerful body as the base, to explosively achieve twice the destructive power.

This was the first morphed technique Garen had obtained from increasing his stats.

It made his heart burn a little with passion, and he began to hold some anticipation for the upgrades the other attributes would have as well.

Chapter 525: Ancient Ruins Expedition 5

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Aaggs! Aaggs!!"

Amidst the loud howling, a lizardman in front of Garen abruptly collapsed to the ground, the huge red single eye on its face leaking bright red blood slightly, dripping onto the floor and emitting a strange rotting smell.

Garen pulled back his right hand, his face slightly pale.

In just over ten minutes, he had killed more than ten of these lizardmen consecutively, so even he had to be somewhat mentally exhausted.

Straightening up his body and leaning onto the wall at the side, he once more picked up his water bottle and poured it into his mouth, the last drop of water reluctantly dripping into his mouth, moistening his dry lips, and causing Garen’s heart to be impatient as well.

"Who knows how long it will be before I can enter the third floor, these ruins are so huge, much bigger than what I had expected before." He watched as the lizardman on the ground slowly scattered into countless black dots of light, and the darkness around him rapidly disappeared as well, once more returning to the previous backdrop of pale blue mist.

He glanced backwards, and it was nothing but faint blue mist behind him, misty and blurred, nothing could be seen clearly at all, the tunnel seeming to stretch into infinity in the mist.

Taking a sharp breath, Garen continued to make his way forth. At the same time, he took that red button out of his pocket.

By now, the black robes all over his body had already been slightly damaged, after so many battles, even he could not keep himself from getting the slightest bit injured.

This was a space where totem power did not work, and he was only left with his own power physical martial skills and his body’s attributes.

Pressing the button, he instantly heard the crackle of static from inside.

"Is anyone there?" Garen asked softly.

There was no reply.

He did not keep the button, but instead Garen kept it held in his hand, and while he continued making progress, he would ask again every so often.

The lizardmen appeared again, these were not particularly hard to manage, but they just had special fist-fighting techniques, and were also faster than before. Still, compared to Garen, that was nothing.

After gaining the Doublecast ability, he had basically tested his limits. His body could only tolerate three uses of Doublecast within an hour, the explosive power of this technique was extremely terrifying.

When he was testing it, just one fist was enough to break a lizardman in half at the waist. The top half flew out extremely far, and the bottom half still did not move at all. The waist part in the middle, as well as a chunk of flesh, devolved into scraps.

In that instant, this technique had increased the power of his simple fist swing to twice the original power.

But the requirements for this technique were also undeniable. It took a tremendous toll on his heart and muscle tissues, if the Dragon’s Heart weren’t strong enough, even if his Intelligence met the mark, he probably would not have been able to achieve this technique either.

Of Garen’s physical battle skills, the most dominating was his Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills, these martial skills, based off the original Mammoth Secret Technique Battle Skills, had direct attacking styles, because the Mammoth Secret Technique was a strength-type secret technique, making its style also very simple and direct.

Of these, the four killer moves were the basics of all of Garen’s physical battle skills, as for the Sky Dragon's Crisscross that he came to understand later, despite the lame name, it had pretty considerable power, and was the fusion of the most brutal parts of his fighting killer moves.

As Garen kept advancing, he started to consider how he could improve the fusion Sky Dragon's Crisscross further, to form a powerful move using the explosive power of Doublecast.

For this sort of move where he instantly and explosively stacks them on, if he used extremely complicated moves as the basis, it would definitely reduce the power in some way, extending the usage time. But if he used a move that was too simplistic, it would not have enough power.

Then he needed to find a balanced middle point.

After advancing for more than ten minutes, the corridor ahead of him began to extend long black shadows again.

Out of habit, Garen stopped his footsteps, waiting for the black shadows to completely engulf him. After all these days, he was already very used to these shadows attacking him, at any such time like this, there would definitely be shadow creatures on the attack.

Standing on the spot and awaiting it with concentration, Garen could vaguely feel that, right ahead of him, a shapely figure was slowly appearing in front of him.

In the darkness, the figure seemed to be glowing on its own, its clear image reflected into Garen’s eyes.

Standing in front of him, was a seductive woman’s body with all the proper curves.

A skintight black leather shirt on top, a short black skirt that would just only wrap her butt at the bottom, revealing a vague glimpse at the scenery under her skirt. Further down, there was even the shape of long and round legs.

This woman had a tall ponytail, her exposed skin pale as jade, two pitch-black swords hanging from her waist. Most eye-catching of all was the black mask on her face, with a pair of bright black almond-shaped eyes on the top half.

Just the eyes and the skin, as well as the shape of her features under the mask, was enough to tell Garen that she was definitely a fairly good-looking beauty.

But why would a beautiful woman suddenly show up in a place like this?

The suspicion flashed past his heart in an instant, and instantly fell on the darkness behind the woman, there were more tiny footsteps coming from there.

Two identically-dressed beauties in short skirts walked out once more, they stared at Garen with calm eyes, the lifeless pupils in their eyes long since scattered, but they gave Garen the impression that they were staring straight at him, as the three of them slowly drew the twin swords from their waists.

Clang! Clang clang!

There were three clanging sounds, and three of them beat their swords together at the same time, as though preparing to attack.

"You three, still have your wills?" Garen could not help but ask, if they still had wills, then he could communicate with them to some degree.

Unfortunately, the three of them did not reply, and just stomped their foot, abruptly disappearing into the darkness, instantly leaving only their six black blades slicing through the air towards Garen in the dark.

The blades were not particularly fast, howling as they cut through the air.

Garen did not dare to let his guard down, after walking all the way here, he had noticed that his opponents had been getting stronger and stronger, so it would not be any different here.

His right palm pierced and flipped towards the wall.

Fwah!

A large piece of stone was torn off the wall and smashed towards the six black swords.

Garen quickly took two steps back, lifted his Tower Shield and shoved it forward.

The edges of the huge shield had long since been sharpened by Garen after these continuous days of use, and was comparable to the sturdiest war swords.

The edge of the shield met with the first black sword.

There was a flash of sparks in the darkness, a splash of fireworks from the clash between weapons.

The black sword was flung far away, wholly undamaged, it just spun a few times in the air, and was soon slicing towards his direction again. The other black swords took turns attacking the Tower Shield, leaving some deep cuts into its surface, and were flung out as well, though they returned quickly and continued their attack.

Garen brandished the shield, and knocked away the black swords once more.

Time after time, the black swords were relentless, every time they were knocked away, they would be completely undamaged, whereas the nicks on the shield grew larger and larger.

Garen frowned slightly, he had knocked the black swords towards the other black swords a few times, at first planning to harm the wielders of the black swords, but strangely, there was nothing behind the black swords but air.

But Garen had clearly seen the three beautiful female swordsmen before, and his senses could even clearly tell if they were real or illusion, with no chance of a mistake.

The black swords were not fast, neither were they very strong, but they just took no damage, no matter how hard he hit them, at the most he would leave some white marks on them, but Garen’s Tower Shield, on the other hand, was getting more and more damaged.

Garen watched the black swords’ attack patterns, movement routes, and the details about his surroundings carefully, over and over again.

The time ticked by, and Garen maintained a constant pace, knocking the black swords away time and time again, but the opponents seemed to know no weariness, sticking to him like glue.

"So that’s how it is?"

Finally, he vaguely noticed a clue.

When the black sword’s attack made contact with its opponent, its wielder would appear from a split second, other than that, there was no other flaw.

He could only attack the swordswoman at the exact moment the black sword hit him. And this instant was extremely short, just a hint of distraction and it would pass.

Once he had an idea in his heart, Garen instantly took the initiative and waved the shield as he advanced, forcing the black sword back.

In the darkness, the tiny bits of golden sparks kept lighting up, accompanied with the sound of clashing blades. Garen separated two of the swords away cleverly, and kept them alone in one area.

Psst!

Instantly, the Tower Shield in his hand split down the middle to form two large chunks, and Garen carried them each in one hand.

With two deep whooshes of the wind, one of the two Tower Shields blocked four of the blade attacks at once, while the other one smashed towards the two isolated swords.

The Tower Shield had a large area, just a light wave could take up most of the space in the tunnel. The black swords could not go around it, and had to face it head-on.

Clang clang! Bam!

Garen kicked out one leg, and a blurred figure behind those two swords was instantly kicked away, plastering onto the left-side wall with a bang, bringing down a rain of debris with it.

He could see that the figure that flew out was one of the women from just now.

After discovering the trick to it, Garen repeated it accordingly, and within two minutes, the other two women were also grievously injured and lying on the ground, their bodies revealed. The black swords also fell to the ground, becoming normal weapons.

The three of them were only average in their physical strength and endurance, it was just that ability they had to hide themselves completely that was very challenging, but it just happened to be countered by Garen, an expert peak-level fighter with plenty of fighting experience. Compared to the ability to control even the smallest split-second opportunity, no totem user could match the number of life-and-death battles Garen had experienced in the Secret Technique World.

The three women figures lay on the ground, but somehow were still breathing, after taking one of Garen’s lightning kicks, even the lizardmen from before were on the brink of death, what was more these weaker female bodies.

Garen walked over, bent down, and picked up one woman by her hair.

"Can you speak?"

Her eyes were wide open, but had no intention of replying.

Garen slapped her twice. After two loud smacks, she seemed to react somewhat, her tightly-closed long legs underneath her short skirt twitching subconsciously, as though she wanted to escape Garen’s control. But her seriously injured body could no longer move, that kick contained Garen’s shock technique, and had instantly destroyed most of the woman’s internal tissues and organs. According to a normal person’s body condition, it was a miracle that she could still move now.

"Do you have no will?" Garen frowned, and pulled off the woman’s black mask.

There was no jade-white skin under the mask, only a mess of blood and flesh, the whole bottom half of her face was rotten and dark red, she did not even have lips, only trembling rotting meat, as though covered with maggots.

The terrible odor made Garen frown deeply, this body truly hated intense stenches.

He looked at the woman from top to bottom, and suddenly tore off the woman’s clothes, with a yank, he revealed the skin underneath the leather clothes, this part was all fair and white, with a clean white chest cloth tying her breasts.

"So everything other than the face is normal?"

Chapter 526: Ancient Ruins Expedition 6

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen snapped the woman’s neck cleanly, and simply threw it aside.

Without that ability to dematerialize, these women figures were not too different from the strength shadows he encountered in the beginning, simple and easy.

Garen searched the other two women’s bodies, and found nothing, so all he could do was twist their necks as well and leave.

In the darkness, the three women’s corpses slowly melted and faded, utterly becoming one with the darkness.

When faced with these swordswomen, if one could not catch that split-second opportunity, no matter how strong a fighter they were, they would be destroyed by time alone. After all, the swordswomen’s speed and strength were not weak by any means, and three had appeared at once.

The battle chance could only be caught by fighters who were extremely nimble in their senses and their speed, and they had to be extraordinarily experienced. Any other type of person would have no choice but to waste away here.

The darkness retreated rapidly, and it became the same pale blue mist once more.

Garen stepped forward and continued on his way.

In the time after that, wave after wave of these beautiful swordswomen kept appearing, and unlike how easily he could dispatch them in the beginning, the swordswomen began growing faster and faster, until they caused him some trouble.

At first these swordswomen appeared in teams of three, then two, and by the end it was just one person at a time.

As their numbers increased, their power increased steadily as well.

By the time he reached the last single-woman team, the swordswoman’s power had already achieved an extremely high level.

The swordswoman’s black sword was like a bolt of lightning in the darkness, it kept turning and slicing, leaving him without a moment to breathe. The onslaught was continuous, the extreme speeds bringing explosive power as well.

After many collisions, the Tower Shield was utterly destroyed. Garen had no choice but to fight with his own hands.

The last swordswoman’s speed was already faster than his, reaching speeds equivalent to about 20 potential points, this seemed to be the limit, the swordswoman’s attacks came at a jumping curve, and the instant the black sword twinkled, the blade was already on Garen’s body.

Garen called this technique the Leap Slash, it was not any particularly special technique, just a terrifying ability born from the swordswoman’s explosive power.

With the price of a deep cut through his shoulder, Garen took the chance to smash the swordswoman to death and win. But he had no choice except to stop as well, waiting for his body to heal naturally.

Although he didn’t have his unnatural powers here, making his healing speeds much slower, but the Nine-Headed Dragon’s Heart still had a powerful recovery speed that normal creatures could not hope to match.

After resting in the same spot for three whole days, Garen’s injuries no longer affected him, so he got up and continued on.

In these three days, he had also understood the swordswoman’s final Leap Slash. The swordswoman’s body was far from as powerful as his, and yet she could demonstrate such explosive speed. That was how valuable that technique was.

After three days of reflection and study, and after so many hands-on fights with the swordswomen, Garen finally understood the key to it.

As an expert fighter who had witnessed many secret techniques, Garen had a far stronger understanding of these secret technique battle skills without any unnatural powers than the Cthulhu King or the Divine God Palace Master. Such techniques naturally held no secrets to his eyes.

His powerful Intelligence came into play in a big way here as well, as he successfully analyzed the principles behind the Leap Slash.

This technique could unleash close to 20 attribute points of speed in an instant, but it required a light and sharp weapon, by controlling the weapon and the rhythm of one’s body, using a special blood qi channeling technique, they could gather all the power in their body, and shoot out their weapon as though it was a hidden weapon.

Although this technique was strong, its limit could not go any further than 20 attribute points in speed, and its power was equivalent to a Form Four battle totem outside. Outside, this sort of technique had no meaning, but in here, in the ruins where he could only use his own body to fight, the Leap Slash had a powerful effect.

This technique may have put a heavy burden on the swordswomen, but to Garen, it was easy as pie. He could absolutely use it like a normal technique, such was the power of a strong Vitality.

Ever since he entered the ruins, this was his second time reaping rewards from it, the first was learning the Doublecast ability, this time it was the simple Leap Slash technique.

Both of these techniques were things he could use by himself, no matter in what surroundings, with or without totem power or Totem Light, they would not be weakened.

Garen suddenly understood, if the legends were true, then the Warlocks definitely had the ability to travel through space, and in the starry space, there were countless planets, some with unique environments, where one could use powerful abilities to leverage on all the power of the surroundings, while others were complete wastelands that could not be leveraged at all, so those leveraging powers would be greatly diminished.

And the only thing they could truly rely on was their own bodies. The channeling of the blood qi in their bodies, to create a tremendous power, that was the true core.

Bringing his thoughts back, Garen finally ate the remaining jerky, and took out the red button.

"Is anyone there?"

These few days he had done this practically every day, asking at least once a day, but there had not been any response from the other two sides.

This time, however, there was finally a response.

"Nine-Headed Snake?" A hoarse voice came from the button. It was the Cthulhu King, he sounded extremely tired. "Are you okay?" The Cthulhu King followed up with a question.

"My body is still okay, it’s just that I ran out of water and food, although I can last several weeks without a problem, my body will still be inevitably weak." Garen voiced out his problem.

"I tried, before those attacking shadows disappear completely, their meat is edible, so you can try it out." As expected of a cult leader, the Cthulhu King had even fewer taboos when it came to food than Garen, a natural born big eater.

"Alright…" Garen also knew that he had no other choice right now, besides the Nine-Headed Snake’s appetite was terrifyingly big, its digestion and absorption speeds also extremely scary, it could change most substances into its energy source, and it excreted its wastes in the form of poison mist, which was naturally extremely dangerous to others, but cleaned up the surroundings for Garen himself.

"Where have you reached?" The Cthulhu King continued asking.

"The swordswomen area."

"Same, that last swordswoman is very troublesome, I’ve been blocked here. According to the information, the third floor entrance should be right ahead, the three tunnels will converge again there." The Cthulhu King reminded, "That fellow, the Divine God Palace Master, is probably already there."

He paused, "According to our intel, other than the three Living Secret Techniques, there should also be a Shadow Demon Mirror in there, it’s an extremely powerful Heirloom that can control all the shadows in these ruins, it’s a War-type Ancient Endor Heirloom, these shadows should be an effect of that Heirloom."

"Why are you telling me all this?" Garen was slightly confused.

"To control the Demon Mirror, you need to fuse with it for a very long time before you can embed your own spirit and will in it, it’s not something you can control in a short period of time. After this, we’ll still meet the strongest shadow creature, but before that I have a proposition."

"Say it."

"I don’t want my portion of the Living Secret Techniques, I just want that Shadow Demon Mirror." The Cthulhu King said straight-facedly.

"That Demon Mirror is linked to the rights to control all of these ruins, right?" Garen chuckled. Looking at it that way, it seemed that the two had the same value, but Living Secret Techniques could be found in other ruins as well, while the Shadow Demon Mirror could only be found here. Obtaining it would be equal to obtaining an extremely powerful shadow army. In truth, the value of the Shadow Demon Mirror was higher.

But Garen was not really bothered with these external items, he placed more importance on upgrading himself. And obviously the Cthulhu King had a different view from his.

"Of course."

"What do you want from me?" Garen mused.

After a long silence from the other side, to the point that Garen thought the line had been broken, there was finally a sound from the other side.

"Get over here and help me settle the swordswoman leader… I… can’t get across…" The Cthulhu King seemed to be clenching his teeth.

Garen burst into laughter.

Breaking off the button’s connection, since he knew that the tunnels would merge very soon up ahead, and there should no longer be any shadow creatures ahead, he hesitated no more, and ran forward at full speed.

******************

Far behind the three people in the three tunnels

Each tunnel had a vague black shadow moving forward at high speeds, the Shadow Cores hiding in the corners on the ground constantly swallowed by this black shadow.

His aura was growing stronger and stronger, larger and larger.

From his initial lower Form Four level, he had rapidly grown stronger, and by the time Garen and the others faced the swordswoman leader, this shadow had already swallowed all the other Shadow Cores, growing to Form Five level power.

Three tunnels, three shadows, each of them with Form Five level aura.

All three were the Light God’s clones, he had already been a Form Five fighter to start with, he just had not reached the peak, and the clones he had created using many years only had low-level Form Four power. Just like God Cloud from back then, peak-level Form Five power, but his clones were only at the Form Four peak, a full one level lower.

And now, after absorbing the Shadow Cores in the ruins, the Light God’s three clones were each at Form Five level power, making him exuberant.

If even his clones had such power, if they merged together, just how strong would his actual body become? This was equivalent to absorbing all the power of the shadow creatures in the ruins, and turning them into the Light God’s own reserves.

Just like the Cthulhu King, after accumulating power over such a long time, even the exceptionally talented Phiros could not defeat him. He still forced himself into the ranks of the peak-level fighters.

As his power increased, the Light God’s ambitions grew as well, and when he occasionally sensed the three ultimate fighters moving ahead, an intense and unnamed desire began to rise in his heart.

If the Cthulhu King died here… then the Cthulhuism Society… would see the birth of a new Cthulhu King!

As for the other two, if they would obediently bow down and become his servants, they could be given a chance to live, if they were not willing…

Other than the Cthulhu King, the Light God’s attention was focused on Garen, this terrifying prodigy had achieved such heights in so few years, he was practically a copy of Hellgate from back then.

Such a prodigy must have a huge secret behind him, this speed of growth was no longer something that could be explained away as talent. Just like Hellgate back then. How did Garen get the Nine-Headed Dragon totem, why did he have unlimited lives, unlike what was stated in the information? These were all unexplainable mysteries.

There were far too many smart people in the world, they would also notice how Garen was different, but his overwhelmingly powerful abilities made it so that nobody dared to investigate any closer. Things were different now…

In these ruins, under these circumstances, the Light God was confident that he could take control of the Demon Mirror, and utterly kill the three of them.

Chapter 527: Secret of the Ruins 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stood at the end of the pitch-black tunnel, ahead was a wall sealing the tunnel shut, and there were no other branches in the path.

He checked the surroundings carefully, but there was no way through.

"Is it a dead end?"

Garen narrowed his eyes, walked to the right of the tunnel, reaching out his hand to knock the hard stone wall.

And then he walked one entire round around the dead-end tunnel, continuously rapping on the hard stone walls, making tapping sounds.

Finally, he stopped in front of one part of the stone tunnel, and hammered it hard with his arm.

Bam!

The previously hard stone wall actually shattered rather easily, forming a large hole.

With a whoosh of debris cascading down, Garen extended the area around the hole, making it larger, until it was large enough for someone to enter while bent over, only then did he stop.

The hole was glowing faintly, completely different from the pale blue mist outside.

Garen crawled into the hole, and emerged in another small room.

More than ten stone tables and chairs stood neatly inside, and there were carvings of wolf beasts on the walls, there were even more than ten round nightlight gems embedded in the ceiling, forming a circle ring that lit up with a pale yellow glow.

To others, this light was just a faint glow, and they would not even be able to see things a meter away clearly, but with Garen's vision, the whole room was bright as day.

The small room was cylindrical in shape, with a diameter of more than ten meters, more than ten skeletons lying all over the floor, with a layer of white membrane like cobwebs all over them, evidently these people had been dead for too long, their blood and flesh drying out until they looked like this.

Garen walked up to these skeletons, and checked them carefully, the dozen or so skeletons were all of normal human height, and there were bits of clothes scattered around them, he just had to step on them lightly for them to disintegrate into dust.

There was also a little arch-shaped door on the right of the room, Garen could not find anything useful on the skeletons, so he could just get up and walk into the small door, there was a narrow tunnel behind the little door, with yellow nightlight gems every ten meters embedded above,

Garen walked several hundred meters ahead, and vaguely heard tiny footsteps from ahead, at first he thought it was the echo of his own footsteps, but once he listened closer, he noticed that the rhythm was not right, and he instantly stopped.

The other person had evidently heard movement here as well, and stopped at almost the exact same time.

"Nine-Headed Hydra?" There was a soft question from ahead. The voice was clear and cool, and definitely belonged to the Divine God Palace Master. The head of the nest leaders walked out from one of the three forks slowly, and faced Garen head-on.

He was still wearing that green cloak, but the hems of the cloak were all torn up, evidently a result of the many battles along the way. But there did not seem to be many injuries on his body.

"So the Divine God Palace Master has arrived." Garen smiled slightly in reply. "May I know how you've been here, Palace Master?"

"About four days." The Divine God Palace Master had no intention of hiding it, and replied casually.

Garen's heart gave a jolt, if he could reach here four days in advance, that evidently meant this person was much stronger than even Garen with Doublecast. This really raised alarms in his heart.

After all, the Divine God Palace Master was not a human, if he truly had second thoughts, it would actually be extremely troublesome to deal with him in these sealed ruins.

Garen glanced at the branches at the detour, there were three branches in total, he was standing in one, the Divine God Palace Master stood in the one opposite him, and there was another in the center without anyone there, so it was obviously the tunnel that the Cthulhu King had gone in.

Garen stared at the Divine God Palace Master, hesitating for a moment, and neither of them spoke anymore, the other person seemed surprised that Garen was the one who showed up first, rather than the Cthulhu King who led this whole expedition.

"I'll go check out how things are with the Cthulhu King's side." Garen said quietly, and walked straight down the middle branch, while remaining wary of the Divine God Palace Master's actions.

It was only after he walked a long distance down the middle branch, and the Divine God Palace Master was completely out of view, that he slowly relaxed.

Walking down the tunnel, he ran for a bit over an hour, and began to hear the sound of clashing metal in front of him.

Soon enough, the faint blue mist in the tunnel ahead slowly faded, and was replaced by an utter and complete darkness.

In the darkness, the red-robed Cthulhu King was being chased relentlessly by a darting black lightning bolt, seeming unnaturally out of his depth.

"Help me!" Seeing that Garen had arrived, the Cthulhu King instantly looked overjoyed.

Garen glanced around, there were still large shards of a chunk of the Tower Shield, it had a sharp shape, like a triangle. He kicked it up with his foot, and caught the shard in his hand with a smack.

"Leap Slash!"

He gathered up all the power in his body, twisted, and formed a shape like a spring, and then Garen released it rapidly as he took in a breath.

Bong!!

The shard in his hand instantly carved out a lightning bolt, and at the very instant the swordswoman leader connected with the half of the shield in the Cthulhu King's hand, he slashed the swordswoman's waist precisely.

With a tearing sound, the swordswoman was torn in half, chopped into half at the waist.

The body rapidly turned into black shadows and melted into the darkness, the pale blue mist filling the tunnel once more. Everything returned to being peaceful again.

The Cthulhu King panted loudly, his chin underneath the mask dripping sweat. His long robes were also soaked with sweat, plastered to his body.

"Much thanks." He leaned his back on the wall, took out his water bottle and gulped down some water, closing his eyes as he began to rest.

Garen was not too bothered either, waiting quietly at the side.

After more than half an hour, the Cthulhu King finally opened his eyes.

"I owe you one for this time."

"Don't hide anything from me anymore." Garen was slightly upset about the Shadow Demon Mirror that showed up from nowhere, this news should have revealed early on, and not tacked on later. If the Cthulhu King was able to defeat this shadow swordswoman by himself, he probably would have monopolized the Demon Mirror himself.

"It was my fault, but the Divine God Palace Master doesn't know about this either." After Garen helped him this time, the Cthulhu King's attitude was much gentler, and he was finally interacting with Garen as an equal of the same level. As for the grudges caused by the ten thousand mile chase from before, these were somewhat eased as well.

"The Shadow Demon Mirror is the main control central for the whole ruins, this was never an underground city, but a military fortress, the shadow creatures left in here had actually lasted for countless years, at first the shadow team controlled by the Shadow Demon Mirror was much larger than right now, it was just that some problems appeared after such a long time."

"I don't care about any Shadow Demon Mirror, don't forget the condition you agreed to before."

"Of course." The Cthulhu King nodded, "There are three Living Secret Techniques, one is a frost-type, one has powerful life force, and there was one more that I had booked before, it's a metal weapon-type."

"Metal weapon works too." Garen agreed after some thought.

"Garen, you never encountered a Living Secret Technique before, right?" The Cthulhu King called Garen's name, in a somewhat friendly manner, he seemed to want to ease the tension between the two of them using these small details.

"That's right."

"I have some info about them here, dunno if you're interested in it." The Cthulhu King held out an olive branch, trying to fix his relationship with Garen.

"Let's talk as we walk." Garen was just frustrated that he did not know anything about the Living Secret Techniques, so naturally he would not reject him.

There was no information at all about the Living Secret Techniques in the Kovitan royal library, these things were a secret that only peak-level fighters had a right to know, so there was no way it would be saved into any secret library.

On the way back down the road ahead, the Cthulhu King told Garen everything in detail, all the general information about the Living Secret Techniques.

Living Secret Techniques had their own innate evolution potential, if one successfully trained a normal Living Secret Technique, it would fuse all the power and blood qi in the practitioner's body, absorbing even the source of their power, fusing and shrinking it, refining it into a Seed of Strength. This Seed would follow the direction most appropriate for the secret technique, discarding all the impurities, and reabsorbing the practitioner's spirit and will once more, growing gradually, growing in a way that completely suited the practitioner's own personal secret technique state.

By then, once the secret technique was successfully trained, they would not need to learn moves anymore, and it would instead become an innate ability, almost like a talent. The so-called secret technique effect, had basically become the body's own ability.

The whole Living Secret Technique was just like a living creature, using the practitioner's will and spirit, killer moves, and power source as its nutrients, after slowly growing and maturing, it would bear fruit, that being a stronger secret technique innate ability.

It would become a natural and mysterious system rooted deep in the practitioner's body, embedding the secret technique ability that had been refined into the practitioner's body fully, forming an almost innate, terrifying ability.

On the way, Garen kept going deeper into all the information the Cthulhu King was telling him about the Living Secret Techniques, the more he understood, the more amazed he felt.

This sort of secret technique was no longer purely a secret technique, and it was instead an indescribable, mysterious seed.

"Then can one person practice two different types of Living Secret Techniques?" After digesting the information the Cthulhu King had, he asked again.

"Unfortunately not, but you can absorb the pros and cons of the two types of Living Secret Techniques, removing the strength secret technique system from one and inserting your own will and spirit into it again, plucking out the Seed of Strength from one Living Secret Technique, and turning it into your own power's Seed of Strength." The Cthulhu King explained, "The Divine God Palace Master plans to do just that. Otherwise the nest leader can't have his own Living Secret Technique at all."

"You can do that?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"Of course you can, but you need to really understand this Living Secret Technique, and at the same time your own secret technique system must not be rejected by it, only then can you maybe try it, and if you fail, the consequences are extremely dire, the spirit and will, as well the source of your power source that you inserted inside will disappear completely, and even the practitioner's many years of hard effort will be utterly wasted. This is a loss of the source from your memory and your body, and it can't be salvaged. Once you fail, the many years of power that you accumulated and tried to insert will be lost in an instant." The Cthulhu King lamented. "If the Divine God Palace Master wants to leave his destiny as a nest master, it will be very, very difficult."

Garen nodded instinctively.

The two of them walked forward for some time, and finally returned to the fork where the three branches met.

The Divine God Palace Master was still leaning on the stone wall, closing his eyes and resting.

"You're finally here." Hearing the footsteps, he opened his eyes to look at the two of them.

"We can enter the third floor now." The Cthulhu King nodded at him. He took a small yellow paper packet out of his pocket.

"If you want to open up the third floor entrance as soon as possible, this would be the easiest way. I didn't expect that I would not use it with the fire people, but ended up using it here instead."

Garen also took out his portion of the explosive packet, and the three of them put the packets together, on the floor right in the middle of the fork. The three of them retreated respectively.

The Cthulhu King took a match out of his pocket, lit it up, and simply threw it onto one of the fuses.

Psst…

A slight burning sound came from the fuse.

Chapter 528: Secret of the Ruins 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In that instant, a burst of burning red light abruptly lit up from the ground at the fork.

Boom!!!

The thick smell of smoke spread everywhere. The white-yellow smoke utterly covered the whole tunnel’s branched exits.

The Divine God Palace Master reached out his left hand and fanned it lightly

Phew!

A whirlwind started up, and his left hand seemed to leave behind a trail of after-images in an instant, as though he had sprouted more than ten palms, waving forward at the same time, which then instantly merged back into one.

The wind that was created immediately blew the smoke into the three tunnels, and quickly revealed how the ground at the center looked like now.

On the floor of the left by the branches, a large black irregular hole had appeared, and small black cracks could vaguely be seen in the hole. It was evidently the result of the explosion just now.

Under these circumstances when unnatural power could not be used, it was the easiest to use a lot of special black powder to find the entrance, of course the three of them could find and create an entrance by themselves, but it would not nearly be as fast and direct as using explosives.

The explosion had created a huge tremor, and it would reveal the hidden entrance, so they did not have to find the specific location themselves.

"There’s an entrance here as well." Just then, the Divine God Palace Master frowned slightly, his hand pressed on the right-side wall, there was also a hole with tiny cracks there, a result of the tremor.

"Two holes, which one is it?" The Cthulhu King asked in a deep voice.

"Do you want to split up and check?" Although Garen asked that, he was already walked to the underground hole, when his right foot stopped.

Bam!

A large chunk of the stone on the floor fell after one step, revealing the pitch-black tunnel underneath, it was like a deep pitch-black well, leading to god knows where.

On the other side, the Divine God Palace Master had already quietly opened up the hole on the wall, making an oval-shaped hole that was enough for someone to enter, there was a vague blue mist coming from inside.

The Cthulhu King narrowed his eyes, but he still followed Garen to the well. The two of them exchanged glances, and Garen just jumped, disappearing into the well directly, the Cthulhu King jumped in as well, and soon only the Divine God Palace Master was left at the fork, he looked at the hole in the ground, and then turned to walk towards the hole in the wall.

**************

Bam!!

Garen landed hard on the ground, creating a middle-sized crater. The ground was a burnt-black stone floor.

This was a huge charred-black hole, there were dark red and charred-black stone chunks all .over the walls, and a long black stone cliff in the middle of the cave. It was like a black metal bar embedded into the middle of the large oval-shaped cave.

The cliff extended backwards, all the way connected to a pitch-black metal door on the cave walls.

By now, Garen was half-crouching on top of the cliff, he raised his head and looked up, there was a small hole directly above him, it was the entrance he had fallen down from.

Phew!

Another red figure fell down, turned slightly in mid-air, and crashed towards the cliff stone floor behind Garen, also creating a crater on the ground.

"We’re here, the Hall of Glory's Testament…" The Cthulhu King stood up and straightened out his long robe. His expression was slightly complicated. "This is where the Divine God Palace Master’s Flame Secret Technique is. Not ours."

"This is where the secret technique is?" Garen was slightly surprised, he looked around, but did not find any special places hiding the secret techniques at all.

He walked to the cliffside and looked down, it was an endless pitch-black abyss down there, and he had no idea how deep it was.

He picked up a rock the size of his head and tossed it down, but he waited for several minutes and still heard no echo.

"So deep." Garen frowned.

"Be careful not to fall in, that down there is the Abyss of the Dead, if you fall in, you’ll just keep falling endlessly, without anything to eat or drink, falling all the way until you die." The Cthulhu King reminded him. "It’s still not time for the secret technique to appear yet, we need to go into the sealed room and finish off the last guardian first, and then only can we go into the secret room to obtain the proof needed to get the Demon Mirror and the secret techniques, before we can finally split up and get our respective Secret Technique Seeds."

"Where’s the secret room?" Garen looked at the Cthulhu King, he evidently knew more about the details, so now he could only rely on the Cthulhu King to lead the way.

"Over there." The Cthulhu King pointed a finger towards the black metal door behind the cliff.

The two of them did not hesitate at all, walking straight towards the large metal door.

Clack…

Suddenly the large metal door began to open outwards, gradually emitting a slight clacking sound, in the middle of the large door, a bit of black abruptly appeared, and like a piece of paper being set on fire, the black burned and spread from the center towards the surroundings, the black flames flying everywhere, while the large metal door, several meters tall, was burned away soundlessly. It revealed a large bright hall behind it.

The two of them walked inside, one after the other.

The large hall was like a huge, wide cathedral, with the surrounding walls made of colorful glass windows, while there was a pointed ceiling several dozen meters above their heads.

The floor was covered with old black and white interchanging bricks, the long black pews mostly damaged and old, while right ahead of them, on a dirty silver-black prayer podium, there was a black and clean thin-necked flower vase, with a wilted black rose in it.

Garen looked towards the two sides of the cathedral, there were some round soil-yellow wooden buckets on the floor, and on the walls between the windows, there were carvings of fresh flowers and angels. Faint pillars of light shone in through some of the colorful windows’ cracks.

"Are you sure we haven’t returned to the surface?" Garen narrowed his eyes as he looked at the Cthulhu King in front of him.

"We’re still way down deep underground, do you really think we could have possibly been instantly returned to the surface without any teleportation, and without us knowing?" The Cthulhu King did not even turn around as he replied in a deep voice. "Look carefully, that is not sunlight… it’s golden lava."

Garen was slightly taken aback, and immediately looked at the window cracks carefully, as expected, the golden color coming from the cracks was indeed flowing slightly, it really was golden-colored lava.

These light pillars were actually rays of light reflected from the dazzling lava.

This entire large cathedral was actually surrounded by copious amounts of golden lava.

Everything coming in through the cracks of the windows around them was gold-colored lava, shining down pillars of golden light, illuminating the whole cathedral and making it bright as day.

While the two of them were observing their surroundings, a small door on the left of the cathedral also opened slowly, and a green figure walked out, it was the Divine God Palace Master who had just separated from them. When he saw that the other two were there too, he paused for a moment, and then began to consider his surroundings. When he saw the golden lava, his gaze focused as well, his expression turning serious.

"With that, we’re all here." The Cthulhu King nodded at him.

The moment the Divine God Palace Master walked into the cathedral, the entrances they had taken to come in, be it the large door or the small one, all of them rapidly faded, vanishing. All that was left was bare walls with carved reliefs, as though there was never any entrance or large door to begin with.

All three of them had their hearts skip a little, and they instantly walked to each either.

Just then, in the black vase on the podium, the wilted rose moved slightly.

Ahhh!!!

There was a sudden scream, like the hysterical wail of a woman.

All three of them were taken off-guard, their minds pausing for a moment, then they saw the wilted rose in the vase growing like living vines, rapidly growing many tiny black roots, looking from afar, it was as though some black liquid was flowing out of the vase, flowing down the podium, and to the ground, it was a black ‘liquid’ made of countless vines and roots.

After the many vines and roots flowed down, they gathered and grew rapidly, becoming taller and thicker.

Soon enough, within a dozen or so seconds, a huge black tree man, more than ten meters tall, appeared in front of the three of them.

Roar!!

The black tree man bent down, opening his mouth wide, and roaring in rage.

"I will promiseseyt ma sela!!"(1) The tree man actually roared out in an unknown language.

Countless black vines suddenly shot out of its two black holes for eyes, rapidly weaving into a huge warhammer more than ten meters long and five to six meters thick.

Phew!!

The huge warhammer crashed down towards the three of them.

Barroom!

Amidst the loud crashes, Garen and the other two separated abruptly, nimbly avoiding the hammer blow.

But immediately after that, the tree man suddenly whipped out vines and swung them neatly behind the three, just like a whip. After several cracking sounds, the three of them were hit squarely, and flew into the corners of the cathedral like bombs.

Boom!!

Garen was completely dizzy and disoriented, his vision a complete mess as the world spun around him, he had been shot out straight through the air and crashed harshly into a large pile of round wooden buckets, in the midst of some shattering and crashing sounds, he shook his head, and slowly stood up among the rubble that had been the wooden bucket shards.

He was just in time to see the giant tree man lift the warhammer, swinging it hard towards the Divine God Palace Master, who had just gotten up.

Before the warhammer landed fully, the huge force had already created a clear circular current of air on the ground, pushing the shards of the furniture and the dust on the floor away.

The Divine God Palace Master’s ears abruptly turned black and sharp, and he even raised his arms to meet the tree giant’s warhammer face-on.

Aaaaahh!!!!!

That piercing woman’s scream rang out again, and the Divine God Palace Master’s actions slowed for just a second.

Boom!

He was directly sunk into the ground by the huge hammer, leaving behind only a larger crater in the ground, a cloud of dust and debris flying up so nobody could see the situation inside clearly.

"It sure has… been a long time since I’ve enjoyed such a one-sided disadvantage…" Garen chuckled under his voice, and wiped the blood flowing down his forehead.

On the other end of the cathedral, the Cthulhu King’s whole body was spinning at a high speed, his arms spread open wide, his whole person looking like a red wheel, emitting a piercing whir as he cut through the air.

In an instant, the movement of his entire body stopped abruptly, from extreme speed to extreme stillness.

Psst!1

A red lightning bolt shot out from his body, and almost as soon as it did, it appeared on the brow of the tree man, it was a red throwing knife.

With a bang, the tree man’s head was thrown back slightly, and a large black hole appeared there, but it was soon filled in by black vines.

It raised its warhammer abruptly, and swung it down towards the Cthulhu King’s direction with a whoosh. But the Cthulhu King had long been ready for it, and dodged it by a hair.

With a cacophony of sound, the long pews and several grey-white angel statues on the other end of the cathedral were instantly demolished, after the warhammer swung in one circle, it was spin in a circle and once more flew towards the Cthulhu King, who had just steadied his footing.

However, Garen’s figure had somehow appeared beneath the tree man’s right foot. He drew a circle with his two arms, folding his palms together at his chest, and at the same time his chest sunk deep as he took in a long breath. It was as though his whole figure had shrunk by one size.

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement!!!"

With a loud roar, and accompanied by the wild soundwaves, Garen’s palms shot forward explosively, and crashed into the tree man’s right leg.

With the full use of his Doublecast technique, the Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement was released in two stages. It was equal to twice the power of Garen’s attack, and with his loud roar of rage and the ensuing soundwaves, it crashed into the tree man’s right leg.

Translator’s note:

This was written exactly like this (yes, English-gibberish) in the raws, no translation needed.

Chapter 529: Secret of the Ruins 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ker-chak!

The black tree man’s right leg fell down kneeling, having been broken down the center.

A large cloud of dust flew into the air, and Garen took that chance to retreat at lightning speed from beneath him, landing somewhere further away and watching the black tree man’s movements from a distance.

Just then, the Divine God Palace Master was crawling out of the deep crater, his body covered in blood, even his green cape had been utterly dyed black. He shook his head, his whole head now covered with black scales and his ears pointed.

Psst!

Four arms shot out from under his existing two arms, the scythe-like arms of a grasshopper, and under they glowed faintly with a flashy silver light under the golden lighting. The two arms he initially had also slowly became two scythe-like folding blades.

His six arms in total opened and closed slightly, making snippy cutting sounds.

Soundlessly, the Divine God Palace Master disappeared from the spot, and directly appeared, as though teleporting, in the middle of the black tree man’s chest.

With a snap, the six arms pierced deep into the black tree man’s chest, and immediately afterwards, they acted like a blender, cutting at high speed, the six arm blades turning into blurred shadows that could not be seen clearly. Many vines and black roots were chopped off and flew down.

Roar!!!

The tree man who had just recovered his broken leg staggered back a few steps, countless black tree roots and vines extending out from all around him, like tentacles from all directions reaching towards the Divine God Palace Master.

Die!!

The Cthulhu King’s voice said abruptly.

In that instant, a piercing red light shot into the black tree man’s right eye hole.

The black tree man threw its head back, and fell kneeling to the ground again with a whumph.

The red light had pierced through the back of its head, and was nailed to the wall behind it with a thump, turning out to be a sharp dagger twinkling with red light.

The Cthulhu King somersaulted a few times in mid-air, and landed lightly underneath the flying dagger, kicking up a stone to knock the knife down with a clang, so that it landed steadily in his hand.

By then, Garen had also appeared beside him, steadying his footing,

"This guy is the final guardian?" He looked at the giant black tree man that was fighting the Divine God Palace Master, and asked quietly.

"Should be, I’m not very sure either." The Cthulhu King stared at the tree man, "Careful, this tree man isn’t that simple."

"You go up, I go down!"

Garen shot out straight away, his arms like a Thousand-handed Goddess of Mercy, his palms instantly meeting in front of his chest, his eyes suddenly turning pitch-black. He was channeling the Black Water True Technique at full strength.

"West Phoenix!!"

There was a gust of wind like a pure bird’s cry beside him.

A pair of translucent wings of air spread open behind him.

His palms abruptly pierced forward!

Garen’s whole person was like a piercing sword, piercing the black tree man’s left leg joints in an instant. The shapeless currents formed a giant bird that screeched piercingly, almost like a solid totem, standing guard beside Garen, while at the same time, it spread open its wings and pounced towards the black tree man.

This was purely using the peak-level shock technique, combining it with the intricate manipulation skill of the King of the Century and other higher levels, the power of this one hit had long since surpassed the West Phoenix Fist from his time in the Secret Technique World.

His palm pressed together, he darted forward, and as the sides of his palms cut through the air, they emitted a screech like that of a huge bird, pulling in the air around him to form an incomparably sharp blade of air.

Psst!

The black tree man’s left knee joint snapped in half with a ker-chak.

Its whole body fell forward abruptly, and it landed face-first on the ground. A huge hole appeared in its chest, and standing in it was the Divine God Palace Master, his brow shining with a green light.

The Cthulhu King did a somersault, his body turning into a red wheel, and he spun as he stabbed downwards.

The red wheel stopped, and he gripped a dagger in both his hands, burying it deep into the tree man’s brow.

Bam bam bam!!

There was a chain of explosions coming from the tree man’s head. Several large holes were blown into the tree man’s face.

The three of them got up at once, leaving the tree man’s body. Watching the silent tree man, they exchanged glances.

The many vines on the tree man torso began to unravel instantly, and soon formed a huge black ring on the floor beside the tree man.

Phwah…!

The moment the ring was formed, the wounds on the tree man’s body rapidly regenerated again.

The expression on their faces changed slightly, and they rushed towards it again, but three vines twined around one of their legs each. By the time the three of them chopped off the vines around their legs, the tree man’s body had completely recovered, and it crawled up again.

"It has an Immortal Body!" The Cthulhu King was extremely familiar with this sort of ability, "We can’t go against this guy with brute force, even outside it would be a Form Five peak! In here, our powers are limited, we need to think of a way!"

"Even the Immortal Body needs a power source to regenerate, we just need to find it and destroy it." The Divine God Palace Master’s icy cold voice came from nearby.

"It’s not the head, nor is it the chest." Garen’s eyes lit up, "That vase!"

"Do it!"

The Divine God Palace Master stomped down, forming many cracks on the surface of the ground, and then he shot towards the black tree man like a missile.

The other two also split up at the same time, forming a triangle to surround the tree man.

Garen did not look at the other two, he just mustered up his power, and wandered around the tree man, trying to observe it and find the source of its power.

Just now he had used Doublecast three times in a row, that took a heavy toll even on him. He was already at the limit, if he used it anymore, it would truly harm his body.

The other two were evidently in the same boat, that terrifyingly powerful killing attacks from before should also have their cost, otherwise they would not have jumped away and rested after the black tree man collapsed.

This time the three of them bided their time in order to recover, and carried the black tree man on a destructive wild goose chase around the cathedral hall.

The time ticked by, and by the time the three of them were more or less recovered, the whole hall had utterly become a collapsed dump of debris.

There were craters of different depths on the walls, the floor, and some of the windows had also cracked, some gold-colored lava forced in through the holes, like fresh blood flowing from the wounds on the walls, slow and viscous.

There was a black circle floating around the black tree man, a spinning ring formed out of countless vines and roots, it was constantly spinning at high speeds, and its sharp edges cut everything it touched, slicing easily through everything.

One time when the Divine God Palace Master was rushing towards the black tree man, he was touched by this circle, and three of his six arms were immediately severed, only after that could he just retreat out of this circle of blades. But even then, he had evidently taken a large blow, his eyes dim and lightless, evidently these six arm blades were not just his method of attack, they also had a close relationship with part of his body’s core origin.

After that, the three of them no longer dared to go against the black tree man with brute force, instead walking around it and waiting to recover.

By the time the lava flowing into the cathedral gathered more and more, the space they had to maneuver began to shrink, and the three of them finally decided to face it head-on, their bodies also having more or less recovered.

If they went on like this, without enough place to move freely, no matter how strong a person was, they would still be crushed to death by the black tree man.

Garen’s top half was practically soaked in blood, as he landed, panting, on a piece of black rock among the lava. He watched from a distance as the other two kept the rather clumsy black tree man occupied.

"That black vase should be on his left palm!" He yelled loudly. After observing for so long, he had finally noticed where the source of the black tree man’s power was. But although his body had recovered somewhat, the poisonous gases and high heat from the lava was roasting his lungs, making it so that he felt rather powerless right now.

If it weren’t for his innate poison resistance, and if someone else was in his shoes, their condition right now would probably be even worse.

The Cthulhu King already had most of his power sapped, thanks to the poisonous gases and high heat, so he could only barely keep the black tree man busy.

Only the Divine God Palace Master still had energy, each of his movements seeming easy and effortless, even though two of his arm blades had been chopped off, his speed still was not compromised. The lava seemed to pose no threat at all to him, he stepped in it many times, but was never damaged.

Hearing Garen’s words, the Divine God Palace Master’s eyes shone, and his legs started changing shape as well, turning into two sharp silver crescent blades, piercing into the ground with several ‘snickkk’ sounds.

In an instant, his whole person had turned into a shadow, pouncing towards the black tree man’s left arm.

Garen half-crouched on the spot, although he had forced himself to recover a bit by then, his insides were still a mess, as he was walking rounds around the tree man, he had been ambushed by the vines twice, and his body was already full on hidden injuries. If it were not for the Dragon’s Heart’s powerful recovery ability, he would probably have died of massive internal bleeding by now.

Without unnatural power, the Nine-Headed Dragon’s superpowered talents would not be expressed. This situation was probably the most dangerous he had been in since he transmigrated here, if the Divine God Palace Master could not finish off the black tree man, the three of them would probably all die here in this sealed room.

"This tree man’s power is at least 30 points! Its speed is about 10 points, it has the Immortal Body, and without more than 15 points in power, don’t even think of penetrating its outer layer, it still has that sharp spinning ring beside it. It’s basically an extremely terrifying war machine!"

Inwardly, Garen estimated the physical attributes and abilities of this black tree person, and the result made his heart tremble slightly.

If this creature was left outside, unless several peak-level fighters surrounded it at once, it could even have destroyed this whole world.

And now only the Divine God Palace Master still had the means to defeat it, Garen stood up, and was just about to rush forward to continue delaying the black tree man, trying to create a chance for the Divine God Palace Master. Suddenly, a black vine shot out from behind him, and whipped towards the back of his head mercilessly.

Garen flipped around, and jumped high into the air, as though there were eyes at the back of his head, avoiding the vines.

And immediately after that, a sharp vine shot out from beneath his feet and through his hand. He gripped the vine tightly with his hands, holding it back from piercing his face.

His arm and the vine were engaged in a constant tug-of-war, then Garen gradually forced the vine away from him.

It was exactly then that, in the middle of the area, there was an explosion near the area where the Divine God Palace Master and the black tree man were fighting.

Barroom!!

The black cutting ring was like a bomb, turning into countless vine thorns that rained down, shooting towards all four directions.

The many black thorns were like a black rain, shooting towards every corner of the cathedral without letting anything through.

The countless wails of the thorns slicing through the air broke all of their eardrums at once, their ears beginning to bleed.

But the most dangerous part was not that, it was the countless spray of thorns.

Garen mustered up his strength, and diverted more than ten of the thorns aimed towards him, but every single one of these thorns had more than 20 strength points, so in the end, his arm strength let one through.

Psst!

A sharp thorn went straight through his left shoulder.

Ahhh!!!

Garen roared in rage, his hands practically waving into two blurred shadows, but there were still some thorns that managed to get through, piercing his right chest, stomach, and knee.

A sense of weakness that he had not felt for a long time kept surging out from his body, Garen’s right knee had been snapped, and he fell down kneeling with a bam.

Just then, the last, largest thorn pierced straight for his brow.

Garen gathered up the last of his strength, and blocked his head with his hands.

Psst!!

The thorn went right through Garen’s palms, and a small part of it buried itself into his forehead.

Garen’s head fell backwards to the momentum, his whole body pushed several meters back by the force behind that thorn.

He opened his mouth, but could not make any sound, his head tilting as he fainted to the ground. The wound on his brow began to ooze bright red blood, but it was quickly roasted into a red-black by the high heat.

Chapter 530: Secret of the Ruins 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beside him, the Cthulhu King was like a sieve, everywhere except his head poked full of transparent holes, his arms and legs had been severed off as well, landing beside him. His cheeks had been pierced right through, his ears torn off and lost elsewhere, a large chunk of flesh gone from the right side of his neck, revealing the white windpipe and red arteries.

Although he had not lost consciousness, he had it even worse than Garen, although he was still conscious, he was already utterly unable to move. Like a broken puppet, he lay on the ground, and nearly touched the lava that was extending towards him. He watched as the golden lava approached him slowly, but could not move in the slightest.

Right now, the Divine God Palace Master was using his arm blades to impale the black vase.

The giant black tree man crashed to the ground, turning into countless black vines and roots, these vines and roots rapidly wilted and yellowed, melting slowly, thick black smoke rising from it as it vanished from the floor.

Other than the rubble around the whole cathedral, there was no longer any trace of the black tree man.

The Divine God Palace Master smashed the black vase onto the floor, hard.

Phwah!

The vase instantly shattered into countless shards.

Ahhh!!!

That same piercing scream rang out again, and stopped abruptly, the pieces of the vase melting instantly, becoming the same thick black smoke, fading and vanishing away.

The Divine God Palace Master’s gaze dimmed, his arms and leg blades all turning back into normal human limbs, as soon as they turned back, he stumbled, and nearly lost his footing. Evidently he had also fought to his very limits.

Boom…

Just then, a triangular black stone platform fell down from above the cathedral, and crashed onto the floor of the cathedral.

There was a stone statue of a kneeling angel on the platform, its eyes closed as it prayed, its hands holding a cross-shaped sword, its expression fervent, and many vines and roots surrounding its lower body.

Directly in front of the angel statue, a clump of vines extended out, forming a black arm that held three badge-like ancient items on its palm.

"The Secret Technique Testament…" The Divine God Palace Master immediately recognized the items on the palm, he took a deep breath, and tore off part of his worn-out cape so that it would not trip him. He glanced at the two people nearby.

The Cthulhu King was on the brink of death, unable to move, while the Nine-Headed Hydra was slightly better, but even still he was badly hurt, and unconscious.

The Divine God Palace Master stumbled towards the stone angel’s platform.

Bam!

Suddenly a large hole was blown out of the cathedral floor to the left, a black hand sticking out of the hole and grabbing the edges.

A black shadow jumped out of the hole, landing lightly beside the black hole, it was a humanoid figure made of pure black air, and it surveyed the situation around it.

"As expected… Just as I expected… Haha… Hahahaha!!!" The black shadow could not help but throw his head back and laughed heartily.

"Who are you?" Hearing the familiar Daniela language, the Divine God Palace Master’s heart sank slightly, and he stared at the black shadow. Even his steps gradually slowed from their intended path to the stone platform.

"Although the location changed slightly, the final result is still very much to my satisfaction…" The black shadow gathered a pitch-black oval-shaped mirror with silver rims in its hand, there was purple mist twirling around the surface of the mirror, as though it was not solid.

"Light God?!" The Cthulhu King from the side suddenly spoke, his voice hoarse, there was no body to his voice at all, it was just the echo of air currents.

"King, you never thought it would be me, huh?" The Light God chortled, his body rapidly turning solid, turning back to his original Light God appearance, it was still that handsome man dressed in white with white eyes.

It was just that his expression now was cocky to a certain extent.

"Forget it, you three are all the world’s strongest fighters, if any accident happens again that’d be bad, I should send you off on your way first." The Light God held up the Demon Mirror, and shone it at the Divine God Palace Master.

Bam!!

The Divine God Palace Master was already almost touching the stone angel platform, but suddenly it was as though he had been hit by an invisible fist, he rolled back abruptly, lying flat on the ground, he wanted to get up, but no longer had any energy.

"The Shadow Demon Mirror can transform creatures into powerful shadows, even their souls will have to obey me, hehe, with demon shadows as strong as the three of you…" The Light God could not help but laugh out loud.

Once the three of them became demon shadows, all of their wealth, strength, power, secrets, all of it would become his, at that time, he would truly be the strongest power in the whole world, even if he wanted to unify the East and West Continents, and become the King of the World, it would not be impossible!

Thinking of that, the heat in the Light God’s heart grew so intense it threatened to overflow. He had never thought that the situation would be this good, the three ultimate fighters and the guardian had worn each other out, and now it was impossible for either side to fight back. This was basically the best possible opportunity handed to him by destiny.

As the thoughts flashed past his head, he held up the Demon Mirror again and aimed it for the Divine God Palace Master.

Bam!

The Palace Master was sent flying again, but he still got up stubbornly, his gaze determined, with no hint of any wavering at all.

The Light God began to frown, the power of the Demon Mirror changed according to the distance, the closer it was, the stronger.

And the Divine God Palace Master evidently knew this because of the Cthulhu King, plus he himself did not dare to go too close either, who knows what other desperation moves these ultimate fighters might have, it would be troublesome if it backfired.

He glanced at the other two, the Shadowfication worked best against people who had utterly surrendered to him, that had the highest chances of success. Although the Cthulhu King was grievously injured, if the Light God wanted to shadowfy him, he would still need to subjugate his will, this was obviously very difficult, and he was not willing to approach the Cthulhu King now, when he was still conscious, even though he was now much stronger, the Cthulhu King still had an advantage over his soul, this was a limiting method that had been buried into his soul from the very start.

On the other hand, that Nine-Headed Hydra…

The Nine-Headed Hydra was unconscious, so although he did not purposely surrender, it should still be much easier than the other two unconscious ones…

Although the Light God had forcibly reached the pinnacle of power by swallowing the shadows, his previous impressions and psychological trauma made him still unwilling to face the three ultimate fighters head-on. Even if he had the Demon Mirror, he still instinctively felt as though he was no match for them. This psychological fear was the absolute impression left behind by the Cthulhu King after many, many years. It was not something that could be extinguished in a moment.

The Light God hesitated for a moment, and then walked towards the stone angel platform, standing in front of the platform, he reached out and grabbed all three ancient black badges into his hand. He did not look at it carefully, putting it directly into his clothes. And then he leaped a few times, landing beside the unconscious Garen.

"This is the first one, hehe!"

The Light God pulled out the Demon Mirror, it was a black mirror the size of a washbasin, oval in shape, with tiny silver patterns on the side, every so often, there was also a small and complicated symbol, like words or perhaps patterns. There was a round pearl on the top that looked faintly purple, and there were three rings of triangular frames around it.

The strangest part was the center of the mirror, in the middle of the mirror, as calm as the surface of a lake, there was a blurred human face, only as large as a person’s palm, with eyes, a mouth, and nostrils that look like black holes, making it look like it was wailing, or terrified.

The Light God lifted the Demon Mirror, and shone it at Garen, who was lying on the floor. The face in the mirror instantly twisted, its features instantly releasing an invisible, mysterious power. The invisible light shone down, but Garen was no longer at the place where the rays landed.

Bam!!

A large hand covered in scabs grabbed his hand that was holding the Demon Mirror.

The Light God’s expression stiffened, and Garen’s terrifying face, covered with bloody scabs, appeared beside him.

For that instant, his brain was utterly blank, a huge force blocking his arm stubbornly, with such powerful strength that it did not feel at all like something a heavily injured person could do.

Scree!!!

In that moment, it was as though he heard the piercing trill of a huge bird, instinctively, the Light God swing his fist towards Garen’s stomach, his leg kicking hard at Garen’s injured knee.

Garen flung his right hand, shaking the Light God until his movements fell apart, and easily dismantled all of his attacks. And the other left arm was already coming at him with a powerful wind, forming invisible wings of air, piercing into the Light God’s stomach with a hiss.

Wah!

The Light God spewed out a mouthful of blood, and his whole body began to fade. His lower abdomen had been completely pierced through by Garen’s left arm. His body was like a dying fish, struggling on the sharp fish hook.

"This is the kind of trash that was taking advantage of us behind our backs?" Carrying the Light God with it, Garen’s right arm swung towards the ground.

Barroom!

A crater several meters wide opened up on the floor as a result of the West Phoenix Fist’s terrifying double-amplified power, connecting to the crater beside it.

Impaled on Garen’s right arm(1), the Light God could not dematerialize anymore, and his body was brought back by the gigantic tremor. In this place that prohibited unnatural powers, he did not have the terrifying physical prowess of the other three, he only had strength and speed of his same level. Although he used to be a Shadow of Strength, and had the advantage of his strength increasing after he dematerialized, he could not use his shadow body when using the Demon Mirror, and was instead caught by Garen, who was pretending to be unconscious, so he was instantly critically injured, and was now on the brink of death."

"Trash with just power, but without the mentality or technique, even a hundred more of you would still be crap." Garen chuckled coldly, pulling his right arm out of the Light God’s abdomen, his fingernail hooking and yanking, instantly tearing off a large chunk of bright red flesh and blood, he even hooked out a large chunk of the Light God’s guts, throwing all of it to the side casually.

Beside him, the Cthulhu King also slowly hid a red needle back under his tongue.

The green veins that had risen up slightly in the Divine God Palace Master’s eyes also slowly retreated.

With a crisp ker-chak sound, Garen tore off the Light God’s head with one hand, carrying it back-handed, while he stuffed that Demon Mirror into his own clothes, but after looking for a while, he still could not find a pocket that was whole, so he had to tie up the hem of his robes, hanging it from his waist.

Finally, he bent down to search the Light God’s body, looking for the three Testaments from just now, after distinguishing them for a while, he shot two of them out.

With two hisses, the two Testaments landed beside the other two.

"This piece of trash dropped the Demon Mirror right into my lap, according to our deal, it should belong to me, right?" Garen laughed lightly.

"Don’t forget our deal." The Cthulhu King suddenly spoke from the side.

Garen nodded.

"We’ll exchange in a bit."

"Okay!"

The Divine God Palace Master looked at Garen deeply, however, although he was a nest leader and not a human, he could still tell that these two had long since noticed that the Light God had been following them, and had staged this pretty play.

"As expected, humans are all sly." He confirmed this again in his heart. Out of the three of them, only he had been kept out of the loop, stupidly fighting with his all against the black tree man, and now that he had been grievously hurt as well, he was now at the same level with those two.

And there was that Light God, although he was not that strong, he was still Form Five, with powerful secret techniques and martial powers, in the hands of the Nine-Headed Hydra, though, he was as powerless as a baby, that just showed how big the difference was between the two of them, making it so that ten percent of Garen’s power was enough to match the Light God’s 120 percent, it was basically a steamrolling!

The Divine God Palace Master picked up the Secret Technique Testament, and stood up without a word. No matter what, they were finally temporarily safe, although the Demon Mirror could control the shadows, but right now all the shadows had been killed, so there was no longer any power for it to control, and all that was left was to split up and get the Living Secret Techniques that were suited for each of them, as per their previous agreement.

Translator’s note:

As usual, the raws can’t seem to tell left from right…

Chapter 531: Secret of the Ruins 5

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After the black tree man fell, three arch-shaped black doors had also appeared slowly on the walls of the cathedral hall, as though black flames had burned through the paper surfaces, the sides of the black doors were all ashes, mingled with black and sparks.

Garen looked at the Testament in his hand, and strode towards one of the doors, no longer looking at the other two.

Going past the black door, he entered yet another cliff, surrounded by a limitless black abyss.

The cliff was in a huge deep blue hole, freezing winds blowing through the air, making it unnaturally cold.

Standing on the edge of the cliff, Garen looked down, only to see a sea of pitch-black, with the vague hint of a roiling black mist. He was all alone in here, and there was a thick layer of transparent ice on the stone walls.

He took a deep breath, steadying his heavily injured body, and holding the ancient badges in his hand, he opened his palm calmly, then he closed his fingers down on it tightly again.

The Testament Badge instantly sliced a small wound on his palm, the blood flowing around his palm, and dripping directly into black abyss below.

The dark red blood drops bumped into each other and rolled about, scattering and falling into the bottomless abyss, disappearing in an instant.

As the blood dropped down, Garen lightly released his Testament Badge, and let the blood-tainted badge slide out from his hand, also falling into the deep abyss.

Whoosh!

Just then, a bit of blue lit up suddenly in the deep abyss.

At first the blue was only the size of a sesame seed, but in an instant, it expanded to the size of a fist, and in another instant, the blue abruptly rushed up from the abyss, a wave of ice cold blue air like a tide.

A giant ice blue bird, several tens of meters tall, flapped its wings and flew out of the abyss, suspended in front of Garen in an instant, its huge bright blue eyes staring at Garen on the cliff calmly.

The huge bird had a long tail feather, like the legendary phoenix, but it had an incomparable and terrifying icy air around it, instead of flames.

The blue ice layer on the walls around them kept growing thicker and thicker, and within a dozen or so seconds, the whole place had become a huge ice cave.

Clouds of almost solid cold white air surrounded the bird and Garen, singing lightly as though it was alive. That was not the sound of the wind, but rather more like a rhythm and melody.

There was still a lot of cold blue air roiling around, expanding, a cold blue current spinning through the air like seawater.

Garen raised his head to look at the giant bird in front of him, the huge blue wings spread open lightly, guarding him from the sides like a statue carving.

The huge bird lowered its head slowly, its beak approaching Garen, and opening slightly.

A dot of blue light fell out of its mouth, and hovered just in front of Garen.

The light had a hint of pure cold inside, Garen could feel that it was not just his body that felt this cold, just looking at that dot of light, even his heart felt traces of cold.

He reached out his right hand, and gripped the blue light dot lightly.

He felt as though the light dot wanted to bury itself into his body, and Garen did not put up any resistance at all either, relaxing his heart and spirit, only to see the light dot dart under the skin on his palm, utterly disappearing from sight.

As soon as the light dot vanished, the huge bird in front of him faded slowly as well, vanishing slowly as though it was an illusion. All that was left behind to prove it was not just a dream was the ice on the walls.

Garen took in a deep breath, and carefully checked his body, but discovered nothing.

He knew that he probably would not feel anything for a while, combining it with what the Cthulhu King said would happen before, he turned around decisively and walked towards the sealed room in the cathedral before.

Striding back to the cathedral, he glanced at the other two black doors, and walked straight towards one of the black doors, where the Cthulhu King’s scent lingered.

Walking past the black door, he saw the Cthulhu King just barely standing on the cliff, evidently waiting for him.

Garen tossed the Light God’s head, that he had been holding this whole time, towards the Cthulhu King’s direction, the head rolling to the Cthulhu King’s foot, but the Cthulhu King did not even look at it.

For world-dominating heroes like the three of them, they would never actually take such overconfident novices seriously. In the end, the Light God’s self-absorbent plans and plots would have no hope of succeeding even if he was facing anyone else other than Garen.

Precisely because he posed no threat whatsoever, they did not place any importance on him at all, forget facing him head-on or hating him.

"Just waiting for you." The Cthulhu King looked even worse than Garen, although there was no longer blood flowing all over his body, the wounds of different sizes were still clearly visible, just one glance and more than ten wounds could be seen. Add that to his deathly pale face, and he had obviously lost a lot of blood, the fact that he could still stand out of his power and determination was enough to see how he inherited the title of Cthulhu King, proving that he was an impressive figure.

Garen nodded at him, and strode over, taking down the Demon Mirror that he had tied up, and threw it over directly.

The Cthulhu King also threw him his Testament directly. The two items crossed paths in mid-air, falling into their respective hands.

Catching the Testament with a smack, Garen strode to the edge of the cliff, turning around to look at the Cthulhu King. The latter smiled at him, and wisely retreated a long distance away.

Only then did Garen grasp the Testament again, applying slight force, so that drops of his blood instantly dripped into the abyss. After that he released the Testament again, letting it tumble down.

In no time at all, a dot of red light lit up again deep in the abyss.

The red light came with an intense whooshing sound, like the sound of an intense wind blowing at a huge fire, then the whole abyss just lit up suddenly, the piercing red light growing brighter and brighter, closer and closer.

In an instant, bright red flames sprayed out of the abyss, like a sea of fire, illuminating the whole cave fiery red.

In the middle of the flames, a huge humanoid figure, more than fifty meters tall, flapped its wings and pounced up.

The humanoid figure was covered in red bone armor, with bat wings on its back, and every time it flapped its wings, it would bring a surge of flames.

In just a few seconds, the red-armored figure had dashed out of the abyss, floating in front of Garen, and looking down at him slightly.

The figure was like one of those legendary devils, with an utterly humanoid shape, black bat wings, and a pointy long black tail twisting slightly behind it. Its whole body was covered with a boiling brand-like red bone armor, and a pair of curly black horns on its head.

What Garen admired most was the countless intricate symbols carved into its bone armor, and the black humanoid carving on the middle of its chest that seemed to be suffering. That human figure had its arms spread wide, as though crucified on the demon’s chest, and its eyes were full of pitch-black smokiness, it was even wailing in a low voice.

Just then, the devil flung its long tail, covered with layers upon layers of thorns, slightly, and it came towards Garen lightly like a snake.

"Careful! That’s the Living Secret Techniques backlash!!" Behind him, the Cthulhu King’s expression changed, and he yelled hurriedly.

"Backlash? Looks like this secret technique should be a type of demonic technique!" Garen’s expression did not change. He allowed the long tail curl around him.

There were countless scales stacking on the long tail like thorns, forming many hooks, and even the slightest touch could tear a large chunk of flesh and blood off any living body.

With a curl of the thick long tail, it was enough to completely hide Garen away, so that he could not be seen at all.

Garen’s eyes were abruptly dyed pitch-black, surrounded by the huge tail as he stood, and suddenly he spread his arms open wide.

Screee!!!

The piercing cry of a huge bird rang out in the air. Currents of air flowed behind him and gathered, forming a pair of huge transparent wings, several dozens of meters long, and flapped them lightly.

Bathump!

Bathump!!

Huge tremors began to spread and beat from Garen in the center, as though it was the pulse of the Earth beating.

The Frost Living Technique that he had just absorbed was rapidly taking root and growing inside Garen’s body, from his lower abdomen, growing countless tiny blue light roots, and spreading towards every corner of Garen’s body.

The most eye-catching was the Dragon’s Heart in the middle of Garen’s chest, the countless blue light strands surrounded and wrapped around it, the mix of blue and red forming a pulsing blue cocoon.

The giant red devil retreated a certain distance, covering its chest with its right hand, pulling back its tail, and bowing slightly towards Garen, lowering its head and smiling as it bowed like a noble.

Boom!!!

The devil explosively scattered, turning into countless dark red flames, spraying everywhere and swimming about, filling the whole cave in an instant. The Cthulhu King had no choice but to retreat into the black door, watching Garen in the center of the flames from afar, that was the only place in the cave that did not have flames.

Garen stood at the edge of the cave, a black-red cross-shaped sword impaled in the ground in front of him.

In the middle of the sword was a carving of a suffering figure, it was just like the carving on the devil’s body, its eyes flowing with black air that spilled down the black-red blade, and spreading apart on the ground, like icy cold air, sinking heavily.

Garen reached out his hand abruptly, and gripped the blade of the cross-shaped sword lightly.

Psst!

A pair of black metal wings spread from the holt of the blade, the wings reflecting a faint black light, stacking and stacking, as though it was woven out of many metal wings.

As Garen gripped it tightly, many uniform and closely-woven patterns appeared on the hilt of the blade, like twining snakes, close-knit and dense, forming a strange non-slip pattern.

The moment he gripped the handle, Garen’s originally pitch-black eyes also overflowed with two streams of black air, like the figure in agony.

Clang!!

The black-red cross-shaped sword was abruptly pulled out, standing straight in front of Garen, the blade of the sword as clear as a mirror, clearly reflecting Garen’s face.

Garen laughed coldly. Holding the cross-shaped sword tightly, he raised it up.

Whoosh…

In an instant, the countless red currents of flames formed a huge whirlwind of fire, as though returning to their origins, rapidly gathering towards the sword’s blade.

The many streams of flame, the many fiery snakes, all poured into the blade.

With just over ten seconds, the whole cave had utterly cleared out, leaving behind not even a trace of fire.

That black-red cross-shaped sword had also soundlessly faded, becoming transparent, and finally disappeared from Garen’s hand.

Garen’s pitch-black eyes also slowly returned to normal.

The cave instantly fell silent, as though the flurry of flames just now was just an illusion.

"Congratulations, Palace Master Garen, on obtaining two Living Secret Techniques." Behind him, the Cthulhu King said loudly as he laughed, this person could give and take rather easily, and seemed to think the ends justified the means. From his arrogance at the very beginning, to his fury and helplessness afterwards, until he finally looked at Garen seriously, he could even forget about their past grudges for the greater benefit, inviting Garen to join in, to prevent the dgpm from overpowering them and monopolizing everything.

Garen turned around, a hint of suspicion in his eyes.

"I remembered you said before, that when obtaining the Living Secret Technique, it would often form all sorts of unique fantasies, these fantasies would mostly be an illusion formed by the unconscious emission of the secret technique’s aura. But what was that just now?"

The Cthulhu King had also seen that huge devil automatically releasing its backlash, instead smiling, bowing, and giving way to Garen. His eyes twinkled, who knows what he was thinking.

"Or maybe… maybe Your Excellency has a powerful existence in you that even Living Secret Techniques cannot resist…"

He lowered his voice slightly, replying softly.

Chapter 532: Secret of the Ruins 6

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen looked at him deeply, that black-red cross-shaped sword was actually the materialization of the Living Secret Technique from that devil.

And it was just then, that the two secret techniques seemed to be slowly merging inside his body, creating a strange and unique effect with his own Black Water True Technique.

The Living Secret Techniques, especially this Secret Technique that the Cthulhu King had given him which was appropriate for himself, definitely had some special characteristics that he did not know.

Seeing Garen's expression sink, the Cthulhu King chuckled, leaned on the black door, and coughed a few times, heavily.

"I didn't trick you, this Living Secret Technique is the real deal, it just has some little side effects."

Garen narrowed his eyes slightly, and was about to say something, but he saw the Divine God Palace Master walk out slowly from behind the Cthulhu King, and the words he had wanted to say paused in his throat.

The Divine God Palace Master glanced at the two of them, and walked to the middle of the cliff by himself, sitting on the ground, and leaning on a protruding stone to rest.

The three of them took up three spots in front, in the middle, and at the back of the cliff respectively, not saying anything.

Each Living Secret Technique was an ultimate and powerful existence, once you find a Living Secret Technique that suited you, and trained it successfully, you could break past the peak of Form Five, like Hellgate, and enter Form Six, reaching a terrifying, unprecedented level. Everyone would want such a treasure, and the more the merrier.

*********************

More than ten thousand kilometers away from the ruins, the Enderian capital, Monolith Main City.

The huge Monolith City was like a giant white dragon, nestled on the soil-yellow highlands.

There were the white Enderian national flags flying everywhere in the city, the white flags with the red cross flapping loudly in the wind.

At dawn, between the scattered swathes of green paddy fields outside the city, many teams on horseback, all dressed differently, rushed towards Monolith City under the attentive gazes of the farmers.

Like so many differently-colored long ribbons, they flowed into the city from all directions.

On the high walls inside the city, there were groups of totem users in white patrolling back and forth, and many Double-Headed White Eagles also flew circles in the air above the city, occasionally squawking, loud and long.

Several huge hot-air balloons were suspended in the air, with people scattering clouds of fresh pink petals from the baskets below, forming petal rains that fell down.

In the group headed towards Monolith City, some were riding tall horses and all other types of creatures, while others just walked, their armor bright and distinguishable. There were even some who sat in carriages pulled by flying birds and walking creatures, advancing at high speeds.

On the two sides of Monolith City's large white stone doors, almost a hundred meter tall, there were two giant white statues, also almost a hundred meters tall, one held a sword while the other held a shield, and both wore helmets so their faces could not be seen. There were occasionally people who stopped at the feet of these stone giants to admire them.

Outside the city gates, the traffic kept flowing, without end, peddlers carrying fruits and vegetables, outsider totem users with weapons, swords and shields on their backs, wandering hunters with their longbows and arrows, even some stout men wearing black silk clothes, these men in silk clothes had a simple pattern of two dragon heads on their chests, and were in fact disciples of the Black Swamp Palace from Kovitan.

"What are the Nine-Headed Hydra's disciples doing all the way here? Could they also be here to join in the World's Totem King Festival?"

On the left of the large white road leading into the city, a worn old black carriage with silver edges drove in slowly, there were several black-armored guards following it, and one of the young guards spotted those few members of the Black Swamp Palace, muttering under his breath.

"Nine-Headed Hydra?"

The carriage's curtain was lifted slowly, revealing a man's face that looked curious.

"Recently, after Phiros died in battle, his many descendants were exterminated, only his oldest son having hidden well enough to save himself. These Black Swamp Palace disciple should be out here to gain experiences, ignore them."

"Even if the Black Swamp Palace Master himself comes here, could he be stronger than Phiros?" Another girl's voice came out from the carriage, with an air of straightforwardness, evidently the owner was a cheery and straightforward person.

"After coming out from underground, it's been such a long time since I've seen such clear skies…" The woman lifted the other curtains, revealing a pretty and fair face, looking up at the sky, her bright yellow eyes revealed an ease as though she had put down a heavy burden.

"The President has called out all of the society's fighting power this time, and even pulled us out from underground, looks like he really means to make it big." The man said in a low voice.

"That's for sure, it's just we still need to plan our move. Phiros' final battle that time caused our President to sustain some slight injuries as well. I didn't expect the King of Daniela to have nearly broken past that limit, if we gave him a few more years, he might really have become a great enemy of ours."

"Thank goodness President was decisive enough, and made his move before that guy became a ticking time bomb." The man nodded in agreement. "The Divine God Palace in the south have gathered a bunch of people, seems like that old fellow hasn't given up yet."

The woman shook her head, and said no more.

The man sighed.

"After settling the King of Ender here, it's time for we, the Black Sky Society, to unite the two continents. But I don't know why, these past few years it's been getting harder and harder for me to understand what the President is thinking… Back then we had followed him out, just by ourselves, and after adventuring for so many years, I really don't know if our first promise from way back then still counts."

"Maybe… the President has already forgotten…" The woman interrupted then, her voice extremely soft, but revealing a hint of uncertainty and worry.

"Pass down my order, send some people to follow those guys from the Black Swamp Palace, and find a chance to clean them up." The man told his subordinates.

"Yes!" A guard woman at the side lowered her head and accepted the order, choosing two others and leaving the team, to follow the people from the Black Swamp Palace.

"Might as well take it as collecting some interest from God Cloud and the others," the man said softly.

************

Just as the people from Black Sky were quietly entering the city.

A hooded man dressed fully in black slowly followed the large road into the city from the other city gates.

In the midst of the hustle and bustle, he squeezed out of the crowd quietly, and walked to the side of a fountain in the city, looking up and towards the distant heart of the city.

There was a giant golden statue of the War God there, more than three hundred meters tall, sparkling under the morning light, the War God held a long spear, bent his right knee, and bent his body as though about to throw it, wearing just a golden gauze cloth around his body. There was a huge and thick beard on his face, a simple snake-ring belt around his waist.

The man in black looked at the golden War God statue, the hint of a smile appearing on his bare face under his hood.

That face had a strange metallic grey hue to it, as though he was not alive, without the slightest blush of color.

"Eternal Night Palace…"

Just then under, right underneath the War God statue, in the deepest point of the huge underground palace, up to a hundred meters deep.

A person dressed in heavy armor and sitting on the throne suddenly raised their head, a pair of white eyes slowly lighting up in the darkness of the helmet.

Ker-chak.

The figure in heavy armor slowly gripped the throne's armrest tightly.

"Hellgate… You're finally here…"

An icy woman's voice rang from underneath the armor.

******************

Inside the ruins

Garen sat cross-legged on the tip of the cliff, staring at the other two quietly, not saying a word.

Of the other two, one stood and one sat, but neither said a thing.

The three of them had all gotten what they wanted, but as temporary allies, they all had their own thoughts, even if they had no ambition, they would still be worried about whether or not there was something suspicious between the other two.

It was highly likely that the Divine God Palace Master had some plans, trying to see if he had a chance to take the things the other two had. Be it the Living Secret Technique or the Demon Mirror, neither were things that could be quickly and completely absorbed and controlled, they all required a long time to fuse and understand.

As a nest leader, if he could kill off these two right here, then the nest leaders would have two fewer powerful enemies to face in the future, after all, such peak-level fighters were not like cabbages that could simply emerge at any time.

But if he was to face the two of them alone, he believed that his condition right now might not allow it; one, on the other hand, was no problem. As a non-human, his recovery speed was extremely fast, and that period of time just now was already enough for him to recover part of his power.

Garen had naturally seen through his intentions, out of wariness, he was in no rush to attack either, so he just delayed it, he was confident that his recovery was no slower than the other's, so he was in no hurry. If at first, before he entered the ruins, he had Form Five peak-level power, then now, after learning Doublecast and spying the secrets of the Living Secret Technique, just a little, his power had gotten an even stronger boost.

Although he did not break his limits, but compared to an old-hand elite fighter like the Cthulhu King, under these circumstances where unnatural power was limited, he was already around the same level.

Faced with the threat of the Divine God Palace Master right now, he was not nervous either, just sitting cross-legged on the ground, to see what the other party had in mind.

The Cthulhu King, on the other hand, had twinkling eyes, his heart somewhat unsure, his expression seemed to be saying that he was planning to let the other two fight it out and he would take advantage of it. This was already the key reason the Divine God Palace Master was wary.

Right now, the three of them had instead formed a strange balance, and nobody dared to make the first move.

At first the Cthulhu King did not have this intention either, but after seeing the scene with the devil just now, he began to have second thoughts.

Looking at Garen, whose expression was steady, the Divine God Palace Master fell silent for a moment, but his gaze floated slightly towards the Cthulhu King's direction, evidently he could not find an opportunity to attack, so he decided to switch targets instead.

Even he, a nest leader, could read some of the Cthulhu King's intentions.

"Divine God Palace Master, this time all three of us have earned much from these ruins, but we are all seriously injured now, what's say we each go back and rest, and only consider other matters once we're healed, what do you think about that?"

Garen spoke suddenly. He had cleverly noticed that the Divine God Palace Master's thoughts had shifted to the Cthulhu King, and by speaking decisively now, he made it clear that he did not plan to meddle, and just wanted to go home and heal, so you can kill the Cthulhu King after I go, I won't interfere at all.

"Humans are all crafty and sly. I don't trust you." The Divine God Palace Master shook his head slightly. If Garen retreated intentionally and hid, waiting for both of them to hurt each other before appearing again, that would be truly dangerous.

"Then why don't you leave first, and then all of us can recover, wouldn't that be better?" Only then did Garen voice his true intentions. What he implicitly meant was, since you can't make a move, worried about this and that, why don't you just not do anything.

But the Divine God Palace Master just stayed quiet and said no more, evidently trying to stall the two of them.

Garen and the Cthulhu King exchanged a glance, and read a hint of cruelty in each other's gazes, both of them figured out that the other wanted to join forces and kill the Divine God Palace Master.

The atmosphere in the cave began to grow heavy.

Chapter 533: Scattered Power 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The atmosphere got heavier and heavier, Garen and the Cthulhu King slowly moved their position, forming a pencil-straight line with the Divine God Palace Master in the center.

The Divine God Palace Masters eyeballs turned slightly, the ink-green longbow on his back glowing with a hint of jade-green. He looked at the expressions and actions of the two in front and behind him, his heart sinking slightly.

"In that case, it might be good to end things here today."

"It’s best if the Palace Master thinks that way." The Cthulhu King chuckled, and stood aside to open up a path. The shape of his mouth was slightly strange, the red needle hidden under his tongue so he could shoot it out and attack at any moment.

The Divine God Palace Master nodded, and still did not use the long bow that remained unused, standing up slowly, his figure turning into a flash of shadow that brushed past the Cthulhu King in an instant, disappearing without a trace.

In no time at all, there was only the Cthulhu King and Garen left on the cliff.

"Together?" The Cthulhu King asked quietly.

"Of course."

Garen nodded.

Although the Divine God Palace Master left, that was just on the surface, if he was still hiding somewhere and waiting for his chance, the dumbest thing to do would be to separate now.

The two of them stuck together, out of wariness for the Divine God Palace Master who might still be hiding, but nothing really happened, following the crack they had fallen down from, every time they leaped up, they could instantly stab the stone wall with their arms and keeping themselves suspended. Then they could leverage on that and leap up again.

Jumping like that again and again, soon enough, the two of them returned to the second floor branch they had used to enter the third floor.

The branch was still covered with a pale blue mist.

The two figures leaped out of the hole on the floor, landing lightly beside the hole, one black and one red respectively.

The black figure was a calm-looking Garen, his golden hair cascading down his shoulder, his pitch-black demon eyes not showing any signs of receding, meaning his Black Water True Technique was constantly channeling at the highest level.

The red figure, on the other hand, was the Cthulhu King with his body full of wounds, his face was deathly pale, and he panted heavily.

"Looks like after going back this time, I’ll need to properly rest and recover for a while."

"Phiros is dead, the situation is extremely unstable now, do you have time to relax?" Garen raised his brow slightly. Now he could no longer compare the events to the original path, he had already turned history utterly upside down, everything had become a mess.

Hellgate did sustain some considerable injuries after defeating Phiros, but after the Daniela War of Destinies, Ender actually did not move at all, so they evidently had some other plan.

The Enderian King(1) and Phiros were two complete opposites, she was mad and extremely active, and most of all, she would not obey any pre-set rules, plus she was herself a peak-level totem user. Compared to Phiros, she had become famous several hundred years ago, and was a long-known peak-level fighter among the previous generation, who knows how powerful her home base was.

This would be yet another world-ending clash.

"Unfortunately… If Phiros had been willing to join forces with me, there’s no way he would have ended up like that." The Cthulhu King shook his head, lamenting.

Garen did not say anything, he just watched the tracks left by the Divine God Palace Master around the area carefully.

The Cthulhu King looked at him.

"This time, both of us reaped a lot of rewards, may I know what plans Palace Master Garen has from here on out?"

"Plans? Don’t you know perfectly well what I want to do?" Garen was too lazy to beat around the bush with him, he was going to lose control of the Living Secret Technique’s side effects. He moved his feet, and instantly became a shadow rushing down the way he had come.

The Cthulhu King cackled, accepting and absorbing two Living Secret Technique Seeds at once, especially the one that he had exchanged with Garen, was not that easy a matter. But the two of them had made a deal and exchanged, neither of them had any intention of regretting it.

Evidently, Garen had also gotten some benefits from that Living Secret Technique.

Garen in front, and the Cthulhu King behind, both of them concentrated on rushing back, neither of them speaking.

Right now, the green and black-red threads inside Garen’s body were interweaving and tangling, darting in and around his body like countless long and thin worms, causing him unbearable agony. Thankfully, his roots were in the Secret Technique World’s peak-level Black Water True Technique, so it was slowly forming a buffer between the two Living Secret Techniques, so that the two conflicts would not be too sharp, and giving him some time to breathe.

The first Living Secret Technique he had gotten was a Frost-type. And the second looked like it would be a Fire-type, but it was actually a Metal-type, the fire devil representing the melting and forging of metal, only the black-red long sword that appeared at the end was the true Seed, the two Living Secret Technique Seeds were tangled up and clashing inside Garen’s body, forming two balls, one green and one black, both spinning at high speeds. The center of the spinning was the core formed from his Black Water True Technique blood qi and the fusion power, that Garen had trained for a long time. But right now, the Black Water True Technique was being burned away quickly, every second he stayed here would cost him another portion of the Black Water True Technique’s fusion power.

Garen’s heart grew more anxious, and he began to run even faster.

Boom!

The stone door to the ruins was broken through explosively, and a black shadow shot out, flying into the dense forest, landing on a small piece of empty land.

There was a black eagle-drawn carriage waiting on the empty land, and a bonfire alit beside the carriage, with Demon Phoenix and Phantom reading their books beside the fire, when they heard the noises, the two of them stood up in unison, turning around to see Garen appear on top of the carriage.

"Palace Master…"

"Leave here at once!" Garen tossed the words at them, darted into the carriage, sat down cross-legged, and fell into a state of self-meditation. There was a slight sheen of sweat on his forehead, as he resisted that immense pain.

Demon Phoenix and Phantom hurriedly put out the bonfire, got onto the carriage, and yanked hard at the ropes.

The black eagle that had been resting instantly flapped its wings and flew up, the huge pulling forcing jerking the whole carriage hard, and then it seemed to suddenly grow lighter, rising into the air.

The Demon Cloud Spirit Light that Garen had asked Demon Phoenix to prepare also did not come to much use this time, that thing was to prevent the other two from ganging up on him, the Demon Cloud Spirit Light was best at turning others’ power into his own. It was the most effective in group battles.

As for peak-level power, with the Form Five Demon Phoenix around, added with Garen’s current recovery power, even if he did not make a move, there would still be poisonous and extremely corrosive Spirit Light aura emitted.

Because of the merging with his aura, his Spirit Light was now a deadly weapon on its own, merged with the Demon Cloud Spirit Light, it had just nicely formed a powerful ‘kill - convert - kill again’ mode.

Luckily, neither of the other two set down other traps, if Garen was not so affected by the Living Secret Technique side effects, perhaps this time he would have a chance instead to kill the other two, but unfortunately, he could barely protect himself right now.

The black carriage carved out a line through the high noon air at rapid speeds, and disappeared into the sky in no time.

On the other end of the sky, a blood-red mask appeared slowly, and then disappeared rapidly, while the Cthulhu King’s figure also vanished at the same time.

After both of them disappeared completely, outside the door to the ruins, the Divine God Palace Master’s figure slowly materialized from the air, as though he had always been invisible from the start, and the other two had not noticed at all.

Looking at the direction the two of them had left in, he touched the end of the longbow sticking out from behind his waist, a flash of hesitation in his eyes, but after a second, he still relaxed his fingers, turned around, and walked towards the other end of the forest.

*******************

Inside the black eagle carriage

Garen closed his eyes tightly, biting his lower lip hard, strands of blood dripping down his chin, but he was totally unaware of it.

Strands of black air emanated from the bottom of his body, soundlessly, creating a thin layer of ice on the wooden floor.

He was using his heart and spirit to match the life forces of the two Living Secret Techniques, with the Black Water True Technique as a buffer that was constantly being absorbed and fused by the two Living Secret Techniques, absorbing the parts of the secret technique memories and wills that suited him, and then forming a larger, stronger clash.

The Black Water True Technique’s core grew smaller and smaller, weaker and weaker, if it went on like this, by the time the core had been utterly absorbed, all of Garen’s True Technique roots would be completely gone, becoming the nutrients for the clash between the two types of Living Secret Techniques. After the conflict leveled up, there would be no more buffer in between, and just one clash would be enough to make him instantly explode, with no chance of survival.

Garen tried his best to slow down the expenditure of his Black Water True Technique, looking for a proper rate between the buffer and absorbing speeds.

"No! If I go on like this, I’ll be sucked dry by the Living Secret Techniques sooner or later!" His thoughts were whirring quickly now. He spent so much effort for so long to reach this level, if he was forced all the way back to the start just for this one accident, it would not match his aim for coming here to these ruins.

Reaching out his hand, he opened up his palm, his palm and fingers emitting tiny whiffs of black smoke that seemed to come alive, destroying and absorbing all of the other impurities and traces on his body, fusing away the useful ones and forcing out the useless ones.

He took the Original Eye out from the War Chain on his arm, and fused in the black smoke. Those black flowers with the frost spirit power were also fused and absorbed into the black smoke, forming nutrients to temporarily slow down the two Living Secret Techniques.

Only when absorbing nutrients will these two Seeds slow down their number of clashes, so although he knew this was barely helping and could make things worse, Garen had no choice but to do it. It was better than the very foundations of his Black Water True Technique being destroyed in front of his eyes.

After the Original Eye was pulled inside, the two seeds suddenly paused abruptly, splitting into half each, and greatly reducing the speed of the clashes, after the black flowers were added in, it just slowed the spinning speed of the Frost Seed.

This way, the endgame of being torn apart and exploding to death within possibly a day was extended to at least one week.

These two Secret Technique Seeds were like greedy beasts, continuously absorbing the structures and sources of the same type that they did not have, trying their best to improve and perfect themselves, and as they perfected themselves, they would also release spirit energy to improve their true bodies, if there was just one type, it would just nicely improve Garen’s body, and may even reach the next level. But if there were two types, that would be bad. The two spirit energies clashed with each other, you want to change it this way, he wants to change it that way, and neither giving way. In the end the one being pulled apart painfully in the center was Garen himself.

He knew that he had been careless this time, he did not think that the Living Secret Techniques would be such dominating things, and they had their own instincts as well. But before actually experiencing it, nobody would know that the fusion of two Living Secret Techniques would create such a terrifying clash and conflict.

"It’s not like I really have no way…" Garen’s eyes twinkled, "If I completely ground down both secret techniques, and let the places where they clash round out completely, so that they’re not so sharp, and find the similarities between them, the two Living Secret Techniques can become one. All the power can be converted into mine. Only then will I truly obtain the legacy information for the Living Secret Techniques."

Right now, because of the secret technique resistance, he had practically yet to truly obtain the ways to train and the secret technique information from the Secret Technique Seeds.

"In that case, the required conditions are…" His mind spun rapidly, going through all the massive amounts of knowledge he had accumulated from before, one by one, each of the different systems trying to create models, failing and collapsing each time, then attempting to build them up again from scratch.

Translator’s Notes:

Yep, it seems to be a female ‘King’.

Chapter 534: Scattered Power 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Seconds ticked by, then minutes.

The Black Water True Technique was being worn down constantly, while the Nine-Headed Hydra’s talent and ability, Swallowed Lives, had been completely destroyed and broken down at this point. It was eliminated immediately as an impurity by both of the Secret Technique Seeds, meaning that Garen would lose his Swallowed Lives ability completely.

All this while, he had killed innumerable enemies and overcome countless obstacles with this ability. But now, he could only stop and stare while it rapidly disappeared into black smoke following the decline of the Black Water True Technique.

However, this was only the beginning, as the Nine-Headed Hydra’s tremendous recovery abilities were beginning to decompose and dissipate slowly as well.

Garen knew that if he did not find a solution soon, his other abilities such as Dragon’s Roar, Poison Mist Corrosion, and Dragon Demon parasitism would be torn apart before decomposing one by one.

The Black Water True Technique had fused with Garen’s own Core Totem and the Nine-Headed Hydra’s genes, but once it decomposed fully, other than losing his Dragon’s Heart, he would also be degraded to the level of a basic Totem User, one who lacked even a Totem.

Garen came up with various solutions and adjusted operation models but ended up destroying one after another, despite using every single one of his twelve intelligence attribute points. If he became a regular Totem User again, it would be impossible for him to create models or develop his logic skills this quickly, even if he happened to be the highest leveled Totem master.

Garen’s powerful neurons made it possible for him to use up to two techniques at once, allowing him to attempt to establish two different models simultaneously, instantly increasing his speed by twofold.

After a seemingly endless period of time, the flying carriage jerked suddenly, as if it had landed.

Garen opened his bloodshot eyes, before getting up to open the curtains.

"Welcome, Palace Master!!"

In the middle of Black Swamp Palace’s plaza, more than a hundred inner palace guards and administrators formed two lines to welcome Garen. Both Skyharp and Blizzard walked towards him, but when they saw him alight from the carriage, their expressions were overcome with shock. They stopped in their tracks. Skyharp even took two steps backward.

Garen’s entire body was currently shrouded in pitch black smoke that swirled around him, binding him terrifyingly like black string. Below his feet, layers of black ice formed on the ground instantly on the plaza’s white stone floor, wherever he stepped.

While looking at both of their frightened and uncertain faces, Garen chose to skip his explanation, before a raspy noise escaped him.

"Take me to the Nine Snakes System!"

"I’ll go inform the Technique Hall!" When Blizzard noticed the severity of the situation, he instantly turned himself into snow before dispersing throughout the ground.

Skyharp hurriedly removed multiple bottles of fiery red medicine, before applying them directly on Garen’s body.

Shh!

When the black smoke and red medicine came into contact, puffs of white gas formed there.

"I can only temporarily stop your poisons from spreading further," said Skyharp truthfully.

"I know." Garen took long strides towards the inner palace, walking directly towards the core of the Nine Snakes System’s controls in the side hall.

The black smoke was actually poisonous mist formed by the scattering of the Black Water True Technique, that had the potential to injure innocent lives in a moment of carelessness. Skyharp noticed this, and took the necessary measures to prevent it.

Demon Phoenix and Phantom alighted the carriage with gloomy faces, staggering as they got down. It was evident that they had been poisoned slightly. Skyharp rushed over to administer the antidote to both of them.

Meanwhile, the black hawks that pulled the carriage earlier now screeched their final breaths, collapsed on the ground, before melting into puddles of black water slowly.

Garen walked towards the core of the Nine Snakes, leaving heavy black smoke footprints on the ground with every step he took, all the while more smoke dissipated out of his body like shadowy tentacles.

The scattering of the Black Water True Technique caused incomprehensible pain throughout his whole body, as if numerous saws were tearing through his flesh.

Although Garen was strong-willed, the pain made it impossible for him to walk properly. Every step he took was difficult and sluggish, and he began to stumble as well, as if incredibly heavy chains were dragging him from behind.

Some of the decorative plants and flowers around him wilted and turned black instantly when he walked past, before melting into puddles of black water.

Thin layers of black ice formed on the surfaces of the stone furniture. Meanwhile, the maids and guards that passed by were unable to avoid him in time froze into black ice sculptures. Some even remained in their bowing positions.

Garen could faintly hear the ear-piercing, terrified screams that echoed throughout the palace endlessly, and the noise of frantic stomping, as well as the shattering of expensive porcelain.

Once he had walked into the side hall where the Nine Snakes' controls were located, he noticed that all of the Elders that were in charge during his absence had gathered there as well.

The image of the Nine Snakes had solidified and appeared long ago, and was now bowing in front of Garen.

Upon seeing Garen’s condition, grave expressions appeared on the faces of the Elders from the Seven Night Tower and the Island Masters.

However, Master Calingan of the Technique Hall became extremely anxious.

"You’re scattering?!" He recognized Garen’s condition at once.

The remaining Elders were currently in shock. Garen was the core of Black Swamp Palace, but during his absence, the effects of his scattering had grown severe. Everyone merely exchanged glances, unable to think of anything to say.

"You were able to tell…" Garen could barely force a smile. He had already combined the knowledge systems of all three worlds to find a barely usable solution. "Nine Snakes, Master Calingan, I need an environment with sufficient pressure, water, and low temperatures. Please hurry!"

Since Nine Snakes had collected all of the purchasable maps in the world, while Master Calingan was a high leveled Totem master, perhaps they would have a solution.

"The current situation requires us to delay the scattering speed immediately!" As a fellow technician, Skyharp had the highest authority to speak.

"Alert the outside immediately! Glittering Water possesses certain buffering functions! Bring the closest reserves now! Hurry!!" Master Calingan found a delaying method instantly.

"I have searched for the best locations." The image of the Nine Snakes made a noise at once. "These three locations can be consulted. Number one: The Mesir Valley draught. The strong wind pressure there fulfills the conditions that require high pressures, and the fierce winds will remove excess heat while producing extremely low temperatures. There is also a little lake within the valley, fulfilling the criteria of water."

"Number two: The depths of the North Sea. A freezing environment with deep waters, low pressures and temperatures, as well as a water source are all present."

"Number three: The Mola Snow Caves. One of the Nest Leader’s hideouts in the northern area where an icy pond with flowing water is located. The icy water there is a hundred times denser than mercury. Therefore, immersing oneself into its depths will also fulfill the above criteria."

Garen muttered to himself for a moment, while his brain searched for the best location quickly.

"To the North Sea!"

The entire Black Swamp Palace was thrown into a frantic state. Under the petrified attention of numerous guards and maids, the Elders and Demon Phoenix carried Garen into the Flying Hawk Carriage carefully, before it flew towards the North Sea.

All of the forces inside the Black Swamp Palace stopped their activities at once, postponed their plans, and suppressed their powers while waiting for the news.

Meanwhile, two out of the three remaining Gargantuans in the Kingdom had already left for the Eternal Night Palace in Ender to get in on the action.

Only the Princess’s forces had remained to form an active alliance with Rainbow Domain, while a large black minaret was being built in her own mountain peak regions for unknown reasons.

Black Swamp Palace was never interested in their power struggle or various plots. Therefore, the other forces were uninterested in their current actions as well.

From their perspectives, Garen was merely an individual who was attempting to achieve peak levels, and as long as they did not disturb him, he would not be a threat to them at all.

So Garen left Black Swamp Palace silently, leaving the Ultimate Protection, before flying towards the direction of the polar circles of the North Sea.

****************

A few days later…

The depths of the North Sea.

A black Flying Hawk Carriage speeded over from afar, before hovering over the surface of the sea slowly.

Suddenly, a black shadow leaped out of the carriage gently, splashing into the turbulent blue waves like an arrow.

Crash!

White sea spray splashed up from the icy seawater, before returning to a calm state immediately afterward.

A sea of complete blue covered the surroundings.

Garen fell into the sea, before rolling around, and looking upwards at the surface. He noticed the bubbles that floated around his body like strings of transparent pearls.

His eyes, ears, nose, and mouth were filled with icy seawater, making him feel extremely suffocated.

Rays of white light permeated the the surface of the sea and into the depths below, giving the illusion that there were multiple layers within the blue sea.

Black smoke drifted out of Garen’s body. He looked up at the light above his head, before slowly sinking into the murky depths of the sea

The light drifted further away, before everything grew dimmer.

His surroundings became colder and darker.

Garen opened his eyes wider to look at the single dot of light above his head. He did not know how much time he had spent sinking.

The black smoke mixed with the surrounding seawater, while a school of whitebait swam past him. However, after swimming for a short while, all of the fish turned over and floated, belly up, all signs of life snuffed out of them.

Below him was an endless abyss. Garen flipped over and moved his arm gently, quickening his dive towards the depths of the pitch black sea.

Gradually, his surroundings soon turned to darkness, devoid any light.

Garen could now feel that the scattering effect had slowed down slightly. The heavy underwater pressures had replaced the Black Water True Technique, becoming nutrients for the Metal Secret Techniques, while the extremely low temperatures had become the corresponding nutrients for the Ice Secret Techniques, decreasing their speeds of decomposing the Black Water True Technique.

However, this decomposition had not stopped fully, and Garen did not hesitate before diving deeper.

Suddenly, a transparent, gigantic disc-shaped jellyfish swam over from afar. The jellyfish emitted dark blue light throughout its whole body, resembling a light bulb that could be seen clearly in the dark. When the jellyfish noticed Garen diving towards itself, it positioned its skinny tentacles and prepared to sting him. Its body froze suddenly, its light dimmed and shut down completely, before it melted into an ink-like poison that was finally dispersed by the water.

The current depths of the waters were unknown, but the high pressures of the surroundings made it exhausting for even Garen. A regular Totem User that was Form 4 or below would implode completely within moments of entering this place.

Although Totem Light could filter out the oxygen in seawater, it could not withstand these terrifying underwater pressures.

This was the largest trench in the depths of the icy North Sea. Garen could not see what lay at the bottom of the sea, as it was completely dark.

He fumbled around the trench and furiously dug a large cavern beside an upright precipice, before hiding himself inside.

While Garen sat cross-legged inside the cavern, he noticed that the pressure had alleviated the effects of the scattering greatly. Unfortunately, his Black Water True Technique was left with its last parasitic Dragon Demon, and the last thing that was decomposing was his strongest core ability, Nine-Life!

Chapter 535: Abyss 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The absence of the Nine-Life Talent meant that Garen would lose his greatest advantage against the other peak individuals. Therefore, he had to find a method to cure the after-effects of both his Living Secret Techniques while he remained in this delayed decomposition environment.

Garen closed his eyes, seemingly free of worry about any trouble breathing he might encounter. This vitality underwent the modifications of the Nine-Headed Hydra’s genes, he gained a Totem Light type ability entering Form 5. Absorbing oxygen from seawater was a simple skill he had acquired, as it was one of the basic abilities of Totem Light.

It happened the moment he shut his eyes.

Thick black mist rose from his body quickly, dispersing in all four directions.

While Garen remained as the center, the surrounding water within a hundred mile radius gradually slowed in its flow, before appearing to almost solidify. The deep sea creatures around him escape by swimming towards the further parts of the sea.

At this moment, the sound of a resonance signal escaped from Garen’s body, transmitting itself to the flying carriage that was hovering above the surface of the sea.

Almost instantly, more than ten giant, dark blue Sea Hawks flew over the sky. The white-clothed Totem Users in who rode on the backs of these giant birds had dignified airs about them.

They were clad in white fur coats, and wore the symbol of the number seven in blue. Blizzard, Angel of the Night, and Spellcaster were among them.

"Courteous Tower Lords of the Seven Night Towers, I apologize for the trouble," Ivycius’s voice could be heard from the black carriage.

"As collaborators, we would never dream of neglecting such a simple task, much less a request from the Palace Master," answered the Grand Tower Lord politely. He was a feeble old man with a white beard that covered his whole face. "Food and drinks will be sent daily, as building a continuous passageway will take a considerable amount of time."

"That’s fine," replied Ivycius. "We must request for the dwellings to be built sooner, so that Skyharp and myself will have a convenient place to stay."

"Of course," replied the Grand Tower Lord respectfully.

He had felt a terrifying force the moment the black carriage arrived in the north. This force had greatly exceeded the powerful strength of his own Precious Heirloom, therefore he did not dare to remain idle, and instead gathered all of the other Tower Lords to welcome the visitors immediately.

He could only breathe a sigh of relief after witnessing Palace Master Garen sink into the depths of the sea, meaning that he had really come here just to retreat.

Among the people that arrived, he noticed that Ivycius, and another Elder called Phantom, were also first-rate professionals of the same level as himself, while Ivycius’s aura showed signs that he would break through any minute. Meanwhile, the other one, Demon Phoenix was impenetrable, meaning that facing her was like encountering an endless abyss. It was strange for such a powerful individual to merely be one of Palace Master Garen’s subordinates.

After witnessing this scene, the Grand Tower Lord thought of the good relationship between the Seven Night Tower and Black Swamp Palace, and his heart ignited with a fiery passion.

"From today onwards, these waters will be designated as Black Swamp Palace’s marine territory, and it will be our responsibility to provide the manpower to guard this place," said the Grand Tower Lord earnestly.

"That will be unnecessary. Palace Master only requires utmost secrecy. He does not need people to guard this place as both of us will be sufficient," said Ivycius in a lowered voice.

"Utmost secrecy, you say?" the Grand Tower Lord nodded certainly.

Suddenly, shocked faces appeared throughout the crowd as they lowered their heads to peer into the sea.

They could see that the previously dark blue seawater was now tinged black. Choppy waves crashed about the turbulent water, while the amount of crushed ice within the sea increased.

Minor changes had appeared throughout the sea.

The Grand Tower Lord’s expression changed slightly, as his fingers frantically drew gestures in the air. Instantly, a ray of white light shot out of his sleeve, but disappeared in flash.

The Grand Tower Lord closed his eyes and concentrated, attempting to detect something.

Moments later, he opened his eyes again, his face overcome with a grave expression.

"These changes have appeared throughout the entire hundred mile expanse of the sea!"

"It’s Palace Master!" said Demon Phoenix suddenly. "I could feel his breath!"

The three members of Black Swamp Palace exchanged glances but remained silent, merely observing the incomprehensible changes that were occurring below them.

However, the members of Seven Night Tower were overwhelmed with shock. If Garen managed to cause these extreme changes despite being submerged in an abyss over ten thousand miles deep, they would have to reevaluate Black Swamp Palace’s strength again.

This was not something within the reach of a regular Form 4!

Below the crowd, within a hundred mile range of the sea, the seawater started turning dark and cold. Dead fish and struggling sea creatures floated up on certain parts of the water. Colorless poisons spread across the expanse of water, before the entire hundred mile stretch of the sea was completely polluted, into an extremely terrifying and toxic no-entry zone.

Garen, who was currently located below the depths of the sea, was covered from head to toe in streams of green and red water. A thin layer of ice spread around him slowly while he remained in the center.

He raised his head and looked at the darkness above him, before closing his eyes slowly and sinking to the bottom with all his might.

*********************

Many months later…

Boom!

Thunderous noises echoed from the rolling black clouds.

Below the black clouds were seemingly endless red plains. Meanwhile, Nest Monsters had gathered there in large herds, resembling a huge wave.

Giant White Bats and Red Unihorn Lizards flew around in the sky like flying insects. At a glance, they looked like clusters of little red and white dots.

On the side of a dark red cliff where countless Nest Monsters were camping stood three silent figures, looking at the terrifying Nest Monster army in front of them.

A slender male figure in a green cloak stood in front, shielding himself so that only his eyes were exposed. He carried a dark green longbow on his back and wore a green hood on his head, giving off an indescribable sense of mystery and quietness.

The other two figures behind him were also clad in long grey robes, making it difficult to observe their bodies.

Dark clouds rolled through the sky, before a round hole appeared above the heads of the three people. A ray of white light shot out of the hole and formed a white pillar of light, descending upon the green cloaked man’s body.

He stretched his hands out before, a green, dark, exquisite longbow appeared in them instantly. It was the same bow that he had been carrying on his back earlier.

There was a spherical object at the center of the longbow that was constantly rotating.

After two crisp clapping noises, two blood-red wheels aimed at each other appeared on both sides of the bow. Meanwhile, a small, green snake slowly appeared on the body of the bow and slithered around silently, before coiling around. Finally, it gradually stiffened in place, before turning into a snake-like embossment.

The white light grew brighter, and along with it the faint light that reflected off the bow became clearer.

The man in the green cloak held the bow and arrow with both hands tightly, before raising it upwards with a quick motion.

Boom!!!

Numerous Nest Monsters exploded in an instant, letting out angry howls.

The Bats and Salamanders in the sky poked their necks out and screeched, while the black Mammoths, Four-Winged Giant Pythons and the other strange and powerful creatures howled in anger, as if they were about to unleash all their strength at once.

"This is a war of vengeance!" A cold male voice echoed from the green cloak.

*******************

Time flew by, as more than a year had already passed since Garen entered the depths of the North Sea.

The world fell into a surprising state of calmness.

Obscuro Society had gathered all of their forces in Ender, but since Hellgate did not make the first move, Ender’s Eternal Night Palace seemed like a powerful moat that was obstructing all of Obscuro Society’s Marshalls.

Strangely enough, Hellgate had suddenly disappeared for seemingly unknown reasons right in front of everyone.

The World's Totem King Festival in Ender had gone on for more than a year, and after the selections from the first match were decided, the strongest competitors were about to enter the semifinals.

Within the span of a year, eighteen competitors were finally selected for the semifinals, and each of them were peak Totem Users from across the land. Now, they were about to enter the Eternal Night Palace for the final matches.

Ender was simmering from within. The relationship between the local aristocracy, the army generals, the exterior forces and Obscuro Society were inexplicably complex and entangled.

Simultaneously, something else was happening on the vast red plains on the other side of the Vicra Mountains, in the northwestern part of Ender.

Obscuro Society’s numerous Empowered armies were engaged in a frenzied battle with the Nest Monsters. The Nest Leaders’ territory was a restricted area for humans, but Obscuro Society’s Silver Totems had invaded their Core areas.

Dark red, rotting corpses and skeletons could be seen everywhere, dyeing the area in a deeper shade of mahogany, while black smoke incessantly wafted out of certain places. It came from the war weapon that the Nest Leaders’ had built, the Rotting Well. This weapon was able to cause a continuous rotting effect to the armors of its enemies throughout a range of many kilometers.

The Rotting Wells resembled eyes that were flashing, with green light in the ground, but once its source was smashed open and the contents of its core flowed out, some of it remained dark and indistinguishable, while the rest of it gathered into winding, glowing green streams.

Monster corpses and Silver Totem skeletons were piled together, while flies and other flying insects buzzed around them. Flesh-eating insects had crawled into some of the corpses as well.

In the center of the red plains, where everything remained silent, a bright red pool was in the middle of the corpses, while the skeletons of two giant dragons formed a ring around the pool of blood.

Divine God Palace Master sat cross-legged beside the blood pool. He wore a black eye patch over one of his eyes, while his body was still covered in the same green cloak, except that it was now torn, with holes and blood stains all over.

Some of the blood inside the pool gathered slowly and formed a bloodied human figure. The human figure stood opposite Divine God Palace Master, while the corners of its mouth cracked suddenly, exposing a strange smile.

"It is almost time." The volume of its voice fluctuated like a communication device with strong signal interferences.

"That’s right."

Divine God Palace Master remained silent before closing his eyes slowly.

"You sacrificed millions of soldiers this year just to temporarily obstruct my return to the inner world, but for what?" asked the bloodied human figure in a low voice. "The flesh of two Time Dragons in exchange for the Original Heirloom to return as the core of the bow, and a pool of the blood of millions of soldiers… How generous…"

Divine God Palace Master did not reply, choosing to remain silent for a moment.

"You will die by my hand."

He stood up and turned around, before walking far away, without the slightest hint of nostalgia.

Chapter 536: Abyss 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He knew that this place would not be able to withstand one of the strongest Totem Users anymore. However, his continuous acts of vengeance caused serious losses towards Obscuro Society. Within the span of a year, most of Obscuro Society’s Silver Totems had destroyed the blood pool in order to save Hellgate. They charged forward without caring about their own safety..

Both sides suffered numerous casualties during the battle with the Nest Leaders, forming the red plains and sea of countless corpses.

The absence of proper leadership resulted in the stalling of their forces by the Eternal Night Palace, causing Obscuro Society to suffer extremely difficult setbacks. Without powerful battle forces on either side, the Nest Leaders were able to obtain great advantages.

This was the first step of the complicated plan that Divine God Palace Master had drafted out after he had obtained sufficient Living Secret Techniques.

The King of Ender cooperated and tempted him personally, hastening the creation of the blood pool. After Hellgate had entered the inner world, he could control and interfere with his exit and entry points freely. However, these complicated plans involved too many people.

They would only be able to obstruct Hellgate in the inner world, making it impossible for him to return temporarily. Meanwhile, it would only last for a year.

An outcome like this…

****************

Kovitan Kingdom

This place had changed completely after a year.

While Garen sealed himself at the bottom of the sea, Ivycius and Skyharp guarded the area, leaving the tasks of the Black Swamp Palace to be handled and discussed by the Elders, allowing Demon Phoenix and the other Elders that had just entered the palace to pass their time comfortably.

The White Knight tribesman and princess that Garen had saved in the field formed a new force after entering Black Swamp Palace. The leader of the White Knights from the White Wind Tribe progressed quickly, and obtained the necessary Appraisal to practice the Black Water True Technique. Once he had coordinated and refined it to his Secret Technique, his powers broke through to Form 4 suddenly, leading him to form the White Knights of the Wind that were unwaveringly loyal to Garen. They were in stark contrast in comparison to the Black Knights of the Four Directions Sky Warriors. Once they had obtained power, their initial plan was to return to their village for vengeance. Unfortunately, their enemies had left their original locations for good and were nowhere to be seen.

Demon Phoenix and the others spent their days enjoying themselves in a comfortable environment that most people could only dream of experiencing. Occasionally, they would travel to the North Sea to check on Garen’s condition. After Garen took them out of their rural homes, they became inseparable from the new dazzling world that they had stepped into. However, their reveration for him remained deeply rooted in their hearts. They would never dare to have other intentions even if they were enticed by others.

Within Black Swamp Palace, only Demon Phoenix and a few others were the clearest about the exact details surrounding Garen’s existence. During the past year, she had restored herself to middle-level Form 5 completely. However, an exhausted feeling still lingered whenever she faced Garen.

While Black Swamp Palace held their troops back and recuperated, the other forces in the Kingdom, including the other three Gargantuans, gathered crowds of Totem Users and civilians that were seeking refuge, before beginning to build two cities outside the protection areas.

The Princess’ constructions were finally revealed. They were called ‘Dawn Towers’, and the five towers that she had built within her domain were able to gather Totem Powers and shoot them across distances of more than a thousand meters. They also possessed the ability to amplify powers, allowing the Totem Users within her domain to experience power upgrades of up to ten percent.

This was a frightening enhancement. Moreover, it also meant that the Princess had first-rate master Totem Forgers among her subordinates. She would definitely have Grand Duke Benoc’s support behind her as well.

Meanwhile, Grand Duke Cody concentrated all of his efforts in the new city, and gathered a large group of regular Forgers to build a superweapon called the Kars Cannon outside the city walls.

This weapon used the Totem Light of fifty Totem Users to cause terrifying explosions within seconds. It was rumored to be the invention of a young prodigy Forger that had fled to Kovitan, thus giving the cannon its name.

On the other hand, internal disputes of interest occurred after the heads of the guild alliances took in Totem Users from the outside, causing numerous large-scale forces to fall apart during the war. This led to changes in the political regime, causing everyone to become weaker in the end, while the Four Gargantuans were also threatened to be removed from their seats.

Through Demon Phoenix, Garen was not completely cut off from the outside world during this period. Instead, he knew the changes and developments of the current situation clearly.

As for the other forces in the Kingdom, Garen was unconcerned about them. This information only reached him because of the close distance between them and Black Swamp Palace. Although the palace did not participate in their affairs and remained detached, they were still aware of certain happenings.

In comparison to the incidents that were ongoing in Daniela, everything else was unimportant. Out of the countless messages and news that he had received, the thing that shocked him most was not the news of Phiroth’s death in battle. Instead, it came from the largest civilian assembly fort in the world that had been built in Daniela — Heart of Life.

A large-scale, widespread epidemic had appeared within the Heart of Life, and before the news reached him, more than a hundred thousand people had already died from being infected there! In the beginning, the spread of this epidemic was quarantined within the fort, but once it reached this stage, they were unable to suppress it anymore, causing the situation to reach an extremely dangerous degree.

The scariest part of this epidemic was not its hundred percent mortality rate, but the fact that it would turn the dead into zombie-like monsters. These monsters hunted the living as food and roamed about. Moreover, they would still be able to live for a few days even if their heads or hearts were destroyed fully.

This made Garen faintly think of the living corpses that he had encountered the first time he entered the mysterious Ghost City. The surroundings of the capital of that little country were filled with the strange zombies that were described earlier.

Vaguely, he could feel that it was highly likely that this epidemic was connected to Ghost City.

The occurrences in Ghost City were caused by the black copper phenomena, of which the root cause was black copper, and the source of the black copper phenomena was very likely to be Hellgate.

Since the situation had reached this degree, it had left the original timeline completely.

Hellgate had disappeared temporarily, and another person had similarly disappeared without any news was Divine God Palace Master.

The Three Territories had formed a temporary alliance, cooperating as one major force. The other domains were thriving prosperously, becoming the largest, ideal, living stronghold outside Ender and the Ultimate Protection area.

****************

A pale blue light twinkled at the bottom of the pitch-black sea, faintly illuminating the surrounding waters beneath the deep sea.

Within the bottomless ocean abyss, a cluster of gigantic, hundred meter tall icicles were erected in the large marine trench. The sharp icicles stood upright like an array of long transparent spears that were faintly stained black.

In the middle of everything, within a sharp large icicle that was over ten meters thick, was the source of the twinkling pale blue light.

In front of the icicles was a stretch of icy ground.

As it was situated in the opening between two marine trenches, gallons of seawater had frozen into ice because of the extremely low temperatures, while the bottoms of the marine trenches were completely filled with ice, forming a gigantic ice mountain that filled the marine trenches at the bottom of the abyss.

The ice mountain was translucent and slightly black, and behind the pale blue light in the center, situated within a large icicle, was a slender golden-haired man that had been frozen within the ice. The man was unmoving, while both of his eyes were slightly shut as if he were in deep sleep. However, it also seemed as if his gaze was fixated on something in front of him.

Meanwhile, a handsome man with a head full of long white hair sat cross-legged on the icy floor in front of the icicle. He wore a long white robe with a silver-black belt tied around his waist while a long white sword lay flat on his knees.

"How does it feel to break through?" An empty-sounding male voice reverberated throughout the layer of ice, as if he were speaking in a large hall, carrying echoes that sounded unconventionally graceful.

Ivycius grasped the hilt of the sword on his knees gently, shaking his head slightly.

"If I hadn’t guarded you here personally and observed the effects and changes of your Secret Techniques towards your surroundings, I would not have entered Form 5 so quickly. The originally estimated time, is still insufficient."

"Only a high-leveled prodigy like yourself would be able to see patterns from the traces of these Secret Technique changes," said Garen casually from within the icicle.

Ivycius declined to comment. During this time, after he married Skyharp, he had spent all of his time guarding this underwater abyss while the professionals of Black Swamp Palace and Seven Night Tower built a simple underwater residence here.

But before they could add the finishing touches to the place, the construction workers were forced to retreat, being unable to withstand the frightening cold air that Garen released increasingly every day.

Ivycius, Skyharp, and Garen managed to connect with each other on a deeper level through their interactions during this time.

Ivycius was a person who abided to his own principles closely. He chose to stay behind and guard Garen, and did not give up on him despite the ending of the Dragon Demon’s bindings. He did not think of the Demon Dragon’s bindings as any form of restriction at all.

In reality, Garen had never imposed any forceful commands on him, allowing both of them to have a normal friendly relationship with each other. For both of them, the presence or absence of the Dragon Demon’s bindings made no difference.

"There have been signs of activity in the Heart of Life again, while Ender is entering the finals. How is your situation here?" asked Ivycius in a low voice.

"Still considerably smooth." Garen did not explain it in detail.

Both of them fell into silence. Within the period of a day, silence was their most commonly used mode of connection, as both of them preferred to enter their own worlds.

Garen suppressed his thoughts, before placing them back within his Living Secret Techniques.

Two of his Secret Techniques had mostly fused already, while the Black Water True Technique had reached its final scattering phase. The forced tearing of two of his main Living Secret Techniques caused his will and fusion powers to be absorbed as nutrients, leaving nothing but the last bits of his Nine-Life Talent.

As the Nine-Life Talent was the core strength of the Nine-Headed Hydra, the fact that the extremely delayed speeds were able to support it for such a long time was already a very rare occurrence. But at this point, they were unable to evade the complete decomposition forever.

Meanwhile, the two Living Secret Technique seeds within his body had absorbed many nutrients from the outside after a long period of time, allowing them to reach extremely desirable states.

After a long period of bodily operation fusions, Garen’s body had fully adapted to the Living Secret Technique’s powerful activities. As the fusion between the two Secret Techniques deepened, the transformations within Garen’s body became more integrated as well, lessening the conflicts.

"Soon… Soon… Only a little while longer before I get to the essence of the mysteries of the Living Secret Technique…"

As of now, he had yet to truly receive the Legacy of the Living Secret Technique. One of the reasons was due to the conflict between both of his Secret Techniques. The most troublesome part was that the true Secret Technique practice message would only be transmitted after he had finished the transformation completely.

The Living Secret Techniques would be able to exceed their limits after coming to fruition, allowing him to achieve peak levels. This was the general consensus among strong, peak individuals.

The fusion of two Secret Techniques would not necessarily bring positive changes. However, they were not too undesirable from his current perspective. Although he had lost many parts that conflicted with one another, the seedlings that were preserved continued to possess the presence of extremely terrifying air ripples.

Once he received the Legacy, the presence of the Black Water True Technique and the large quantities of Living Secret Techniques that he had accumulated recently would definitely allow Garen to achieve a higher level within a short span of time. After all, he had already obtained an extremely high Secret Technique state.

Chapter 537: Abyss 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Many months later, in the Ender Kingdom

More than ten gigantic white hot air balloons floated in the blue sky, pulling banners filled with celebratory words and messages of congratulations for the Totem King finals behind them.

Elite participants from various countries stood in their respective lines on the War God Plaza in the middle of the Kingdom, waiting on the plaza quietly.

The surrounding areas were filled with people, including aristocrats, civilians, artisans, and merchants; more than half of the population of the Kingdom had gathered here. From above, all four corners of the area looked like they were filled with dark stretches, that were actually the tops of human heads. Although everyone was merely discussing and exchanging information among themselves softly, the noises they made was still loud enough to form a distinct hum.

There was an exquisite silver diamond-shaped carved fence in the middle of the plaza, that cordoned off a circular area where Totem User finalists stood. Each of them possessed unique styles, and while some of them had calm expressions on their faces, others appeared malicious, still others were either gentle and polite, or completely indifferent.

All of them had their trusted subordinate deputies behind them.

Since the King of Ender had organized many competitions in the past, he had built up a fine reputation for himself all this while. If that was not the case, the elite participants from various countries would not have hastily believed that he would put up such a generous sum of wealth as the prize for the finals.

A white, hollowed out sacrificial altar carved with various patterns was placed in the center. Below the feet of the golden War God statue, two thick books were placed on two sharp thorn-like white-gold platforms, while two sacrifices stood behind the books and flipped through their pages, loudly chanting prayers for the finals.

More than ten beautiful young girls stood on the side and held vases, sprinkling some of the clean water that had been soaked with flower petals on the foreheads of all of the participants gently.

Next, the participants and representatives came forward to greet the audience, while their bodies activated rings of different Spirit Lights naturally. These were recorded by specialized note-taking officers, in order to prevent impersonations or replacements.

Finally, the inspection officer came forward to individually check the permitted items that the participants had brought with them.

The concave black main door of the Eternal Night Palace was slowly pushed open.

"Let the finals begin!!"

An old feeble voice was amplified and echoed through the sky above the entire Ender Kingdom.

Bang bang bang!!

Suddenly, white-gold fireworks exploded throughout the sky, before tiny white-gold lights fell on the ground like gentle raindrops.

A bell toll echoed from afar. The female sacrifices sang the eternal hymn of the Giant Divine Statue loudly, as their voices turned into physical, silver colored, transparent music notes that floated in the sky.

The sages stood on top of the Kingdom’s three holy pillars and released all of their strength simultaneously. Three crisp tearing noises could be heard, before three white-gold light beams shot out of the ground and pierced through the sky, extending through the clear sky above the fence towards the infinite universe.

Only then were the finalists led into the Eternal Night Palace by the guides.

At this moment, the world leaders were paying close attention to the Ender Kingdom’s movements. Numerous analysis, reports, and forecast texts were constantly placed on their desks.

Radios broadcasted the whole course and reported all of the movements that happened at the scene in real time.

Among the group that was entering, a figure in a long black robe raised his head slightly, before the corners of his grey metallic-like mouth curled into a faint arc.

*******************

On top of an ashen cliff, somewhere between the Three Territories

Black Prince sat leaning against a pile of overlapping ashen rocks on the cliff. His entire body was covered in a suit of black armor that made it impossible to see his face, except for the faint gleam of red light that flashed through his eyes that gave off a wild, beast-like violence.

There were two other people on the cliff. One of them was a tall man, with long black hair that reached past his shoulders while a large black horse stood beside him. Thick black smoke would appear around the man and the horse’s bodies occasionally.

The other person was a woman, clad in splendid attire from head to toe. She wore an exquisite red gown with a long train that dragged behind her and a dark silver fan-shaped crown on her head. A strange, evil-looking smile flashed on her beautiful pale face from time to time.

"Divine God Palace Master and the King of Ender’s plan trapped Hellgate for a full year. Now, it seems that Hellgate was unable to find Divine God Palace Master, and decided to go directly to Ender’s Eternal Night Palace instead. Who can be sure of the winners and losers this time?" said the woman in the red dress in a soft voice. It sounded as if she were speaking to herself, but also seemed as if she was asking the other two a question.

"Ender’s chances of winning are less than thirty percent," answered the knight with the black horse quietly.

Black Prince raised his head and glanced at the Black Knight. "I refuse to flinch, even if the situation has truly reached its most dire point." His voice was hoarse, resembling the low roar of a wild beast.

"With the core of the Three Territories as the foundation, our numerous Precious Heirlooms as the bones, and the Origins of all three of us as the blood, we must swear not to let Hellgate or the others escape from the Eternal Night Palace!" said the woman in the red dress as she lifted up the strands of hair from her shoulders gently, without a trace of seriousness or worry on her face. "We don’t know how much protection power will remain in the Three Territories after this."

The three people from each of the Three Territories had their own ideals and wills. Obscuro Society’s Hellgate would perish if he continued to resist, and after Phiroth was destroyed, the decline of Ender would occur again, before their Three Territories would befall the same fate next.

At the crossroads of life and death, the leaders of the Three Territories would finally meet again.

All three of them became quiet at once. None of them opened their mouths again as they were all waiting for something.

After some time, three slender white light beams lit up in the sky from afar, and pierced through the clouds.

"It has begun… That’s Eternal Night Palace’s Moon Scar light…" The woman in the red dress looked towards the beams in the distance.

The Black Knight mounted his large horse and shook the reins before, the large smokey horse moved in that direction immediately. The sharp sound of its footsteps could be heard clearly above the static while it entered the depths of the man’s heart. Moments later, the giant horse jumped off the cliff and began to trot through the sky normally as if it were walking on level ground.

The red gleam in Black Prince’s eyes flashed suddenly when he stood up, before he gradually turned transparent.

A green light flashed beside the woman in the red dress, before a cold but handsome swordsman appeared. He held the woman’s waist with one hand, while the sound of a sword echoed beneath his feet and a green light screen flashed and appeared out of thin air, pulling both of them towards the light beam hurriedly.

************

"It has begun…"

Clad in a white robe, a white-haired old man with a white beard stood in front of a little wooden house in a remote mountain forest in the East Continent.

He raised his head and looked at the continuous drizzle in the sky. His gaze seemed to have passed through the clouds, allowing him to look at the shapeless changes behind them.

Two youths in identical white clothes stood behind the old man. One of them had silvery eyes and was carefully smoothing out the wrinkles on the old man’s long robe.

"This is the first time you’ve come out to bask in the sun in such a long time. What bizarre things are you about to say now, Mr Noah?" It was obvious that this was not the first time the youth had heard this old man speak.

The other person was an even younger male youth who only smiled after hearing the things that had been said.

"I’m not joking this time, Stone." The old man had a serious expression on his face.

"Wasn’t that what you said last time?" Beckstone was dumbfounded.

The old man turned around and grabbed Stone by his wrists suddenly.

"Don’t mind me, just go and do the things you were supposed to do. Wasting your time on an old dying person like myself just isn’t worth it." The old man’s face was unusually solemn.

Beckstone and the other youth finally realized that the old man was truly being serious this time.

He stopped his tidying actions and met the old man’s gaze instead.

"Mr Noah, are you doing this wholeheartedly?"

The old man let go of his hands and became silent for a moment.

"The Moon Scar Light has appeared. Therefore, the things that were prepared by us old people and both of our Presidents should truly be of use to you now…"

Beckstone’s heart sank for a moment. The Terraflor Society President had died because of Hellgate, while all of the involved Elders were captured in one go. The only person left in the whole Terraflor Society was this heavily injured old fellow who only had a few months left to live.

Although Hellgate had kept to his promise of letting Terraflor Society go, the commanders below him would not release them so easily.

Stone did not have a close relationship with these old people. He only returned this time to accompany the previous Thunder God Hannet to look for a place to nurse his injuries, but never expected to save Mr Noah by accident. After getting to know each other for a period of time, Noah gave all of his knowledge and assets to Stone. Their teacher-student relationship and Stone’s own interactions with this man made him acknowledge Noah as a wise old man.

However, when he realized that the President and Elders had already expected an ending like this long ago and had even made preparations in advance, Beckstone’s heart was slightly heavy.

"Take everything from Terraflor Society and go… Go to the Eternal Night Palace… Stop Hellgate," said Noah in a low voice. Suddenly, a pointed sphere like red gem was gently placed in Beckstone’s hand.

"Hellgate’s goal is the Door to Heaven, so it’s unnecessary for us to block him from the front," said the other youth suddenly. "Pulling open the Door to Heaven requires a great price to be paid. Therefore, as long as we wait for the right moment, we’ll get a chance to work together and kill Hellgate!"

"That’s right, Mr Noah. Why do we have to stop the appearance of the Door to Heaven?" Beckstone was not confident enough to make a move at this moment either. Their forces were too weak, and if a face to face confrontation occurred, Obscuro Society would crush them easily.

Noah exhaled slowly.

"Hellgate has no intention of using his own powers to pull the Door to Heaven open. His true goal is to use the Eternal Night Palace’s power! Now that Phiroth is dead, if the people who are coming to get Ender die as well, no one will be able to stop Hellgate’s desires anymore!"

Both Beckstone and the other youth became faintly gloomy. Regarding the death of their President and Elders, they were not emotionally moved at all. After all, they were too far apart. However, after listening to Noah explain the current situation, both of them began to form clearer judgments of the larger picture in their minds.

"Hellgate has already promised to let our Terraflor Society go, so why do we still need to continue going in?" Beckstone’s question concerned his greatest doubts.

"Let Terraflor Society go?" A mocking expression appeared on Noah’s face. "What he wants, is an obedient Terraflor Society; a secret association controlled by his people. He doesn’t want an organization of previous enemies like us that will definitely cause trouble for him in the future. Moreover, it’s not like we wanted to cause trouble for them. On the contrary, they were the ones who would never let us go…" Suddenly, Noah smiled mysteriously. "Listen… They’re here…"

At the same time, the sound of soft footsteps echoed throughout the mountain forest, while beast-like roars could be heard occasionally.

Suddenly, a grey membrane layer appeared across the sky.

Clang!

The sound of moving chains rang out throughout the sky at once.

God Cloud’s figure floated out slowly and appeared in front of the little wooden house. His head was completely bald while his body was surrounded by thin black chains. Meanwhile, his falcon-like gaze focused on old man Noah’s body instantly.

"Never thought that there would still be some scum for me to clean up, Noah Counterman."

Chapter 538: Abyss 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beckstone and the other youth reacted at once, and stood in front of the old man. When they noticed the increasing number of Silver Totems around them, both of their faces soon became extremely unsightly.

"I’ll hold them off! You take Mr Noah away!" shouted the other youth in a low voice.

"No one will escape today!" sneered God Cloud. "Noah, give me the Earth Flower! A Precious Heirloom like that can only show its true value in the hands of President Hellgate!"

Noah did not show the slightest hint of worry. Instead, he looked towards God Cloud with a mysterious smile on his face.

Pfft!

A flash of golden light appeared in front of them immediately.

Beckstone and the youth were blinded for a moment, unable to see anything.

"Amplified delivery technique!! Noah, how dare you!!!" When he heard God Cloud’s furious voice, a panicked feeling washed over him as he reached over and grabbed in Noah’s direction, but his hands merely met air.

******************

Many days later…

The depths of the North Sea.

Garen’s body, frozen inside the icicle, had a sudden, slow movement. .

The sound of quiet footsteps echoed from the deepest, darkest end of the plaza, in front of the icicle.

Ivycius had accompanied Skyharp to collect medicinal herbs, leaving Garen alone underneath the deep sea. This was the bottom of the deep sea, the darkest and coldest place in the entire North Sea. Under normal circumstances, no one would ever dare, or even be able to come here. However, an exception had appeared now.

The sound of footsteps grew clearer, before a person slowly emerged from the darkness..

This plaza was isolated from the rest of the seawater using a specialized technique. A large cavity formed in the area that allowed noise to reverberate through the ice plaza continuously, like the endless echoes across a valley.

Pap… Pap… Pap… Pap… Pap…

The person stopped in front of Garen. Its human like figure was completely shrouded within black mist, making it impossible to see its attire, appearance, skin color, and even its hair color.

The figure raised its head slightly to look at Garen, suspended within the gigantic icicle.

"I designed a stage, and I was wondering if Palace Master Garen would be interested to come in and see it?" The figure’s voice was neither male nor female. Instead, it was a completely specialized and neutral, an obvious sign that it had been processed beforehand, making it impossible to distinguish the speaker’s gender.

"Oh?" An unusually graceful male voice could be heard from the icicle. "What a secretive fellow… I don’t even know your identity, yet you dived into the depths of the North Sea just to say these mysterious words to me?"

The figure smiled. Although it was covered by black mist, Garen could still sense that it was smiling.

"The world is balanced, and the order of survival of all creation depends on this battle. We reap only what we sow. . Aren’t these the laws that govern the universe?"

Garen remained silent, as he waited to hear what the other person would say next.

"Throughout the entire polar region of the North Sea, areas spanning more than hundreds of nautical miles have turned into poisonous and forbidden marine territories. Palace Master, although you willingly decided to conceal yourself here for more than a year and withstood these abominable environments as the price to pay for scattering, do you truly not desire the next stage in your quest for power ?"

Once the figure stopped speaking, silence once again covered the plaza. .

Garen calmly focused his attention on the other party. .

"Did you come here just to speak. ?" he asked suddenly.

"Of course not." The figure smiled again. "I came to give Your Excellency an unexpected surprise."

They had just finished speaking, before the figure turned into a shroud of black mist suddenly and flowed into the icicle. The black mist had merely come into contact with the ice before the sound of corrosion hissed loudly. .

Moments later, the black mist passed through the icicle, before entering into Garen’s nostrils.

Seconds, minutes ticked by, before Garen finally shook slightly and opened his eyes again.

"King of Ender… How generous!" A satisfied smile finally appeared on Garen’s face.

Simultaneously, a strong quake could be felt from the direction Ender was in. Even in the depths of the North Sea, these vibrations were strong enough to be noticeable. Garen gladly accepted the King of Ender’s gift. .

She had lost. During the secret fight in Eternal Night Palace, Hellgate had forcibly defeated the powerful Giant Divine Statue soldiers, before controlling them with his mysterious energy, quietly turning them into his puppets in the end. However, this strong willed woman had not given up. Instead, she took the key knowledge and memories that she had stored earlier, and placed them inside a clone that she had prepared, before turning it into Garen’s gift.

This was the stage she was talking about.

Yes, the stage had already been built. . The only missing piece was the debut of the main character. .

A giggle could be heard, before black threads once again appeared in Garen’s eyes. .

********************

Ender Kingdom

Numerous local Ender professionals, diplomatic envoys from various countries, Totem Users, and representatives of both major and minor forces were all waiting for the doors of Eternal Night Palace to open again, as well as the arrival of the final outcomes.

Pale flower petals fluttered like rain in the wind, while the sound of hymns turned into numerous tiny silver lights that flew around the expanse of the rocky city.

Within the largest area among the five main sections of the city, inside one of the secret aristocratic buildings.

Goth sat in front of the third floor window steadily, while a familiar-looking woman sat opposite him.

"Jessica…"

"Aren’t you happy to see me?" asked Jessica with a smile as she sat opposite him. She was clad in a long, pale white dress, as she intertwined all ten of her fingers of both hands on the table casually, currently free of any heroic spirit.

"How is our child? Is everything still alright?"

Goth remained silent. . He turned his head and looked out of the window; the pale flower petals and silver dots of light that cascaded like snowflakes had now piled up into a thick layer on the roof, on the opposite side of the street. The entirety of the Ender Kingdom had turned into a sparkling silver field, and every building seemed as if it had been covered in a layer of silver fluorescent powder.

"Coincidences don’t happen in this world often. Why did you have to pick such a key moment to return…"

"I don’t know," shrugged Jessica. "Perhaps the Totem that’s controlling me decided to do this. It was involuntary. A little boat floating on the sea wouldn’t know when a wave would come and swallow it either."

When Jessica noticed that Goth’s face had matured, she smiled faintly.

"Goth, don’t you want us to return to the past, to that period of time in the beginning, when we were at our happiest?" She spoke in a kind, gentle voice, her soft gaze set on man in front of her.. He was the most important man in her life; her one and only.

"Those were the happiest days of my life…" Goth smiled reluctantly but felt an indescribable bitterness in his heart for some strange reason.

"That person said that as long as you help me do something, she’ll release the control she has on me," smiled Jessica sweetly.

Looking at Jessica’s sweet, familiar smile tugged and squeezed at Goth’s heart, , forcing him to close his eyes. Vaguely, he knew that something incomparably pure in his life had slowly begun to shatter. .

Jessica, who was opposite him, stood up and walked over quietly, before embracing Goth’s head against her chest.

"I know that you love me more than anything in the world , only you…" She nestled her chin against the top of Goth’s forehead, while her eyes betrayed the traces of resentment, pain, and insanity intertwined within. .

"As long as you destroy Garen’s life, just one life… she’ll finally release me."

No one knew, that after the many times that Garen had provoked Obscuro Society, Jessica, whom they were controlling, would be used as a tool to vent their anger. She was heavily injured, to the point of death, time after time, and had suffered various types of torture. At the end of the day, she would be locked in the deepest part of the filthy underground water dungeon with nothing but cockroaches and insects as food.

Before she arrived, she had once again suffered the hand of violent abuse. . The woman that appeared suddenly changed her methods, and chose to torture her continuously instead. She did not know what had upset the other woman, but it was clear that Obscuro Society had once again suffered a great loss at the hands of Garen..

But, it didn’t matter. She was already used to it.

Violent beatings like this did not bring her pain, but stirred a faint, strangely pleasant sensation within her instead. Compared to the torture that she had suffered in the past, this was merely child’s play.

However, what made her the happiest, was the thought that she would finally be free, as long as she killed Garen. That incredibly successful Black Swamp Palace Master, Garen.

Why did she have to suffer in the damp, cold, smelly water dungeon, while he lived comfortably in a magnificent palace?

While she suffered various kinds of torture and was beaten up mercilessly, the others were busy enjoying themselves and having fun…

Hehehe…

Jessica could not help but giggle softly.

So many days had passed, but no one had found her, or even remembered her. She was forgotten, left in a corner of the world, forced to suffer a repetitive life of dark, endless days. .

*********************

Black Prince leaned against his mother’s chest quietly, like a newborn baby, a sentimental smile on his face.

"If I’m able to wake the dragon up again, what will you be willing to give up in exchange?" A low male voice rang out behind him.

"Everything," answered Black Prince softly.

His vision blurred, before Black Prince realised that he was staring at the diplomat in front of him, while the other person was currently explaining the situation of the Ender Kingdom finals.

He was seated on the throne in the main section of the Ambassadorial Hall while the Dragonfield Totem User officials filled the seats on both his left and right sides.

"My thoughts wandered off again…"

*********************

As she walked through the street corners of the rocky city, it seemed as if the excitement of the finals had spread throughout every block in the Kingdom.

Queen Earnest was dressed in plain clothes, and resembled a fragile, pretty young girl. She held Green Dragon Swordsman’s wrists, making them seem like a romantic young couple strolling through the various stalls, occasionally buying cheap but cute accessories.

Although they were squeezed by the crowd, neither of them seemed impatient at all.

"Could we not participate in the movement this time?" For an unknown reason, Green Dragon Swordsman felt an indescribable sense of worry when he looked at Her Majesty the Queen’s cheerful smile. As her long time Green Dragon Sword companion, he had an extremely sensitive instinct towards matters of survival.

Waves of uneasiness constantly stirred within his mind..

"Don’t worry. The numerous Precious Heirlooms are the price we have to pay, while the resources of the defense foundations of the Three Territories will be used as the core. Therefore, all three of us controllers will only require a small amount of blood as a form of permission. There will be no danger at all," said Queen Earnest as she brought the swordsman’s arm towards her chest slowly, letting it rest there.

"It was really difficult for us to get here. Tonight, I am yours…" the Queen whispered as she gently leaned against the swordsman..

"Let’s get married when we return." A trace of gentle warmth appeared on Green Dragon Swordsman’s cold, but handsome face.

"Mmhmm."

A light breeze blew past, while fluttering silver dots and flower petals fell on the Queen’s long hair. Coupled with her milky white skin and pale lips, she was definitely the most beautiful creature in that moment. .

Chapter 539: World 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Within the dark and gloomy Eternal Night Palace.

The yellow light by the wall dimly lit the round, spacious passage, which had two huge pillars textured in golden circles.

There were a pair of triangular mirrors every few meters on the ceiling in the passage that was at least ten meters wide. The shiny mirror had reflected everything within the corridor.

Ding!

Suddenly, a single note of the piano echoed through the passage. The key was pressed again and again, like an anxious heart beating incessantly.

The piano notes gradually climbed higher, from the deepest area of the Eternal Night Palace. The spherical melody traveled like a ripple.

The notes were random and out of rhythm, nor was it pleasant to listen to. It was rather painful to the ear, as countless sharp short, tones blared.

A person in black robes slowly traveled down the corridor with a wheelchair.

The actions he took beneath his robes were slow. There was a white haired girl, in full armor, in the wheelchair with her eyes closed. Her pale skin was slick with sweat.

"What a beautiful melody…" The person who was pushing said softly.

"You have a very unique sense in music." The girl in the wheelchair tried her best to laugh.

"What kind of emotion do you need to produce such a strong melody? I’m really curious." The person pushing the wheelchair said.

Their figures inside the mirror were slightly bent, and what was strange was that the reflection of the person who was pushing the wheelchair inside the mirrors, kept disappearing and reappearing. It was as if the girl was moving the wheelchair on her own.

As the wheelchair moved forward, a white light appeared in the distance. It was the only exit from the Eternal Night Palace, and the final passage to arrive in the outer world.

A deafening roar of a crowd cheering traveled from the outside, accompanied by the din of a master of ceremony doing an introduction.

An ocean of heads was looking inside, and there were even two rows of beautiful ladies throwing flower petals out from a basket. Two sacraments were guarding the entrance with a silver robe and white gold flower chaplet in their hands. It was the reward for the champion.

The man pushing the wheelchair wiped the sweat off the girl, smiled gently and pushed the wheelchair forward.

Creak…

The wheelchair was moving out of the exit, slowly but firmly. At the same time, the girl’s face turned very pale.

"Welcome the honored Eternal Night Palace Master, the King of Ender! Her Majesty Serena!!"

The master of ceremony’s voice was choked with passion, and the girl’s pupil shrunk as she saw each pair of eyes in the sea of people focused solely on her.

She opened her mouth and tried to speak, but strangely, only kept opening her mouth wider and wider. Suddenly, a pool of viscous blood gushed out and kept flowing out from her, onto her chest, and subsequently to the ground.

In that instant, the crowd went silent. Then, a sharp scream broke the silence.

The blood kept flowing out from the woman’s mouth, as if there was an endless source within her. The ground was stained crimson as it spread around her, congealing into a pool.

Now, the screams had erupted across the plaza, as emergency response units came rushing into the pool of blood. As their feet stepped on it, they, too, joined the screaming, as they seemingly disappeared into the pool. Their lower bodies corroded and dissolved into the pool of blood. After a few steps, they would tip and disappear completely.

Ding ding ding…!!

Bell tolls joined the chaotic symphony of noise, as the whole kingdom was slung into a state of panic.

"Her Majesty has been assassinated!""Help!!" such were the screams that permeated the kingdom, as teams of guardians quickly gathered together and flew out of the Eternal Night Palace. They were the Ender Kingdom and multiple countries’ elites.

Boom! Boom boom!

The hot air balloons’ baskets in the sky exploded one after the other. Whatever sounds the occupants had produced, only silence remained. Only the balloons themselves could take their space, in serenity, on top of a bed of chaos.

From a bird’s eye view, the small pool of blood in the center of the Monolith City spread outward at great speed. From the size of the nail, its liquid tendrils extended into the size of a palm, then to a basin, and further and further beyond at an alarming speed.

Whatever living being that was stained by the blood, be it a commoner or a totem user, immediately melted like a burning candle. What was their being was now thick, red, blood.

The pool of blood continued its crusade across the city, chasing the countless fleeing citizens in every direction. An unlucky soul would find himself beneath the feet of the tsunami of bodies, and then, as he tried to get up, in the pool of unstoppable blood. Every corner of the city; merchants, alleys, shops. None were spared from the chaos.

Screams penetrated whatever order sound had tried to form.

And it was at this moment, that three white lights flew inside the city.

"Gentlemen, do what you do!" A girl’s voice emanated from one of the light orbs.

"The queen is too kind!"

"This is what we should do!"

"We must save Her Highness!""Her Highness is already dead!""Impossible!"

The second wave of white lights floated on top of the sea of blood, all at least form four totem users from multiple countries. The tri-country alliance, together with the King of Ender’s plan, the whole line up was almost filled with the elites from the Eastern Continent.

"Stop arguing!" One among the three lights from the first wave shouted deeply. "Great Starry Sky Sacrifice Tactic, activate!"

Goth’s eyes seemed to be on fire inside the white light. He reached out his right hand and stabbed it with a dagger, as his blood dripped down to the ground.

The remaining two people, Queen Earnest and the Black Prince did the same..

Kachak!!

Countless white lightning arcs started to flash among the crowds.

In an instant, with the three district leaders as the core, the white lightning had formed into a net.

"Judge!!" Queen Earnest shouted.

A white, meaty tongue came out in between the space of the lightning net and descended.

The tongue was about a few hundred meters wide, and it seemed to not have any limit in length as it kept elongating. It was also covered with a white, disgusting fluid.

Buzz…

The earth started to tremble, as the buildings in the Monolith city started to fall apart one by one, as if they were a bunch of dominos.

A small vortex appeared at the center of the large, bloody pool.

The vortex became larger and larger, and expanded to the edge of the sea of blood within seconds.

Kaboom!!

A dark red, giant hand reached out from within sea of blood and collided with the white tongue in the sky.

"Judgement!!"

Goth shouted.

The sky was immediately engulfed in darkness as dark as black clouds descended upon the city. The dark cloud kept tumbling, giving off an intense oppression.

Bam!

An arc of lightning appeared, lightening up the faces of the citizens and totem users who had managed to escape from the city.

The outskirts of the Monolith City was suddenly surrounded by a huge group of people in white robes. Most of them were Divine Officers from the Ender Kingdom. The top totem users within the three districts were mixed in among them.

They raised their hands up high, as black smoke seeped out from their bodies and gathered in the sky.

Behind these circle of white robes, there was another circle of people in red robes. They had different kinds of Heirlooms shining in their hands. These Heirlooms kept disintegrating and turning into countless white dots, floating up in the sky.

The black clouds in the sky then amassed into one.

The clouds shaped themselves into a giant humanoid figure, which looked strong and muscular.

Its muscles were packed full and its body was made purely out of the black smoke, and was large enough to cover the city. He growled as he lowered down his head.

"Your spine is the world’s to smite! Repent! Villain!"

A wavelength made of pure energy rippled outward, turning into countless languages, and then directly into everyone’s head.

The giant reached both of his hands out and placed them upon the sea of blood.

The world stopped to look at this moment; as countless totem users joined together and cast a feed of the Monolith City out across the world.

The Three Districts allied with the Ender Kingdom, the remaining forces of Daniela, and countless of survivors hiding in the dark to fight the final battle against the Obscuro Society’s Hellgate.

Another giant hand appeared from the sea of blood, and resisted the giant arms made of black smoke.Both hands joined and connected, forming a huge pillar from the heavens down to hell.

Among the three largest white dots, the Black Prince raised his head, and looked at the giant in the sky. He could even feel the gaze from the other two.

"You need me…" His hands reached, outwards, touching the inner wall within the white film.

Screech!!

In that instant, he pulled the inner wall of white film with both of his hands.

"What are you doing Black Prince!!??"

A shout of rage came.

"No!!"

"Your Highness!""What are you doing!!"

Waves of roars came, as banded as the totem users that came together.

The white film that was torn apart, and slowly began to lose its glow. What replaced it was the evil smile of the Black Prince.

His lips curled, and then he exerted once more.

Screech!

The film was torn split into two. He walked out of the white light surrounding him, gently made his way to the ground.

"...Welcome back…" A bald man slowly emerged from the sea of blood. He smiled and looked at the approaching Black Prince.

The Black Prince marked an arc in the middle sky, and the sea of blood automatically spread out as he landed on the side of the bald man.

The white net of lightning took the Black Prince’s betrayal and faded. The power source of its resistance was now gone. The electricity arced in all directions, collapsing in on itself and disappearing

The giant made of black smoke dispersed along with it. The band of totem users in battle began to regurgitate crimson, as their bodies trembled and fell to the ground. Some had even imploded, showering the ground with their blood. Still others disintegrated in mid-air, their now lifeless corpses as dark as the Black Prince’s betrayal.

Goth and Queen Earnest’s light film shattered, and they fell from the sky. They barely managed to flee the city, and landed safely, and were attended to by the people they’d prepared earlier.

Giant hands kept emerging from the sea of blood, one after another, right in the heart of Monolith City.

Two became three, then five. Ten. Twenty. Fifty…

An innumerable wave of crimson hands, a huge pillar column that grew unstoppably longer, reaching far into the sky.

Goth and Earnest looked at each other and took out two, shiny blue spherical cores.

"I didn’t expect that it would come to this…" Earnest muttered, her heart and spirit heavy.

"Haven’t we decide on this earlier?" Goth said calmly.

"Without the Black Prince’s black district core… I’m not sure if it would be successful." Earnest shook her head.

Under the protection of those around them, their gaze was transfixed on the forest of dark red arms that pierced through the clouds. The stench of blood filled the air, asserting its dominion.

The ground trembled greatly, the sea of blood hammering the earth with incessant shocks.

The world fell into darkness as hands blanketed the land.

The only things still shining were the weak green light from the green spheres in their hands.

Compared to the forest of arms, they were about as significant as ants under the leg of a giant.

Although the current conditions of the other totem users were thrown into the unknown along with the light, at least they knew without a doubt that their first plan was a total failure.

"I’m not sure what the Queen of Ender Kingdom has in mind, but I hope the second plan is effective." Goth looked at the forest of arms, his face devoid of expression.

Chapter 540: World 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the Cthulhuism Society, all the Cthulhus had gathered together, as they sat in a huge, oval living hall. The afternoon sunlight came into the room from the left, scattering across the long table.

All the Cthulhus, sat in 2 rows, were looking at the monitor on the other end of the table.

It was showing the horrible chain of events that happened in the Ender Kingdom’s capital, Monolith City.

Countless dark red arms as tall as the sky looked like giant, oppressing mountains.

The whole living hall was in complete silence.

********

Kovitan Empire

A huge, square water mirror was floating in the sky, on top of the Kingdom, in between the peaks of three mountains.

The water mirror was constructed by a huge amount of clear water and broadcasted the situation in Ender Kingdom, thousands of kilometers away.

Countless citizens of the Kingdom had their heads raised, their gaze firmly fixed on the screen. They prayed, they were in pain, but most of time hold their breath as they waited for the arrival of the end.

It was in their plan to let the others know how cruel and merciless that Obscuro Society was.

At one of the small buildings in the Palace District.

Sofea, and her sister Danielle, were doing some gardening in the garden. She was in a white dress, and she had a pot of water in her hand as she watered the flowers. Her gaze was also on the giant mirror up in the sky.

The two sisters kept looking at the situation within the water mirror.

There were masses of dark red arms, and the unending cries of citizens gravely injured. It was like a mountain of trash piled together as they ran away from the kingdom in fear.

The earth would occasionally tear apart and swallow the crowd.

A few people tried to maintain order, but were immediately torn apart by the wolf type totems summoned by the Obscuro Society. Those totem users who were able to fend for themselves were surrounded by multiple strong empowered totems.

The totem users of the Obscuro Society were merciless, as they slaughtered and murdered the people escaping from the Monolith City.

On the other screens were the battles between the remaining totem users from different countries and the empowered totems from the Obscuro Society. No one seemed to have the upper hand; the quantity of the empowered totems were far too great. A majority of the most elite totem users had entered the Eternal Night Palace, and had yet to come out.

The explosions in the town, the guttural roars of creatures and cries of dying citizens all joined and continued a symphony of destruction across the whole city.

The Monolith City had become a battlefield overflowing with blood.

"Sister…" Danielle hugged her sister Hathaway tightly.

"It’s going to be okay… We’re inside the Ultimate Protection... " Hathaway tried her best to smile.

However, the countless red hands had, indeed, faltered her heart. She found it impossible to believe what she had just said.

No one could be sure that the Ultimate Protection would be able to defend against that terrifying strength.

**********

At the peak nearby the Kingdom, there was a white manor that was recently built.

On the balcony outdoors.

Emin was holding onto a wooden crutch, as he looked at the water mirror in the sky quietly. There were a few disciples standing behind him, watching quietly as well.

"Teacher…"

A man voiced out softly from behind.

"We can do nothing but wait." Emin replied softly.

"Hellgate of the Obscuro Society is simply too powerful…" He looked at the water mirror. He could feel the overwhelming power, even though it’s so far away.

The stronger the totem user, the more they understood just how powerful one needed to be to create such a scene.

"The Obscuro Society will definitely eliminate any forces that pose threat to them. They will definitely come after us!"

"We still have brother Garen! With him and the Ultimate Protection, we will definitely be fine!!"

"Yes! We still have a chance, since we still have the Ultimate Protection and the Big Four!"

The disciples' voices kept coming from behind and yet Emin still lowered down his head. Deep down they knew that Hellgate was the strongest since the death of Phiroth.

Since the Obscuro Society had directed the big turmoil of the aberrated beings, no one was fond of them, and in fact was filled with hatred.

Many people had lost their families, relatives, and their peaceful lifestyle because of them.

If the Obscuro Society were to succeed…

*******

The sky was trembling.

In the sky of Ender Kingdom, countless giant dark red hands pierced through the black clouds.

Arcs of white lightning flashed within them.

Countless of dark red arms pierced into the clouds as if they were pillars supporting the sky.

"All shall return… All shall return…"

A song could be faintly heard in the sky, spreading across Monolith City, and then the Ender Kingdom. The melody travelled through the air, across oceans, and even into the Western Continent.

The whole world had been instantaneously filled with the same melody.

Everyone in every country could hear its faint notes, like someone singing. The song carried with it a sad air about itself.

The black rain started to pour onto the ground.

The people around the Monolith City raised their heads to look at the forest of arms that pierced through the clouds.

The black rain descended upon the land, dying them in the same shade of black.

The rain was like oil, sticky and smelly, just like fresh blood.

In the sky, a crack of pure, white clouds appeared.

The pure white light pierced through the black clouds like an arrow, as it shone onto the dark red hands.

A huge circular door of light slowly appeared above the forest of red arms, supported by them.

The door was carved with scrawls of symbols and textures. The white gold flowery texture of carvings depicted nature in its many forms; in the form of mountain valleys, rivers, oceans, forests, snowy, mountain capped peaks mountains and many more. As one looked at it, it was as if it weren’t a motionless picture. The picture was moving, alive, just like mother nature herself.

A mirror as clear as glass was in the center of the door, but it was dark, and nothing was reflected off its surface.

The innumerable, dark red hands reached and held onto the door, before they collectively pulled on it from the sky. The melody that floated across the land had come from this very door.

"The Door to Heaven…"

Under this door, and above the bloody Monolith City, a bald man in black robes was levitating among several white hot air balloons.

His silver skin was rather dim under the white light, as he stared at the giant white door with his silvery eyes and smiled a smile of satisfaction.

"Finally… Finally I’ve succeeded.."

At this moment, viscous blood flowed from the red arms up to the door.

The sea of blood pushed Hellgate upwards to the mirror, getting closer, and closer...

Boom!!

A layer of blue light exploded from the surface on the red sea, and halted its movement.

A mouthful of fresh blood came out from Goth’s mouth, outside the city. Goth, who had just entered the middle fifth form had instantly degraded to the elementary tier. As the Black District’s core inside him exploded, his strength instantly dropped by half.

Queen Earnest, to one side, raised the Rainbow District’s core up high as she walked slowly towards the sea of blood.

She crushed the green core in one swift movement.

Boom!!

The sea of blood that was climbing up to the door was once halted again. The layer of blue light shattered and disappeared.

Hellgate stared down coldly and raised his hand.

Queen Earnest was impacted by something invisible and was sent out flying like a ragdoll. She landed tumbled about before coming to a halt. A simple attack from him had caused a grave injury on her, and blood started to flow out from her body.

"No!!" A green light came from behind and landed beside Earnest.

The Green Dragon Swordman kneeled down and cradled Earnest in his arms.

The sky was then covered in a layer of a pure, blue net, and countless huge symbols were blinking within it. The huge blue net had separated the sea of blood and the Door to Heaven; a terrifying power blasted to wind and surged out in all directions. Not a single survivor in the vicinity could open their eyes, and they fell lower and huddled their bodies when the wind blew.

"The world!" Hellgate raised both of his hands up as he shouted.

The sea of blood trembled.

"The world!!"

He raised his head as if he were trying to shout with all his might.

A circle of blood appeared in the sky.

"The world!!!"

Hellgate’s roar masked over the mysterious holy music.

The blood gathered together, and gushed upwards.

The sound of a huge impact reverberated through the land

The blue net was torn apart, and completely drowned by the sea of blood.

Hellgate’s face turned pale. It was only natural, as he was going against two major district’s energies that had been accumulated for countless years. There were also the energies from the Heirlooms, and countless of totem users. In addition, there was also the secret battle against the King of Ender and the series of major battles that followed, and also the formation to obtain full control over the Eternal Night Palace. He had also sacrificed countless of lives to pull out the Door to Heaven. Even if he was the strongest totem user in history, he wasn’t able to resist the damage, as injury after injury started to appear within his body, at the same place where Phiroth hit him.

He raised his head as his eyes turned red.

The sea of blood behind him increased picked up speed as it pushed him to the Door to Heaven.

"The world!!!"

He roared!

Kachak… Boom!!

The mirror in the center of the Door to Heaven shattered.

The holy music stopped instantly.

On the peak of a mountain, far away, the Cthulhu King, clad in a white robe, opened one of his red eyes.

Within an active volcano, a single head could be seen bobbing above the lava. It was the Divine God Palace Master. The scorching hot lava flowed on his body, like springtime dew on a leaf at dawn.

Under the abyss in the ocean, Garen, who was covered in poison and ice, slowly had his eyelids part. Krak! A fine, thin line cracked its way down the ice.

The world, was changing.

Chapter 541: World 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"People once said that the sky was originally red mixed with black instead of blue."

"Red mixed with black? Do you think that’s possible?"

"Perhaps. There are things that exist even if we don’t believe it."

Noah, who was in a wooden chair, gently placed down a copper yellow watch as he smiled.

It was dead silent inside the small house and only a faint chirp could be heard from outside as the black rain poured nonstop outside.

"The dance stage has been all set." He looked at the sky through the window as his body became more and more transparent.

"Serena… I really wish I can see you one more time."

A gentle wind blew and only a robe was left onto the table and no one knew where he went.

At the same time, in the sky of the whole Eastern Continent.

Three silver meteors flew towards the Monolith City at great speed. The three meteors pulled out a long tail as they flew from three different directions. The sound of the shockwave deafened the sky.

The black clouds were moving about and no one could make out if it was day or night.

In the middle of the black cloud, the huge white door was giving off a pure white light, which pierced through the clouds as if it was the only Door to Heaven in hell.

Three meteors landed onto the ground, forming a standard equilateral triangle.

As the silver light shone, a deep explosion could be heard as it immediately cleared off the empowered totems from the Obscuro Society within the vicinity.

"Ten Jedi!!" A huge green sword appeared and cut the black clouds into half in an instant.

The sharp sword was like a green lightning as it went after Hellgate in the air.

Clank!!

Hellgate moved his left hand and an after image appeared in front and blocked the attack directly.

His hand and the sword collided together and countless of green sparks appeared and spread around him and locked him in place.

Pew pew pew pew!!!

In an instant, a series of green sword kept attacking Hellgate with great precision.

Nine greatswords landed onto Hellgate as fast as lightning.

Clank! Clank! Clank! Clank clank clank! …

As they collided against each other, Hellgate who was flying towards the Door to Heaven was pushed back down.

"Sun God King…" He turned his head as he looked at the origin of the green blade.

The silver light dimmed down as the Divine Gone Palace Master’s green robe appeared. He was holding an exquisite green great longbow which spanned at least ten meters long, which was larger than him. There were two sharp blades at the edge of the longbow and it’s a weapon that could be even used during melee combat.

Sizzle Sizzle…

The silver light from the other two ends dimmed down as well, revealing two figures in the middle of the sky.

The Cthulhu King and Garen was floating quietly as the three of them surrounded Hellgate.

"Sun God King, the Cthulhu King, Black Swamp Palace Master, and the instant teleportation via the Earth Flower from the Terraflor Society’s master. Looks like this is the gathering of the strongest in this world." Hellgate didn’t seem anxious at all as if he was just having a chat after a meal.

"Is this Noah’s final formation?"

The Cthulhu King’s expression was heavy. He, who was in a red robe, held the magic mirror tightly in his hand as a pale face kept floating within the mirror.

He gently jolted the magic mirror.

Pew!

A stream of black light instantly soared to the sky, engulfing him in the process. The light soared up the sky and started to change its shape as it formed into a big black minotaur figure. It was constructed with countless of shades, forming into a humanoid figure. The upper body was of a human and the lower body was of a fish’s tail and had a black harpoon which was about ten meters in one of its hand.

The horned humanoid gently tapped its tail.

The Hellgate’s body jolted as if there was a great force exerting onto his body.

The fish tail moved once again.

Hellgate’s vision turned muddy as everything became out of focus. As he was covered in the shadow, his body had become 2 times denser than before.

The fish tail moved the third time.

Hellgate’s lower body twisted and, pew!

The shadow’s left shoulder was suddenly split opened. At the same time, the same thing happened to Hellgate as well.

"Heh…"

Hellgate suddenly smirked as he gently moved his body.

Boom!

A circle of black light was released from his body and spread in all direction.

"Sun God King, you’ve finally created your own Living Secret Technique…" He glanced at the other two and immediately paid attention to the Divine God Palace Master as if the other two weren’t even worth his attention and only the Divine God Palace Master was the only threat.

Garen retreated slightly as he smiled. A black cross sword slowly appeared in his hand and grew longer over time from about one meter in length to three meters. It was filled with concentrated black smoke and slowly forming into a great halberd. At the tip of the halberd, a cold blue light could be seen.

On the other side, the Cthulhu King who had transformed into a mermaid had countless green jellyfish behind him.

Each and every green jellyfish pulsed as they illuminated a faint green color as their numbers kept increasing. In an instance, half of the sky was filled with them as if it was highly contagious.

"Attack!!"

In an instance, three people disappeared.

The jellyfish, black halberd and green blade lit up at the same time.

With a roar, the Divine God Palace Master grew a pair of red butterfly wings and had a pair of eyes textured onto it. The wings fluttered, creating a gush of strong wind which went towards the Hellgate. He then moved his giant longbow to produce a huge, solid green blade which pierced through the air, forming a stroke of green line.

The Cthulhu King, who had transformed into a mermaid, rushed towards Hellgate with countless of jellyfish following him tightly from behind. He then increased his speed and the jellyfish looked like a series of green meteor showers.

Garen took out the great halberd and held it with both of his hands.

The black great halberd instantaneously increased its length to tens of meters and in an instance was swung towards Hellgate.

Three of them attacked at almost the same time.

Three of them managed to hit Hellgate and cut off countless of dark red hands in the process.

Boom boom boom!

Three consecutive explosions could be heard and countless of jellyfish were melted, the green blade was shattered to pieces as it was caught by Hellgate. The shattered pieces caught fire as they fell into the sea of blood but the fire did not distinguish.

Garen’s great halberd was caught by Hellgate with one hand as well and a great spark could be seen. However, as the tip was in contact with Hellgate’s hand, it fired out countless of black metal spikes towards his eyes and ears.

Hmpf!

Hellgate scowled as he raised up his other hand and a transparent crystal wall appeared and blocked off all the spikes.

The black metal spikes were all nailed onto the crystal wall.

However, in that instance, the green blade pierced through his armpit and the black harpoon hit him fiercely from the top.

The Divine God Palace Master, Cthulhu King and Garen took this opportunity to get close to him. The green longbow blade hybrid, black harpoon and the great halberd. These three weapons once again went after the Hellgate in the center.

With the teamwork among the peak of form five, a mysterious vortex was formed with the four of them as the epicenter. The black clouds from the surrounding gathered together, forming a horrifying whirlpool.

Buzz!!

Suddenly, it was as if Hellgate had an additional pair of hands as afterimages of his hand could be seen and interacted with the weapons that was about to landed onto him.

Hundreds of metals colliding against each other could be heard, trembling the sky.

The horrifying shockwave spread out from the four of them towards the empty land.

Cracks formed on the ground as the earth quaked!

Shockwaves came from the sky one after the other, hitting the ground and towards the totem teams who had yet evacuated.

There were cries of pain, agony, explosion, craziness and hopelessness.

Countless of emotions and voices were mixed together.

The formations created by the totem users were shattered by the shockwave as if they were all legoes. They were shattered by just a gentle touch. Those totem users and totem creatures in the sky exploded as they couldn’t withstand the shockwave.

"Is.. Is that Garen…?!"

Among a team which was moving, Goth raised his head as he looked at the horrifying figure battling in the sky.

"The King of Ender separated his wealth into three portions and gave it to these three as they’re the last hope of this world." Earnest muttered as she was being carried by the Green Dragon Swordsman.

She raised her head and looked at the horrifying battle in the sky. "Those three are the last resistance from this world…"

Huh!

The Divine God Palace Master pulled his longbow and the tips of the longbow were lighted in red, forming two arcs.

The Cthulhu’s mermaid form shrunk and condensed as if it was turning into an ancient fish creature. The contour of his black muscles could be clearly seen as well.

The halberd in Garen’s hand would occasionally turned into a sword, dagger and countless of other weapons. The transformation was smooth and natural.

The combination attacks from those three had no flaw and with the countless of afterimages of Hellgate’s hand, the situation had reached a stalemate.

The sky was agitated as the earth cried.

The walls of the Monolith City couldn’t withstand it and start to crumble.

This millennium old city started to disintegrate as these four fought.

Suddenly a green light landed.

Boom!

Following tightly was another two black light landing onto the ground, causing the dusts and dirts to filled the air.

Although Hellgate’s hands were filled with small wounds, he seemed to know feel anything from it as he looked up and went after the Door to Heaven as the sea of blood pushed him up.

Garen crawled out of the crater as the blue light around his body spread out.

Hehehehe…

He suddenly laughed crazily as he realized he’s in a dire state. Wasn’t this kind of life that he had been yearned for?

To bet everything that he had and enjoy the battle of life or death as he met a stronger foe.

Didn’t he want to see the world from the peak when he started practicing martial arts?

"This is it… This is it…!!" He muttered as he could feel that his blood is boiling.

A strong fusion of energy poured out from the seed of Living Secret Technique and with him as the epicenter, cold air leaked out from his and spread across a few hundred meters, freezing everything and turned the land into blue.

As the ice and metal Living Secret Technique merged together, it didn’t bring forth a stronger Living Secret Technique but a system that was more suitable to him.

Garen had finally reached the final phase of merging Secret Techniques as he relied on his past experience and the wealth given by the King of Ender.

However, this was also where countless of peak form five totem users failed.

He raised his head up and looked at Hellgate in the sky.

Garen suddenly disappeared from the ground.

As if it was their plan, the other two flew towards the Hellgate as well.

Kaboom!!

Four of them collided against each other and a spherical shockwave spread out with them as the epicenter.

This shockwave disintegrated countless of limbs and the fleshes flew up and rained down.

At that instant, the three attackers’ robe was torn into pieces and their bodies were showed towards every totem users.

The Divine God Palace Master’s left arms was completely gone and one section of his right knees had disappeared, leaving behind a messy injury.

The Cthulhu King’s head was split into half vertically and one could see the sky behind his head. His brain was almost split into half.

One of Garen’s eyes exploded, leaving behind a bloody hole. His body was filled with countless of small holes but it was frozen by the ice crystals to prevent any major loss of blood.

In that instant, the three of them threw everything they had towards Hellgate.

Two puffs of bloody mist leaked out from Hellgate’s waist as his face turned pale.

************

Kovitan Kingdom, which was far away.

Hathaway held onto her mouth as she tried her best not to scream. She could feel Danielle holding her arms tightly.

"That’s.. Brother.. Garen.." Danielle muttered.

Hathaway thought that Hellgate had recognized someone wrongly as Garen was just a form four totem users in everyone’s perspective and was nowhere near the peak of form five.

She no longer had any doubt as the black robe was torn into pieces.

It was indeed Garen. Unknowingly, he had reached the peak of the world.

However, she would rather Garen to be a form four as this cruel battle was not something someone in their mid twenties should experience…

A sense of pride and complicated feelings kept conflicting against each other.

Hathaway stared closely at the water mirror in the sky and realized that the one eyed man was smiling. He was smiling!

He was enjoying such a cruel battle.

It was something that came from within. It was his deepest emotion.

*********

At the other corner of the Kingdom.

The princess and the remaining Gargantuans and elite totem users gathered together.

No one spoke a word as the oval shaped water mirror floating in the long table was broadcasting the horrifying battle in the Ender Kingdom.

The princess held the fan tightly in her hand as sweat had completely filled her hand. She stared closely at the water mirror and didn’t want to miss out any single detail.

As she looked at the face of this young and crazy man, she suddenly felt scared as she didn’t expect the man whom she thought she knew so very well had hidden such an incredible strength.

As she recalled the interactions with Garen in the past, she felt very conflicted.

A sense of fear and complicated feelings kept appearing inside her heart.

She looked at the remaining two Gargantuans and Grand Duke Cody was horrified.

As they’re fighting against each other to obtain power and authority, that young man had unknowingly surpassed them and obtained a very powerful strength.

He was able to fight side by side with the Nest Leader Divine God Palace Master and the strongest person in the Cthulhuism Society, Cthulhu King.

All of them had terrifying powers.

Grand Duke Benoc’s expression was calm but he was holding the arm rest tightly to the point that the metal arm rest had a mark on it.

Everyone didn’t know what to feel as they didn’t expect that the young genius who once stood side by side with them in terms of strength had far surpassed them in such a short time.

Chapter 542: World 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the Black Swamp Palace

Countless of disciples and guardians had walked out of the palace and looked at the water mirror in the sky.

Lala held her arms tightly and shivered as she looked at the horrifying battle in the sky. All she prayed for was that Garen would survive in the battle.

Groups of disciples in the Black Swamp Palace was passionately observing this world class battle as it’s the battle that decided the fate of this world. As the Palace Master’s figure appeared in the screen, everyone’s spirit had engulfed the whole palace.

These disciples felt an immense proud as they’re different from the others. They grouped themselves into two or three crowds and gathered at the balcony, entrance of the palace, residences, gardens, public, etc. In that instant, everyone was looking up at the water mirror in the sky.

Some prayed, some shouted loudly and some were in complete rage. All the disciples of the Black Swamp Palace were cheering at the final battle in different ways.

Ivycius and Demon Phoenix stood together with the elders.

None of them spoke. Excluding Ivycius and Demon Phoenix, everyone’s face turned pale as they’re oppressed by the immense strength displayed from within.

Some unconsciously brought themselves into the battle as they started to shiver and almost vomited blood as well.

In this level of battle, it’s best to not understand at all as those who were able to understand aura and yet unable to resist it were in the most trouble. They could feel the immense amount of strength and those strength were able to reach them mentally from afar.

The battle inside the monitor had far surpassed everyone’s imagination. It wasn’t a battle for a mere mortal but a legendary battle told in the folklore!

The black rain in the sky dropped harder.

The holy music that appeared once in a while had another voice mixed within it.

"Death! Death!!"

"Death is eternal!!"

It sounded like the whistle of the wind or the sound of the droplet.

The Ultimate Protection in the Kovitan Empire’s skies trembled as ripples appear one after the other as if there was a strong force hitting on it continuously.

**********

Jesicca held goth tightly as they looked at the battle in the sky.

Those four people had went insane as everytime they collided against each other, the earth shattered and the sky roared.

Goth held his fist so tight that his nails almost pierced through his skin. He could also feel Jessica looking at him as well.

An explosion could be heard and countless of hand columns were torn apart.

With the Hellgate as the epicenter, the trio was pushed down to the ground.

One of them were pushed towards the both of them.

It was Garen!

Goth could clearly see that Hellgate purposely sent Garen to his location.

Garen was hit by the giant dark red arm as he crashed onto the ground.

The ground trembled as countless of dirts floated up into the air.

He cough a few times, took out a silver bottle from his body and immediately drank it.

His injury was beyond serious but a sense of excitement kept flowing out from him.

Garen panted as he started to smile.

He could feel that the Seed of Strength inside his body raised every time he fought. Fighting against Hellgate was like walking on a very thin thread where he would die if he were careless.

At this moment, the hand in the Monolith City finally broke down.

Boom!

One hand broke apart and fall onto the ground.

Then the next one followed along.

The second piece, third piece.. The tenth piece…

More and more hand broke apart and they weren’t able to resist the strength from the Door to Heaven.

Even if it were to strength of the Eternal Night Palace and Hellgate, it was their limit to be able to hold onto it for this long.

It was forbidden to obtain a strength that was able to pull out the Door to Heaven and now this amount of strength wasn’t able to hold on any longer.

"Heh… Hehe…" Garen couldn't stop laughing.

He wasn’t sure how the other two were doing but he almost succeeded.

"No!!" Hellgate covered the injury in his waist and the sea of blood behind him rose once more, pushing him to the Door to Heaven.

"Die!!"

Divine God Palace Master stroke out a green light and stabbed the back of Hellgate.

The Cthulhu King had exhausted all of his strength and the magic mirror on his hand had no light coming out from it. His entire condition was dire and weak as he laid inside the crater, unable to move and all he could do was to look at the final battle in the sky.

Garen got up and the black halberd in his hand transformed into a wheel of black crescent. The Living Secret Technique had almost reached its edge as he kept battling.

As he’s near the edge of surpassing Hellgate, Garen’s intelligent attribute started to spin and countless of inspiration kept entering into his brain.

Thousands of potential points that he had accumulated inside the ancient ruins started to drop at an incredible rate as if the rise of the Living Secret Technique required countless of potential points.

Garen sort of understood that Potential points can be used to replace the time to learn the Secret Technique and the strengths that he needed can be obtained by Potential points. If he were to really encounter a threshold where there were no tiers, the potential points would be useless.

In that instant, the convergence energy within him started tot shrink as the Ice Secret Technique and Metal Secret Technique kept fusing with each other, forming a small seed at great speed.

The speed were then planted deep into his soul and he could feel that his soul was flying. It felt comfortable and was free from everything.

"This is it… This is it… Hahahaha!!!" Garen started laughing and the whole sky was filled with his laughter.

Jessica and Goth stood behind Garen, who noticed their presence and ensure that his aura didn’t hurt them.

Goth’s expression was strange as he looked at Garen’s back, as if he wanted to say something. Jessica had left everything behind as he didn’t want to lose her best friend because of the tragedy in the past.

"Becareful Garen!! Goth wants to kill you!!" Jessica suddenly shouted as she shielded Garen with her body while facing Goth.

Garen was stunned and his mind went blank.

Garen who was currently at the most crucial part of promotion felt it and was about to turn around.

Stab!

A black dagger-liked being was stabbed into Garen’s back by Jessica. The dagger instantly twisted like a snake and drilled into Garen’s waist.

Goth’s mind went blank as his pupil reflected Jessica’s twisted smile.

Garen was stunned as well as he pressed onto his waist with one of his hand.

Boom!!

A hole was blasted in his waist and fresh blood and flesh flew everywhere. A hole appeared in his abdomen and a snake flew out as it went towards Hellgate. However, Garen caught it with one of his hand and snapped it into two pieces.

Garen walked a few steps to the front as he stared at his abdomen.

He was interrupted at the most crucial moment during his promotion. In that instant, the seed of the Living Secret Technique became unstable and the original bloodline was obstructed and the damage was severe.

Ugh….. Agh..!!!

He raised his head up and roared.

With him at the epicenter, a shockwave was blasted out.

Jessica was the first one to be sent flying off. Together with Goth, both of them were sent flying off as if they were hit by something big.

Goth’s vision turned blur as he tried to gain control of the situation and tried to reach out his hand and grab Jessica but she was falling from the sky slowly.

He could hear Garen’s agony as he was enraged and couldn’t believe of the betrayal!

"Hehehe. Die!! Die die die!! All of you should die!! Hahaha!!" Jessica started to laugh madly in the sky as her face was filled with hopelessness and bitterness and yet she didn’t realize her face was filled with tears.

Boom!

Jessica’s body was slammed onto a stone pillar and her head was pierced by a sharp stone and she instantly stopped breathing.

Thud!

Goth finally kneeled down and cried as he covered his face with his hands.

The sky was then lightened by a circle of green ring.

The whole sky was instantly brightened up.

The Divine God Palace Master’s chest was deformed by the attack and fall into the sea of blood.

Hellgate panted as he moved his attention onto Garen.

No one knew when, but Garen stopped shouting.

He was calm and standing still.

The bloody hole in his abdomen was about the size of a fist and one could clearly see the black ground behind him. However the whole was being filled by countless of red ice crystal.

The attribute pane underneath his vision was reacting crazily.

In the skill pane, The Black Water True Technique was something like of an unnamed Living Secret Technique. As the Living Secret Technique was learnt, even if it’s not fully learnt, countless of messages appeared.

The messages were frozen by a blue fluid as it kept gathering on the skill pane, forming a deep blue whirlpool.

A clear name appeared inside Garen’s mind.

It was a name automatically derived after merging with the Living Secret Technique.

He opened his lips.

The icy blue whirlpool stopped rotating as it formed into a complicated and strong symbol.

A blue icy crystal halberd appeared behind him, aiming at Hellgate.

Hah!

Garen’s eye was filled with icy blue fire that completely covered his pupil and he could only see two icy blue smoke.

Northern… Trident Frost-Fire True Water technique!!

Garen muttered softly.

The name of the Living Secret Technique carried a mysterious magic power. As he softly muttered it, a giant dark blue whirlpool appeared behind Garen.

It was a huge whirlpool constructed with countless of blue crystal halberds.

The halberds were mixed together into the whirlpool like an exquisite gear as it moved slowly.

Garen looked up and stared at Hellgate.

Go!!!

In that instant, a deafening chirp soared into the sky.

Countless of icy blue halberd soared into the sky from Garen’s back and the deafening chirp was created by the countless of sonic boom as the halberd moved forward.

"This is my dream… my only dream!!" Hellgate muttered as his expression became firm and his gaze, crazy.

He raised up both of his hands.

Countless of icy blue halberd rushed towards him and within the stream of halbert, Garen’s figure appeared and with a halberd in his hand, he stabbed forward.

"Towld!!!"

Hellgate started laughing as he opened his hand, as if he was welcoming something.

Thud!!!

The sea of blood in the middle of the sky exploded and all of the dark red hands broke apart and assimilated into the sea of blood.

The sky was completely dyed in red.

As they were covered in fresh blood, Hellgate looked at Garen, the person who had just entered form six and destroyed what he had built.

This was the peak of the world and no one could see them through the sea of blood.

"Can you accept one of my request?" Hellgate smiled gently as his body was pierced through by Garen’s halbert. His body was slowly disintegrating into pool of fresh blood starting from his legs.

Garen kept quiet for a moment.

"Say it out."

Hellgate smiled happily.

"Please go into the Door to Heaven in my stead. I want to know what’s inside, what’s inside…"

Garen was stunned.

"That’s my only dream…"

Hellgate smiled as his body disintegrated while one of the red light flew in front of Garen.

It was a pure Secret Technique memory and it was a gift left behind by his opponent.

The word dream kept reverberating in his ears as Garen looked at the gift given by Hellgate.

Chapter 543: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dream.

The only thing Hellgate was going after all these while was his dream.

Garen used everything on his last attack. Although Hellgate was severely injured and had no energy left to pull the Door to Heaven, he still had the energy to deflect Garen’s crucial attack. However, he gave up and dissipated this strength to Garen so that he could have the opportunity to enter the Door to Heaven.

Kaboom!

Thunder roared as an arch of lightning flashed above his head.

Garen woke up from his unconsciousness. His abdomen was in pain and all of his body felt sour as his body was filled with countless of holes. He was like a deflated balloon, falling down from the sky.

He looked up and found out that the black clouds were dispersing.

The clear and white door went back into the clouds and soon returned to where it came from.

The wind whistled as it moved his ragged clothes up and down.

Garen hesitated for a moment but in the end he sighed.

He reached his hand out to take the red light ball. As his finger touched the ball, it instantly fused into his skin and disappeared.

All information regarding form six and its strongest inspiration, Living Secret Technique and its uses and understanding entered into Garen’s mind.

This was the last gift from the Hellgate.

Garen sighed as he looked at the Door to Heaven. In the end, he chose not to go for it.

The Door to Heaven’s changes would affect this world and he didn’t want to become the 2nd Hellgate.

Huu…

Suddenly, a rain poured and the black red rain disappeared as it was replaced by a normal transparent rain.

The Door to Heaven entered into the clouds and rain poured more and more heavily.

As the black cloud tumbled about, lightning could be constantly seen and thunder kept roaring.

The sea of blood on the ground disappeared quickly as Hellgate disappeared. As if it didn’t exist in the first place, revealing the remains of the Monolith City.

Garen floated in the sky as he deactivated all sorts of Secret techniques and totem energy, leaving nothing extraordinary flowing inside him.

He was merely floating in the middle of the sky as countless blood and halberd disappeared. As the dust settled, he quietly looked at the scenario from the top.

Monolith City was filled with corpse as the people from the Obscuro Society had left. What was left remaining in the Monolith City was the remaining totem users and citizens who came rushing back in as they witnessed their abandoned houses. Some were crying as they kneeled down, some were still shivering from the fear. However, most of them looked at at Garen and bowed slightly before helping the injured.

The Cthulhu King was carried out of the crater by the people from Cthulhuism Society and he seemed to be on his last breath.

Although Hellgate’s attack didn’t attack the physical bodies, it’s injured both side at the same time and even the nicknamed immortal Cthulhu King wasn’t able to avoid it.

He laid down onto the black stretcher as he looked at Garen who was descending. He opened his mouth but didn’t say anything in the end

No one noticed that the Divine God Palace Master had left the scene. He had left the place when the sea of blood disappeared and Hellgate being killed by Garen. As the Nest Leader, he would always be the enemy of the humans and with the biggest threat Hellgate being dead, he would be asking for death if he were to stay around any longer with his injury.

As he slowly descended to the ground, Garen looked around the area. He then looked at Goth, who seemed half dead and Jessica’s corpse not far away.

He didn’t know what to feel when Jessica was being used by Hellgate’s as an ambush as he left a huge dagger which had the strength of a form six. He also had successfully diverted his promotion as well.

If not for the potential points that were used to replace his life, any other totem users would’ve died no matter what.

The potential points had saved him once again and Jessica, who was used as an ambushed tool had injured herself in the process.

As he recalled the days with them, Garen felt complicated towards the whole situation.

Owh!

He vomited a pool of blood.

The fresh blood landed onto the ground and froze instantly.

The after effects of his injuries finally surfaced as he tried to suppress the condition with his Secret Technique forcefully. In the end, he couldn’t suppress if further.

Garen didn’t think much and immediately fly up and disappeared in the horizon.

The whole battlefield was in a dire state. As the situation calmed down, countless of totem users and soldiers formed a team and started the rescue mission.

The teams were lead by strong totem users as they went to investigate if Hellgate had truly died. They also had to face the remaining power from the Obscuro Society inside the city.

After Garen flew away.

Beckstone and his team who had arrived late walked out of the forest nearby the Monolith city. They looked at the broken city from afar as Beckstone slowly placed down the Earth Flower Heirloom. He was hiding inside the forest and used the Ancient Endor Heirloom to increased the trio’s strength during the battle to ensure that their will weren’t affected by their injuries.

It was the cooperation between him activating the Earth Flower and Master Noah from afar that managed to send these three attackers here.

Without this Heirloom, no one would be able to send these three here in such a short notice.

"Is it all over?" The girl in red armor beside Beckstone asked softly. He looked at the severely broken city as she couldn’t believe this was the damage caused by a few people.

As she looked at the corpses everywhere, she shivered and unconsciously held Beckstone’s arm tightly, as if this was the only way for her to find peace.

"Perhaps…" Beckstone shook his head as he sighed. "If that man isn’t the next Hellgate, perhaps everything will end soon."

"That man…" The red armored girl was worried but she didn’t say any word after that.

"Let’s go help the rescue teams." Beckstone tapped the girl’s arm as he walked towards the battlefield.

The earth that had turned black had cracks everywhere. The teams were moving in between as they looked for any survivors.

From afar, the Monolith City looked like a circular cake that was chipped away by mice as the whole city was filled with misery.

A rescue team leader stood at the edge of the crack as he looked at his members holding Goth up and placed him in a simply made stretcher.

"Although we’ve won this battle, we’ve sacrificed way too much…"

"Yes…" Another totem user nodded slowly. "At least half of the citizens didn’t manage to escape out of the city and the rough estimation on the death toll is sixty thousands, excluding the ones missing or had missing limbs."

"I wonder how many years Ender Kingdom require to fully recover from this battle…" The captain said.

"This isn’t the end." Totem user shook his head. "Those bastards from the Obscuro Society needs to be killed! We have to kill these crazy lots sooner or later!" He started to grit his teeth as he say so.

Cris of agony and pain could be heard from afar.

Although both of them were not citizens of the Ender Kingdom, they couldn’t help themselves but to feel pity as they saw the scene. This organization appeared because of them and these truth had made them outsiders realized that the world had view the Obscuro Society as the common enemy.

"Yea… we’re not done yet… This is just the beginning!" The team leader saw a corpses kneeling down as they protected their children. The hatred inside the children’s eye made him shiver.

He knew that in the near future, there would be another bloody battle between Ender Kingdom and Obscuro Society.

**********

The world was filled with joy.

No matter if it’s humans or nest leaders, everyone was celebrating. However, most people from the Ender Kingdom were holding a funeral. Some of them buried the dead while some only had tombs containing the personal items of the deceased. The forger who was forging the tombs had become the hottest occupation but they weren’t willing to earn these money. This was because they knew that the others required this money for something else other than sculpting a tomb.

Ender Kingdom, Kovitan and Daniela.

The already broken Eastern Continent was finally free.

From the existence of Obscuro Society to its downfall was nothing but a few years. However, they had caused so much havoc within these few years.

The capital of Ender Kingdom, a thousand year old city was completely destroyed. The elites from the Ender Kingdom was completely annihilated, where the strong ones were heavily injured and most of the citizens had passed away.

On the other hand, Kovitan had lost half of their land and could only move about inside the Ultimate Protection. As they’d saved some strength, they were able to reclaim some of the lands. However, this didn’t mean that they could recover the lost of half of their citizens. All kinds of industries and business flunk. Compared to the days of the past, they’re probably in the lost of millions of silver rumbs.

Daniela, the holy land was turned into an abyss when Hellgate fought with Phiroth. The country’s strength was less than ten percent and the place was claimed by the Cthulhuism Society. However, Cthulhu King said that he needed to isolate himself from the outside world to recover his injuries during the battle with Hellgate. His soul was seriously damaged and he had overused the magic mirror as well. This made him sacrificed a lot and the Cthulhu King was on the verge of dying due to the consecutive major attack from the Hellgate. Hence he could only isolate himself and no one knew how long it would take for him to completely recover.

Chapter 544: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After Divine God Palace Master's Sun God King‘s mysterious disappearance, all the hideout masters automatically retreated into the underground.

The underground had been cleared out by Hellgate in secret ages ago, regardless of the occupants' species. They had all been exterminated by Hellgate's strong plague, the top-tiered experts had been secretly eradicated after Hellgate's breakthrough, and mankind's strongest organization: Elder's Hall had been annihilated.

It could be said that the underground had been emptied out under the leadership of Divine God Palace Master, and the lords of the hideouts have avoided the fight over resources with the humans on the surface. Instead, they began excavating the underground and formed an independent force to be reckoned with.

All that was left on top were some mutant creatures and low-level creatures that had no intelligence. These creatures were all creatures that were considered to be trash in the eyes of the hideout leaders.

As the time passed, the aftermath of the destruction of the Door to Heaven began to show.

No matter if it was totem users, or even mutant creatures, all the totem powers and totem's light began to deteriorate rapidly. The speed at which it deteriorated was similar to unplugging the sinkhole in a pool, it formed a large whirlpool that leaked all the unnatural powers.

This war at the Door of Heaven had been coined the term "Battle of Heavens" by historians of many countries. Harp players and the musicians have all made songs out of this war, and songs and poems were uncountable, for a time after the war broke out, an inexplicable literary revolution happened.

The corresponding opera, drama, and novels have also come into being.

Whereas the three top-tiered experts have never appeared anymore after the war broke out, people had been exaggerating the myths due to the very same reason, and they became the symbols of the world's strongest existence.

**********************

As the time passed quickly.

50 years have passed in the blink of an eye.

The Monolith City which fell into ruins was now full of greenery and flowers. The crumbled walls were now densely packed with moss.

Those who came to admire its history could not help but to be mesmerized and prolong their stay, which spurred a lot of franchised hotel businesses.

Due to the aftereffects of the way, Monolith City was full of irregularly sized cracks and rumbles and was no longer suitable to be rebuilt as a capital. Conversely, a large number of tourists have been attracted to visit this ruins of the great war, whereas the plains outside the city were developed to be a tourism-centric city called the Monolith Town.

In the town was a white square, and in the middle of it was the memorial of the people's heroes. It was erected in memory of the three King-level experts' noble life stories which have almost become a myth at this point, as well as the countless innocent lives of civilians and totem users lost in this war.

The evening light dyed the entire square yellow.

On the side of a flower bush, a bearded tour guide is enthusiastically introducing the accounts of the things that happened 50 years ago to the tourists.

"... the peace and serenity that we enjoy today were largely attributed to the aftermath of the Battle of the Heavens. Sun God King, Cthulhu King, Northern King, the three King-Level experts have fought here, for their own principles, the ten of thousands of subordinates and subjects behind them, they chose to risk their lives to stop Hellgate from annihilating the entire world. That war shook the heaven and earth, even the thousand-year-old Monolith City which was the capital trembled in fear from that war. The heavens howled and the earth was covered in scars; that immense power was absurd, like a legend. According to the account of one lucky survivor's memories, the situation then was….."

"Who would believe it.. Haha.." some of the tourists began laughing softly, the laughter was deeply hurtful towards tour guides. As it contained a large amount of disbelief, sarcasm, and a suspicion that couldn't be refuted.

"It is now the technological era, totems? Could this pseudoscience reach this level?" someone continued saying

"I guess the heroes were memorialized, things like totems, I have tried a few activation methods, but there weren't many effects, aside from strengthening your body. Whereas the Secret Techniques excavated from the ruins were not bad, the combat techniques were all very practical."

"Is it? I had just realized too, previously I have been learning Secret Technique from a teacher, it was apparently a family heirloom, it was indeed very practical."

"How does a Secret Technique look like in real life? I have only read about them in novels."

The group of tourists have now taken an independent topic as the core of the discussion and were socializing.

This caused the tour guide in front of them to speechlessly shake his head this is not the first batch that was like this. To disbelieve the Battle of the Heavens, have been the common consensus among the tourists of recent years.

They originally had some hesitation but when they reached the actual ruins, they immediately stopped believing it completely.

There wasn't any other reason, but the ruins looked too terrifying.

Monolith City was a large capital with a population size over a million people and at the same time, they had a strong defensive reserve troop, to say that a war with only a few people had formed this horrifying scene, nobody would have believed it.

Totems? Totem Users?

Even if such a thing really existed in the history, it could barely compete against the increasingly powerful guns, bombs and cannons. It would probably be a legacy that is directly made obsolete by these technologies that grew stronger.

Moody among the tourist group believed it, that this battleground was the aftermath of a few people's doing. Everyone else believed that this tragic scene was the result of the explosion of countless explosives. It was undeniable that the three King-Level figures had a part in this war, but those armies and subordinates were the actual heroes that should be respected.

This was especially so in the recent years when the affected armies' descendants' living conditions were exposed, and many countries began introspecting it.

As the tour guides were in deep thoughts, he brought the tourists around the ruins of Monolith City according to his routine. Now that East Continent has tens of countries of varying size, almost all of the tourists came over to look at the historical site and achievements, the locals that were born and raised in the town could actually make a relaxing, decent living out of being a tour guide.

"Caddy! Valerie and the rest have already finished their class, are you done yet?" A middle-aged man shouted from afar as he stood in front of a bar, waving towards the tour guide. That's the man whom he used to play cards with, Jack, both their sons were studying in the same boarding school. Coincidentally, it was weekends today, so he should be fetching the child home.

"Almost done!" The tour guide replied. "Give me a minute!"

"Alright!"

The tour guide brought the tourists to the final spot of the day, and then hurriedly met up with the middle-aged man.

As the day fell into dusk, it was getting late.

"Hey! Little Beck! How's life in school?"

"It was good. I can take care of myself." A young boy, aged 11 with silver hair and of gangly height replied.

The father and son walked out amidst the packed crowd which was leaving school, and they walked home while holding hands.

"Is mom alright?" Beck had a vibe of a young clan leader, with his little bag and his milky white skin, as he raised his eyebrows and asked.

"She has to work overtime today, perhaps she will be going home late, as there was a dinner party that needed planning. But Old Beck and Lady Cyan will be coming today, they said that they want to visit their favorite grandson. I guess Lady is already in the kitchen working on your favorite cookie." the tour guide laughed.

"Really? I meant to say since before, that that type of cookie is really too sweet."

"But that's the tender loving care of your grandmother."

"But if it's too sweet, it's not good for the teeth, isn't that what you said?"

"Um…."

"I guess I should learn how to politely refuse." Little Beck thought deeply while touching his chin.

The father and son discussed along the way and played all the way home.

The grandfather with a full head of grey hair, Old Beck was reading the newspaper, whereas Lady Cyan was indeed in the kitchen. This young-hearted lady in red attire came rushing out with a large smile on her face and gave Little Beck a smooch after hugging him.

"Oh, my dear Little Beck I really hope you never grow up, and stay this cute eternally."

"Please refrain from using adjectives like cute to describe your grandson, it is insulting to my character." Little Beck, whose full name was Jack Beck struggled.

"Alright, alright, stop messing around." The grandpa who sat on the sofa put down his newspaper, he looked at that brat with a stern face. " Looks like it's been a while since we had messaging contacts, your thoughts have been misled. Sleep with me tonight, I shall correct your recent thought process."

"By using your experiences? That's great! There're more great stories!" Little Beck threw his bag aside and cheered loudly.

"Those are not stories!" Grandpa's face turned stern.

"Yes yes, those are true accounts, it is your precious adventure, containing countless life's wisdom!" Little Beck immediately followed suit.

"Speaking of which, dad, every time you told this brat a story, it always felt so real…" the tour guide was asking softly beside him.

"Those were your geezer's personal experience! At that time, there weren't any cannons or missiles, totem users were the true force to be reckoned with. Haven't you been repeating the Battle of the Heavens daily? Why would you still ask such childish questions?" the old man's face turned serious.

"Alright, alright, Beckstone you're always this emotional about this topic, those things were of the past, the history, speak less and take care of that heart of yours." Lady Cyan Berlina was advising with laughter on the side.

"What did you say when you proposed to me? Didn't you fell heads over heels over my immense strength and cool aura…" Beckstone looked at his old partner's warming smile, he suddenly felt guilty and gradually spoke softly.

"Looks like someone has been getting too much pocket money.. Hahaha…." Berlina still had that warm homely face.

"Be fearless!" Little Beck suddenly shouted.

"Correct! Be fearless!!" the duo then started sprinting away.

Beckstone circled around while pulling his grandson, but he was internally reminiscing the times of fire and fury.

There's nobody who had it clearer than him.. The Battle of the Heavens among the three kings were indeed from the history.

Even though the aftermath of the destruction of Heaven's Door had led to the nearly complete annihilation of the totem users, the world could no longer see the existence of totem's power and totem's light. But only the elderly who survived that era could truly understand the near-mythical era had actually happened.

Following the weakening of the totem's power, the immense power of Form 5 he was once proud of have now been reduced to a regular Form 1 totem users' totem's power, which could only be used to conjure up some small tactics like a trick.

Furthermore, people who had no totem's power were completely unable to perceive the existence of the said tactics and tricks..

Beckstone had a premonition that the Heaven's Door had been some sort of a living object, as after it recognized the immense threat of the totem's power, it began consciously altering the world and let this power slowly go extinct.

" I wonder how the enemies are doing now…." without him knowing, he began thinking about the past again.

"Grandpa, quick, show me some new tricks!" little Beck called out mysteriously.

The world would have changed in the end…

Chapter 545: Change 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the new Kovitan capital, Escalvate.

In the clear blue sky, flocks of birds in V-shaped formations soared through the air.

"Sister, have you take your medication?"

In an old but lavish looking white building.

An old lady with a head full of white hair was carrying a grocery basket as she ascended the flight of stairs. She took out her keys to unlock the door and walked into a wide living hall.

"Madam Dani." a maid in white skirts stood by the door as she greeted the old lady.

"Thank you for the hard work, Little Jenny " Dani greeted the maid warmly.

"Another quiet day…" a coarse elderly voice was heard from the study room near the living room.

Dani laughed after hearing the voice and handed the basket to the maid before walking towards the study room located at the deepest corner of the living hall.

An old lady full of white hair with a graceful figure was sitting in a red rocking chair by the full-length curtains near the study room.

Her face was wrinkled but her eyes were calm and serene, with no traces of the pessimism and low-spiritedness of an elderly.

"Sister, I bought your favorite goby fish. I saw someone foraging it from the wilds, so I bought all of it since it's fresh." Dani said as she exerted large amounts of force to push open the curtains.

"Aren't you supposed to go to the palace festive? Why are you free to come over here?" the lady who sat on the rocking chair asked softly.

"Isn't it because of my worry?" Dani laughed. "Once I saw that you left your medication at my place, I immediately sent them over."

She took a chair and sat next to her sister, Hathaway. The sisters gazed at the bright blue sky beyond the window, enjoying the serenity.

"Speaking of which, it has already been more than 50 years, time really does fly in the blink of an eye." Hathaway sighed. " I wonder how is he now, there hasn't been any news from the palace."

"It was said that due to the aftermath of the battle, he is still recovering." Dani nodded, her eyes solemn. What kind of injuries would take 50 years to recover? They were afraid they were injuries that would be deemed terminal… She dared not speak of such words though, as she was worried that her sister's last hopes would be extinguished.

After fifty years, what used to be the powerful and influential Black Swamp Palace was now the world's second largest hybrid university in the new capital.

After the world's totem power was weakened to the brink of extinction, the Black Swamp Palace had invited former totem users and swiftly converted into a government-run university. Using their core martial techniques' powerful reputation, they have established their reputation.

In these years, numerous talented disciples have been admitted into the university, among them were the top-tiered prodigy Ansapello who became one of the few martial arts masters of the world. After continuous effort, he was hired as the leader of the Kovitan Empire's Military Headquarters. He even opened up a separate martial arts school, which was widely available worldwide, called the Pure Hearted Fist and had many disciples under him.

Aside from that, that girl called Pefalia had established the Blackbird Double-Handed Weapons Combat school after she left the school, and it too spread everywhere.

There were actually many more talents that graduated from Black Swamp Palace that had established their own careers and had expanded into different industries, obtaining decent achievements of their own. Even the least of them were at least industry experts.

Hence, there will be a moderate sized festive held in the entire new capital.

"Has Ansapello dropped by recently?" Dani suddenly asked

"Why? That brat visited me a few days back." Hathaway had a very good impression towards that genius who respected her. Ever since Garen had disappeared, he remained respectful towards her even through the darkest of times in the Black Swamp Palace. Even though he had already graduated, he still tried his best to help his fellow students and seniors. Though he looked arrogant, he was actually a responsible person.

"That brat has recently proposed a resolution in the Senate, it's slightly controversial… as the nation grows stronger in recent years, it seems that the boy is becoming ambitious again." Dani frown as she spoke.

"What did Ivy and Skyharp think about it?"

"It's neutral I suppose. They didn't overtly reject nor support." Dani shook her head.

"Then it's best that I don't express my opinions. The matters of the country are not something we can judge with our personal eyes. As our position differs, our perspective may differ too." Hathaway said as she shook her head. "Right, how's that brat at your place doing?"

"Same old, same old, he brought his family for a vacation at West Continent, leaving behind this lonely old woman alone." Dani started complaining. She lifted her head and saw her sister's face that was no longer comparable to her youth, and her heart shivered.

"What about you, sister? Was it worth it, waiting for that person for so many years?"

"There's nothing unworthy about it, I've grown used to waiting all these years. Plus, I don't feel lonely at all, Lala, Ivy, Angel, Sylvia and the rest have always been visiting me. With so many friends around me, what else is there to feel unworthy about?" Hathaway had remained single even though she had been wildly popular among men when she was young. They had all been turned down politely, whereas her sister Dani had found a decent man to marry, and her family was now one of the top-tiered nobles in Kovitan. She had two sons and 5-6 grandchildren, which made every gathering a rowdy and warm one.

In these years, the Grand Princess has inherited the title of Queen and become the honorary symbol of spirit in the Royal Family. The actual administration of the country still fell upon the Senate that was composed by the four giant influences. Among that, Black Swamp Palace took two seats, which one would consider to be the biggest influence in the entire Kovitan. Aside from that was the Grand Duke Benoc, who represented the Grand Princess, now the current Queen, as well as an organization representing the civilians. Grand Duke Cody had long been eliminated, hence his whereabouts were unknown.

Even after the fall of totem users, the radio that had been developed all those years ago still had very holistic functions; its core still used resonance technique and not totem's power, hence its usability was not affected.

This had expedited the spread of messages within this world, in the midst of the high speed, high volume message transmission, technology had also abruptly improved at an exponential rate. Countless forgers from the totem world had migrated to scientific research and used their previous knowledge as a basis for many breakthrough theories and research results that took the world by storm.

In merely fifty years, the technology evolved from the original firearms and steam engine locomotives up to the biplane, a wide variety of cannons, tanks and civilian-friendly technology, born as the results of multiple conflicts.

With giant ferries traversing between two continents, countless water bodies have been explored.

In the fifty years worth of recovery, the global population had dramatically increased under each country's strong push for policies encouraging population growth.

At the same time each technology continued its growth, the medical standards have improved tremendously. What used to be specially used by totem users, such as microscopes, incubators, training equipment and the like have all been converted for medical purposes. Mankind's birth mortality rate had decreased drastically and everything was developing at an unprecedented rate.

****************************

In a deep sea trench of North Pole.

An immense blue ice mountain stood upon the entrance to an abyssal trench.

In the deepest part of the ice mountain were some tiny spaces, and there was actually a man-made underwater tunnel and plaza. What used to be a place that isolated water had been ruptured and flooded with water and shards of ice.

The plaza was dark with a hue of blue, minus a swarm of illuminating jellyfish floating through slowly, their bodies expanding and shrinking. The pale blue glow emitted by the swarm was calming and serene.

Oddly enough, these jellyfishes were different from jellyfishes from the outer world; the ends of their tentacles emitted a faint purplish-blue light.

Soon, a school of anchovies swam through the plaza in circling motions, they also have the similar purplish-blue hue on their sharp teeth, which seemed unusually ferocious.

This was the world-renowned Deadly Poison Sea Territory. It didn't mean that the seawater itself was poisonous, but rather the species inhabiting it, as for unknown reasons, all the species here carried some lethal form of poison.

The Deadly Poison Sea Territory was considered famous in the North Pole, and there would be a certain amount of tourists expected to visit here even though the sea creatures here could not be consumed. Instead, their unique appearances left the tourists mesmerized.

Under the ice mountain deep within the trench.

It had been many years since anyone had entered this realm.

Ever since the totem's power had been destroyed, there hasn't been any human capable of traversing such depth.

This was the deepest trench in the entire North Pole, tens of thousand meters deep. After repeated measurements done in the recent years, this trench was rated one of the deepest existing trenches, and second place in terms of depth.

At the deepest parts of the trench, a faint crackling sound could be heard from the inside of the odd ice mountain's serene pitch darkness.

"How long has it been…."

Garen slowly woke up from his deep slumber.

As he opened his eyes, his surrounding was still the same blue ice layer. This ice was from his body, forming a cryogenic hibernation area.

Outside the icy layer, the migrating poisonous jellyfish floated by once again, Garen suddenly had a flash of realization.

"Has it already been another ten years?" He mumbled. When that swarm of jellyfish passed through this area once every decade, up to this point, he had already witnessed it 5 times.

"Fifty years already?" Garen's head had some delayed memory recalling. Not being awake for exactly ten years, always being in the state of recovery, it was normal for him to be unable to recall something immediately after waking up suddenly.

After the last time where Ivy, Skyharp and the rest of the elders came to visit thirty years ago, there hasn't been anyone who'd come to this underwater trench.

The water isolation plaza that was supported by totem's power had also been ruptured, and it had turned into a wonderland for the underwater creatures.

There were already signs of the weakening of totem's power thirty years ago, and Ivy, who used to rely on his own power to come in, had to combine powers with the rest of the elders to forcefully come down.

That was the last time Garen had had any contact with humans outside..

In the later years, he relied on the special radio to contact the outside world, but then even the radio had run out of power and had broken. Since then, he'd always been alone…

The totem's powers' had been weakened, but Garen's body already had no totem's power, what replaced it was the brand new Living Secret Technique. This power was not affected by the destruction of Heaven's Door and had retained its immense power.

This was already beyond the realm of a totem user; to be breaking through into form 6.

Garen made a detailed scan of his own body's condition.

The Secret Techniques of his body had completely integrated, Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique was a technique that would have been no different from a normal Living Secret Technique, but due to the interruption by Hellgate's subordinates during the final advancement, it'd caused an anomaly on the technique's formation, which became an evil technique. Piling onto the side effects and heavy injuries sustained in the war, the Secret Technique put him into a deep slumber recovery status, each sleep lasting more than ten years.

Taking advantage of the immense pressure and extreme coldness as food and resource of the North Pole Deep Trench, it slowly recovered his body's injuries.

Alone in the vast deep sea, he stayed there for tens of years.

Even a totem user with a mind as calm as Garen, he couldn't help but fall into a state of mental disarray.

He checked his body's condition. In the final war where he killed Hellgate, the deed hadn't earned him any potential points. But instead, his attributes and talent underwent their first changes in history.

The real change was in the Attribute Pane.

"Strength 18. Agility 14. Vitality 14. Intelligence 12. Potential 0%. Soul limit 20."

Garen turned his gaze on his attribute pane and disregarded the large pile of complicated things at skill pane.

The Attribute Pane has undergone a huge change.

Chapter 546: Change 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

His strength had merely been 16 points before advancing to form 6, which means 2 points had been added.

Agility was at 12 points, increased by 2 points.

Vitality was also at 12 points, also an increment of 2 points.

Intelligence was the same, so there were no changes.

For the potential points to have silently fallen to 0, Garen believed he had a theory; after killing Hellgate, he didn't obtain any potential points, hence he didn't have any increments. Whereas ever since his closed training, the potential points had decreased during the process of recovery over the years. Obviously, the recovery of the body via Secret Technique was due to the consumption of the potential points.

Even though the Secret Technique absorbed the pressure and extreme cold to repair the body, the source of the power that was used to activate the recovery was ultimately the potential points.

The Secret Technique that morphed into an evil technique, any other totem user would have died from the self-detonation from this change. But Garen had enough potential points to spare to replace his life force. This was what allowed him to survive the harsh conditions of the deep sea.

After checking over himself carefully, Garen could feel that there was only a tiny part of his body that was completely repaired. It was obvious that the potential points had been completely exhausted, and he could only wake up from the deep recovery slumber when the Living Secret Technique lost its source.

As well as the last Soul Limit, though he was unaware what that was.

Garen frowned and looked over at the Soul Limit pane. A descriptive message then appeared in his head.

‘Soul limit is the highest limit of one's attributes. The life gene will increase its upper limits following one's natural physiological properties, this was innately decided, just like all other creatures, this is a limit bottlenecked by the flesh and blood given by their parents. Whereas the soul limit helps adjust the genetic limits beyond the congenital limit, perfectly reaching a higher realm and breaking through the innate shackles.'

Garen felt that this message had already been in his head originally, but was only activated when he paid attention to this place. This allowed him to confirm that this special ability was based off from his subconscious' generation of such immense ability. To be able to use his understanding of the knowledge and language systems to the fullest extent, he could collate and tap into the potential of the subconscious to maximize the use of external forces, accurately reflecting his status.

Hence, his abilities would continuously undergo changes alongside the expansion of his knowledge, though what he didn't know would not be preemptively shown. It was the same for the Soul Limit.

If that was the case, were his Soul Limit to be at 20 points, did it symbolize that all his attributes would be maximized at 20 points?

As he began to doubt, he decided not to pursue it further, as the messages from the subconscious feedback were reassuring.

His brain began to become active again as he woke up.

Garen's body moved slightly, and the ice layers around his body began melting.

While he waited for tens of years' worth of ice to melt, Garen checked on his body's conditions.

Living Secret Technique had broken through Form 6, which also meant it had reached its completion.

At the peak of completion of Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, it began circulating in cycles. There was a viscous icy qi which circulated throughout his blood vessels endlessly that made Garen's blood turn icy blue and carry an intense coldness.

Even his blood had the effect of intense cold. Garen couldn't help but feel very amused by such an odd sensation.

It was obvious that there was a lack of warmth in his body, his usual body temperature was at least negative 30 degrees, but his bodily functions and blood circulation were normal, and there were no discomforts.

This anomalous Living Secret Technique had circulated in his body, it also occasionally caused the cold stream move. It was very amusing.

When Garen looked into this Secret Technique in detail, excluding the odd, amusing sensations, the actual functional abilities could be categorized into systems, totaled into a few types. These abilities also included the abilities acquired after advancing into Form 6.

"Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique:

1 Control of Extreme Coldness, metal weaponry, fluid and Frost Fire, absolute control within a radius of three hundred meters.

2 Trident Lair, an unlimited barrage of tridents. Trident owner can simultaneously move to the location of the trident.

3 Ice Rejuvenation, slowly rejuvenate owner's injuries. Forms defensive ice plates to protect itself.

4 Form 6 combination power - weather manipulation, buffing from cloud formation, maximized scope of energy combination with an attribute source of their own properties, forming an advantageous ground."

These 4 abilities were the strong abilities of Form 6 Living Secrets that could manipulate weather.

To Garen, these abilities weren't that important, what he cared more about were the changes in his Attribute Pane. Entering Form 6 may seem like a huge feat, but in reality, most of the offensive techniques relied on the condensation of external power.

There weren't many changes to his own body. That was probably why his own body's attributes haven't improved much.

Aside from that, Garen realized that there was an ability that wasn't part of the list of abilities.

Origin Seed of Living Secret Techniques.

This ability allowed the Living Secret Techniques to be completely recondensed as a soul seed, returning to a state of inactivity and stored into the deepest parts of your consciousness.

Subconsciously, Garen felt that this ability could have a pivotal function. So he carefully made a mental note about this.

The icicles had finally melted completely…

Garen slowly walked out from the sky towering ice pillar, as both his legs slowly stepped down on the ice plaza.

His surroundings were dark and there was only some faint blue luminescence from the ice, dyeing the entire area blue.

The igloos on the plaza were still here, except there was nobody living here anymore; Ivycius and Skyharp have already left for the surface as they could not withstand the immense cold and pressure.

Even all the experts from the Seven Knights' Tower had retreated, leaving him here alone.

As Garen moved around the plaza alone, even though there was no totem's power providing him with oxygen, using his strong manipulation of water, he could use precision controls to obtain enough oxygen for his consumption.

Garen extended his hands, and slowly touched the rough surface of the igloo, and that realistic touch sensation caused him to shudder for a moment.

In the tens of years of inanimation, aside from his hearing and vision, the rest of the senses had been basically unused, and now that they were reactivated, this long-lost feeling made Garen tremble without realizing it.

After some time, Garen pulled back.

"Totem's power has indeed disappeared…" He can feel the empty void of totem's power.

Totem's power used to be inside all living things. While the seawater now has a feeling of unprecedented purity, there wasn't a speck of unnatural powers.

"This is infinitely similar to my previous world…" Garen suddenly had this thought.

He floated upwards slowly, swimming towards the surface like a slow fish.

AT this point, two giant green light bulbs lit up in a large round cave hidden between a layer of ice in a dark corner on Garen's far right.

It was a deep-sea octopus king which spanned over a hundred meters. It had an odd green pair of eyeballs, and as its giant tentacles swiftly latched onto the walls, with a strong pull, its entire body suddenly shrunk and it shot out of the cave like an arrow.

The octopus king took no effort to reach Garen, but it had no hostility, but instead, it was an uncontrollable desire to get closer to Garen.

Its giant head was lowered, indicating that it wanted Garen to sit on it.

Garen smiled gently, and lightly sat on the octopus' head. Its head was about thirty meters wide, Garen looked like a little pebble on it, it seemed ordinary.

With its eight tentacles propelling it, the octopus and man swiftly glided upwards.

As it approached the surface of the ocean, the water temperature increased as well, and the seawater around it became brighter.

Garen looked up towards the surface, that clear layer of blue, from dark blue, to light blue until the white light on the surface of the sea. Layer by layer, it slowly ascended. But without him realizing, the octopus king stopped ascending.

It was actually a deep-sea creature, and the water temperature here was already the limit that it could bear. Ascending any further would mean a boiling hot sensation for it, so it could only stay here.

Garen patted its head, and he leapt off, swiftly swimming towards the surface.

Splash!!

He shot out of the water suddenly.

The squawks of the seagulls, the splashing sound of the waves, as well as the blow of the whale from a place far away.

All these things have led Garen into an inexplicably touched state.

For in that instance, he felt the same sensation as transmigrating into a new world, just like the first time he got to this world, everything looked so clear and elegant.

The skies were crystal clear, and as he basked in the sun, a warm sensation was felt for a moment before it was cooled by the sea breeze.

As the seawater around him rippled, there were pools of white bubbles floating on it.

As he looked around, there was only seemingly endless water on the horizon, as though the entire world was nothing but ocean.

With a leap, he swiftly sprung out of the water and gently landed. The seawater under his feet freezes instantaneously and formed a sturdy white float, supporting Garen’s weight.

He stood upon the piece of ice about a meter wide as he surveyed the skies and his surroundings.

The air around him had zero traces of totem's power.

Chapter 547: Years 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kovitan Kingdom

Around the mountains surrounding the Kingdom, there were many mushrooming towns and villages of different sizes.

These villages were centered around the Kingdom, with many farms and windmills everywhere. What used to be the Kingdom was no longer just a small area, but was now a gigantic city more than ten times larger than what it used to be.

Garen stood on the large white road far away, watching the huge city that used to be covered by the Ultimate Protection, his expression unnaturally calm.

The Ultimate Protection above his head had vanished completely a long time ago, and there was no longer any hint of totem power in the air.

He had come all the way here following the road, and of all the people he met along the way, basically none of them had any totem power.

There was vaguely the sound of radio music coming from a car repair shop by the road nearby, a little boy humming as he arranged the things inside the shop.

Coming straight at him were two bull carts with some unsold fruits. There was also a wooden plaque beside it, with a sign on it, with the words 'Square Stone Road' on the wooden plank pointing forward.

He had no intention of making a fuss, on his way here, after discovering the condition and general situation of the world, Garen knew that his face, that had not aged for several dozen years, represented something huge in this time.

He walked forward slowly, his steps looking slow but actually far faster than a normal person's walking speed.

After going through several little towns and villages outside the city, the sky had already gone dark outside, and the road that wound around the mountain, that had led into the Kingdom and was once heavily guarded, was not too far ahead of him.

There was nobody on guard anymore in the arrow guard tower, this was an era of peace, the arrow tower no longer posed any threat now that cannons were everywhere, and there was a sign that refused visitors on the door.

Finding a carriage that went uphill, Garen was kindly taken up the hill together with a talkative old carriage driver, he sort of hitchhiked, as the two of them chatted idly on the way.

The old man had also experienced the warring times, and believed completely in those matters regarding the totem users, and as he spoke, he kept on lamenting how the young people these days did not believe all that had happened back then, or how they did not respect the true history, so many of the older generation had seen the Kingdom under the Ultimate Protection with their own eyes back then.

Now many of the elderly had passed away, the totem power had wasted away, and this younger generation began to treat the legends of the totem users with incredulity, they could not believe that those could match up to the bombs and cannons they had now, and assumed that those were just the results of the fear and respect the previous generation had, allowing things to be slowly deified.

Garen kept nodding in time beside him, but also found out a lot about the situation in the Kingdom.

He found out that the Black Swamp Palace had somehow become a general university now, and that prodigy disciple that he had acknowledged back then was now one of the Black Swamp Palace's two most accomplished scholars, he even held the power in Kovitan, and was an extremely influential person throughout the whole country.

Garen could not help but sigh inwardly, the time had passed like an arrow, and to think that the little fella back then had now become a pillar of the country.

Just as it was about to become completely dark outside, Garen got off the carriage at the entrance to the Kingdom on top of the mountain, there were no more guards there, and instead there was a lot of traffic there, many people ascended the mountain at night in search of entertainments, and left the city at night to return to their own estates and cottages, interweaving and flowing like a stream at the city gates.

The house prices inside the Kingdom were too high, and many people who could not afford it had to stay outside, so over time, many small areas came up around and outside the Kingdom, halfway up the mountains, and the whole Kingdom had truly become a city within a city.

Garen walked towards the direction of his cousin Hathaway's place, completely familiar with the way.

Many new buildings had come up in new places around the roads and streets from several decades ago, and several places on the road had also been changed.

He still had to ask many people before he finally found the house Hathaway was living in.

At night, standing outside the house, Garen raised his head and looked up at the little bit of yellow lamplight on the second floor of the house. This world had no more totem power, and the technological pathway that had been developing slowly before was now blossoming.

With the foundations of the totem forgers, the development of science far exceeded everyone's imaginations, and electricity was created to meet the demand.

This was originally just an unstable source that totem users had stumbled across in their experiments, and after totem power disappeared, it had finally and rapidly replaced totems in their functions.

These forgers were also now what modern people called scientists.

The electric lightbulb was one of these scientists' newly-invented products.

Garen glanced at the guard post outside the house, there was a guard sleeping there.

Soundlessly, he darted, as though floating, past the guard post, leaping up and landing in the garden behind the metal gate.

Walking up to the door of the house, his palm jolted towards the door, and with a crisp 'ker-chak', the house door was opened lightly.

Sitting on the living room sofa, an old white-haired woman with a white towel on her knee entered his line of vision.

Maybe the sound of the door opening had attracted the old woman's attention, she put down the book in her hand, raised her head, and glanced over at him.

With that look, she never lowered her head again.

Garen was also staring dazedly at the old woman on the sofa, the fifty years of time had carved deep traces on her once-handsome features. Her previously smooth and fair skin had become wrinkled, loose skin. Her once bright and beautiful eyes, had also become the muddled, calm eyes of the elderly.

Her hair was snow-white, and Garen could only sense a vague hint of his cousin's image from that indescribable aura of hers.

"You… you are his son?" Hathaway's voice was slightly hoarse.

Garen shook his head, a hint of gentleness in his eyes as he looked at his family's cousin, who had once been pretty and handsome.

"It's me."

He said softly.

"I've come back."

Hathaway's old gaze gave a hard jolt. This familiar way of speaking, this familiar tone and gaze, it was as though she had instantly returned to the time fifty years ago, and it was as though that handsome and powerful young man had just gone overseas for a few days, saying calmly when he got home, I've come back.

Hathaway's eyes welled up, she waited so hard for more than fifty years, and now, with the passing of time, she was already this old, but Garen was just like how he was back then.

"Don't lie to me… Did Dani get you to come here and lie to me? Did she give you the key?" She suddenly thought of something, and smiled sadly as she shook her head.

"Dani's fine, right?"

Hathaway suddenly fell silent.

All of a sudden, she realized that she no longer knew how to face Garen. After waiting so hard for several decades, with the situation being what it was right now, what ending could they have? Now that there was no longer totem power, over seventy years old was already reaching the average lifespan these days.

She was already on the brink of death, and Garen… Hathaway laughed self-condescendingly, she did not believe that this young man was the Garen from back then.

"When did he go?" she asked suddenly.

Garen was dazed for a moment, and instantly reacted, Hathaway thought he was dead, and had asked his 'grandson' to find his old flame before he died.

She still did not believe, could not believe that the Garen from back then was still so young.

All of a sudden, a sense of faint loneliness surged out from the deepest depths of Garen's heart.

He looked at the old woman on the sofa, walked up to her, and half-knelt lightly, kissing the back of her hand.

"Don't wait anymore…"

With that, Garen stood up, turned around, and left the room wordlessly.

Behind him, Hathaway did not say anything more.

Perhaps neither of them knew how to face each other.

After all these years, Hathaway had truly become the matriarch of the Trejons family and the Black Swamp Palace, she had adopted one of her little sister Dani's grandchildren as her own, to become the next heir for the Black Swamp Palace Master's position.

This grandchild was unnaturally excellent, and had the full support of the current Head of Military.

And now, even if Garen came back, what was the point? Other than disturbing everyone's peaceful lives, there was no longer any place for him here.

Everyone, all of them, including Ivy, including Skyharp, Angel, et cetera, all of them thought Garen was already dead.

Died in the ice-sealed extreme depths of the ocean.

The Kingdom had even set up a memorial especially for him, every year there would be mighty officials and nobles making their way there to pay their respects.

As for his reappearance, taking over the Black Swamp Palace again? What was the point of it?

Back then when Garen started this organization, other than to collect information, his deepest intention was simply to leave the mark of the White Cloud Gate in this world. He had regrettably died in battle in the Secret Technique World, so he could only leave his teacher Fei Baiyun's legacy here.

The Black Water True Technique had traces of the Mammoth Secret Technique everywhere, it was actually equivalent to a totem version of the White Cloud Secret Technique. That was already enough.

Leaving the house quietly, Garen walked on the brightly-lit Kingdom roads slowly, there were night stalls and night markets on both sides, with snacks, clothes and accessories, little knick-knacks, a balloon-shooting game, gambling games, and all sorts of other night market activities, making Garen feel as though he had returned to Earth.

Before he knew it, he had actually walked back to where the Mercenary's Guild was by himself.

What had been the Mercenary's Guild was now just a true and actual bar, the people coming in and out were fat rich merchants with beer bellies and all sorts of slender barmaids. Or there would be young men and women, fashionably dressed.

Loud and noisy music floated out of the bar, and even standing outside the door, he could feel the rhythmic drumming sounds.

Garen released his five senses, and reached into the bar.

There was no one else with totem power inside, and they were all young people. He would occasionally 'see' some young military officials with black military guns on their waists, and they would be the most intimidating presence here.

As for the totem user mercenaries? What about Angel, who Garen had unconsciously come here in search of, that friend of his who was the first to join his War Chain, there was no more trace of her whatsoever. He did not know if she had died, or left…

Garen stood for a while outside the bar, just staring at the bar dazedly, until some seductive young beauties came up to him to try and chat him up, only then did he slowly turn around and walk away.

"Fifty years… who's still alive?" He asked himself in his heart.

Those friends from back then, who was still around?

He walked towards the direction of the Black Swamp Palace subconsciously, the night street market with the throngs of people, somehow made him feel a faint loneliness that even he was not aware of.

Chapter 548: Years 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Black Swamp Palace was no longer as heavily guarded as before, there was a notice plastered on the wall beside the door announcing the recruitment of students this year, as well as the steps and places to register. There was even a red feedback box nailed beside it.

The university students in the prime of their lives were leaving and entering the school gates, in groups of twos and threes, the sounds of their laughing, talking, and playing permeating everywhere.

Just above the palace gates, on a huge semicircular sign, the words 'Black Swamp University' were clearly carved.

Garen was dressed fully in a black, looking clean and neat, and added with his natural aura of nobility, the guard assumed that he was one of the school's students, just raising his head for one glance before continuing to read his novel.

Walking through the palace door, there was an extra glass cabinet on the left wall, with the school's name list pasted up inside.

Of these, his portrait was the very first one.

'Garen Trejons: The Black Swamp Palace's first founding principal and Palace Master.

Sun calendar 3550 -- 3592.The great founder of the Black Water True Technique Secret Technique, one of the first members of Parliament, the country's honorary Military Commander-in-Chief, and the winner of Kovitan's first Highest Contribution Award. He was the only person to win the 3958 World War and Peace Award. Ranked number thirteen among the World's Historic Figures.

With the light from the streetlamps, he looked at his own portrait, and could not help the urge to both laugh and cry. He was standing right here, alive and kicking, looking at the results of his life as written by others. Even his general time of death had been set down.

The young man in the portrait was handsome and stern, with an aura like a lion or eagle in his eyes, his golden hair falling over his shoulders, his gaze sharp as a blade, giving the impression of a hero of an era. This was probably what the artist thought of him.

Garen guessed inwardly.

Going past his pane, the second place was the second row of Historic Figures.

Demon Phoenix Trejons, had become a voyager, traveling all over the world, in the end she was caught in a storm on the left of the two continents, in the West Pole Ocean, her ship overturned and no trace found of her. By then totem power had already disappeared for more than ten years. After that, people found her and her friends' corpses, burying them on a nameless island on the West Pole Ocean, and that island was also named after her, becoming the Demon Phoenix Island.

"To think she actually took my last name…" Garen did not know how, but he still had the mood to smile.

He continued reading.

Ivycius and Skyharp had gone to the West Continent for an exchange, the two of them had many children and grandchildren, and had already become the highest tier family of the entire Kovitan. They were equal to the Trejons family. Recently, medical checks had found that the two of them had illnesses. In order to investigate and overcome his disease, Ivycius performed some of his own studies and research, actually becoming a famous medical expert worldwide, specializing in lymph tumors.

His trip to the West Continent this time was to make a medical report on that matter.

That Master Calingan from back then, and the three Master-level disciples he had chosen himself, all of them had left a deep impact on the history of the university.

As he continued reading to the end, Garen's heart began to grow hollow before he knew it.

Walking past the list of Historic Figures, he walked slowly inside the school, what was once a palace had now become several different teaching and experiment blocks. He could occasionally see some foreign exchange students with different-colored skin walking around, speaking some awkward Kovitan as they tried to chat with the local students with difficulty.

Taking a leisurely stroll around the school, Garen did not meet unexpectedly any old faces, all the people, all the faces, he did not know any single one of them.

Walking in the Black Swamp Palace that used to be so familiar to him, was like walking into someone else's house.

He had also found the Black Swamp Guards modified by the Green Vine Sphere, but these Guards were no longer as powerful as they used to be, and were just a lot stronger than normal people in terms of vitality and aura, without that unnatural power they used to have in the beginning.

Evidently the Green Vine Sphere's modification had also been affected by the disappearance of totem power, and had utterly become a normal process.

The main palace hall that he himself used to live, half of it had been sealed away as a historic site, and the other half had actually become a popular rendezvous spot among the students due to the dim lighting there.

After Garen bumped into several little couples, he was no longer in the mood to survey his old home.

If he was willing, the whole Kingdom would still return to his grasp in a very short time, but what was the point of that?

When Garen walked out of the university, he turned around to look at the words above the palace gates, his feelings unnaturally complicated.

His coming to this world, had been an accident after all.

The only person he felt guilty towards in the Kingdom, perhaps in the whole Kingdom, was his cousin Hathaway, after waiting so hard for more than fifty years, the final result was that neither of them knew how to face the other, with such a great difference in their appearances.

Or perhaps she had really taken him for his own grandson…

Garen thought somewhat self-deprecatingly.

With the disappearance of totem power, practically all the unnatural power had completely disappeared. As such, the totem users who relied on that reproduction ability to lengthen their lifespans had also naturally lost their longevity, falling one after the other.

The world had become a world of normal people.

The ones who were Luminarists had become knowledgeable scholars, the ones who were forgers had become scientists using the power of science to solve all. The ones who were totem users, only the very peak-level ones, could become famous martial artists.

Before leaving the Kingdom, Garen went to visit his teacher Emin's grave. The Tasura Academy was a clan renowned through the whole Kovitan, so Emin's grave was covered with all sorts of fresh flowers, evidently there were disciples and students coming here to clean his grave often.

All of the people he had once been familiar with had left forever, and this world that he had grown familiar with had once more slowly fallen into estrangement.

Garen left the Kingdom soundlessly.

Before leaving, he checked Hathaway's body for illnesses, using the power of his Living Secret Techniques to freeze and clear away the roots of her diseases, allowing her to live for at least more than ten more years.

This was the only thing he could do for her. Similarly, there were his friends from back then, Prynne and the others, Garen also made the same final arrangements for all of them.

The secret technique he was practicing did not have the ability to increase their lifespans, and may even have other harmful side-effects to normal people. But if he controlled it carefully, he could precisely kill the diseases within a body, attaining the complete eradication of diseases.

*******************

The country of Black Field, Meteor Town.

In a white graveyard outside the city limits.

Garen sat in front of a black tombstone, holding a black beer bottle in his hand, and chugging from it every now and then.

There was no alcohol in it, only coffee.

Under the setting sun, the black tombstones reflected a red glow, the black tombstone with a bit of white had the following words carved clearly onto it: the Combined Graves of Goth and Jessica.

The carvings were extremely simple, other than the row of simple names, there weren't any other words. No summary of their lives, no singing his praises as the Black Field Master, bot even their birth and death dates.

Just the two names.

Perhaps this was Goth's atonement for himself.

After coming to the Black Field Country for the past these days, Garen had more or less found out how Goth died.

After the Battle of Heaven, Goth's previously strong body began to deteriorate rapidly, and in the end he died suddenly of myocardial infarction and a stroke.

Be it Jessica's betrayal and death, or Garen's eventual disappearance, both had sunk the once-powerful Black Palace Master into the depths of guilt and despair.

For some reason, as Garen sat here before Goth's grave, he just reminisced like that with unnatural calm, his heart unexpectedly peaceful.

He could understand Goth's final feelings, that man looked strong on the outside, but in actuality, his heart was still as fragile as a child's. Jessica's betrayal was a serious blow to him, like a hard stab in the heart, hurting him so much he could barely breathe.

With a life like that, perhaps just living in this world was a sort of agony, so he might as well die and call it quits.

The Cthulhu King's base was near Black Field, and he went there to look around too, but there was not a single Cthulhu there, all of them had died back when the totem power scattered.

The Cthulhu headquarters had become an utter wasteland, and the Cthulhu King was nowhere to be found. Some people said he had left and headed for the mysterious South Pole, some said he headed underground, but more people believed that perhaps he had already died, died in an unknown corner of the world, without any of his past glory, only a body's worth of injuries after the disappearance of totem power.

"Why does it feel like the sky without totems is a lot cleaner?" Garen threw his head up and drank a mouthful of coffee, as though talking to Goth, or perhaps talking to himself.

All of Goth's achievements had practically been buried away, only some very few of the older generation still remembered the Grand Duke who was once the Black Field Master. That was why a stranger like Garen could sit in front of Goth's grave like that, and nobody would bother.

Some of the men and women coming here to pray in the evening glanced at him from afar, seeing Garen sit in front of the grave, they might have thought that it was just a drunk relative here to visit, so they left quickly out of understanding.

Garen did not really care, after the initial melancholy, now his emotions had utterly gone calm.

"These days, I suddenly have a feeling." He said softly, "As though I have become the only, lonely person in this world. You've gone, Teacher's gone, Ivy and the rest are all old now, and perhaps soon, they will leave for sure as well."

He paused.

"All of a sudden, I don't know what to do."

"Everything I know is leaving me." He raised his head to look at the slowly setting twilight sun, the bright red light dying his face completely red.

"A person's life is just like this sun, rising and setting, no matter who it is, they won't be able to escape this natural cycle. I'm just a few steps slower than you guys."

Standing up, Garen just left the beer bottle in front of the tombstone.

"After leaving this time, maybe I really won't come back here anymore." He paused. "When I have time, I will think of you." And then he turned around, walking towards the distance, leaving.

Without turning back, it was just like having a cup to drink with an old friend, and then going back to their respective homes, calmly.

There was still the last stop…

Garen's heart welled with an unprecedented loneliness, this sense of loneliness had only grown stronger since it emerged in Kovitan. Like rounds and rounds of dark-colored vines, tightly, they wrapped him up in layers, at first mildly, but towards the end, they grew tighter and tighter, until he was finding it harder and harder to breathe.

He could not help but remember Hellgate's last moments.

That stubborn man, had he been just like Garen was now? Having experienced the times when his friends and family left him, over and over again, that bone-deep loneliness, that obstinance that no one else could understand, perhaps that was the true source of his motivation to purely chase his ideals.

Everything in the world would pass with time, only the everlasting principle, the ever-unchanging Door to Heaven, was always and ever standing right there.

Garen desperately wanted to find that last person, the one who was most likely to be like him. Even if it was just a tiny comfort...

Chapter 549: Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the north-east direction of what used to be Daniela, among the thick forest near the sea, in an underground base headed towards the depths of the world.

Among the dense forests, there was a lonely little town with very few people.

Looking down from above, amidst the forest as thick as a green ocean, the town was like an irregular yellow spot, clear as can be.

There was no sign of anyone in the town, everything around was surrounded by thick vines and grasses, from afar, the houses and buildings in the town looked like they were covered by a layer of sticky green liquid, and some was even flowing down from the roofs.

Walking inside for a look, he saw a curtain of dense green moss and vines, and the ones drooping down from the roofs were some long leafy vines.

Dressed fully in pitch-black, Garen walked into the town slowly.

This was once an entrance into the underground world, countless totem users going in and out had formed a busy town for trade and exchanging supplies.

And now, this place was merely a deserted wasteland.

Walking slowly down the town's streets, he would occasionally sense some movement darting through the thickets of dense foliage by the main streets, there seemed to be something small dashing past at high speeds.

The sky was dark and heavy with clouds, as though it could rain at any time.

Garen raised his head to look at the sky, his hands in his trouser pockets, as he walked slowly toward a house on the left with some worn and torn cloth hanging outside.

There was some blurry writing on the large red horizontal sign that he could not read clearly, and some black bugs he could not name were crawling over it slowly.

The house was still intact, just the doors and windows were all destroyed.

Garen pushed open the half a door casually, and walked into the house.

A stench of mold assaulted his nose, it was completely dim inside the house, and there was green moss all over the floor.

It had been three days since he came to this town, and he had not discovered anything, but he still did not leave.

He had indeed found the entrance into the underground, but unfortunately that entrance had been completely obscured a long time ago. After digging for more than a day and getting nothing in return, he simply gave up.

It had been three days, after one more day, he will leave this place. That was his plan.

Standing in the moldy house, Garen just stood in the doorway, raising his head to look at the sky outside the door, his heart completely calm.

Boom…

The deep sound of thunder came from the distant skies, and the sky began to grow even darker.

"It's going to rain…" Garen murmured instinctively, in this place with no other traces of human presence, he seemed to be talking to himself. But he also seemed to be talking to someone else.

"Yeah, it's going to rain…"

Suddenly there was another voice behind him.

Garen's expression froze for a second, and he turned around, deep in the darkness of the house, a huge silhouette appeared.

It was a grey-brown Mantis, a full two meters tall.

A giant Mantis dressed like a human. It just stood there in the darkness, only revealing its head, as it stared at Garen peacefully.

"Garen, it's me."

Garen's gaze intensified, he recognized this voice. Although it was old and weak, it was indeed exactly the same as that familiar voice from back then.

"Sun God King…"

This was the Divine God Palace Master that had explored the Shadow Ruins together with them.

Whooshhh…

In an instant, the rain poured down from the sky.

By the time he recovered, the man and the Mantis were already sitting side by side under the roof outside the house, staring at the heavy veil of rain less than a meter in front of them.

It was as though heaven and earth had been covered by this heavy rain, nothing could be seen clearly, and this house was their only shelter.

"I knew you would come." The Mantis said quietly, "Ever since totem power started vanishing, I just knew."

Garen looked at the veil of rain and said nothing.

"It's a new era now." The Mantis seemed to smile, "It's a miracle that I, a creature from the previous era, could last this long."

"Where are your subordinates? Where have they all gone?" Garen asked softly.

"Them? Most of them became normal beasts, but even more, died of old age." The Mantis replied calmly, "You know, most creatures don't live long to begin with."

"If you break through as well, could you continue living like me?" Garen asked calmly.

"I don't know." The Mantis raised its arm blades with difficulty, scratching its mandibles lightly, just like a gesture a real mantis would have. "Actually, I was supposed to die several months ago. But my premonition told me, that an old friend might come visiting."

"So you held on until now."

"That's right." The Divine God Palace Master looked at the veil of rain, without any hint of fear towards his impending death, just peace.

"Is there anything you want to tell me?" Garen fell silent.

"Anything I want to say?" The Mantis shook its head, "These years, I've gone to many places, so many, many places… Looking everywhere for the traces of the old era, I saw a lot, and experienced a lot. But when the Cthulhu King died in front of me, my heart suddenly went empty."

The torn bright red cloth curtain drooped down on the right, swaying in the wind, fluttering.

"That feeling, that you're the only person in the world, it sure hurts… There are people all around you, but not one of them is the same kind as you." The Mantis' mouth split into a grin.

Garen did not continue, and just looked at it quietly.

The sky was growing darker and darker, and time continued to tick by.

In the rain veil, the man and the Mantis chatted idly, talking about their experiences back then in the ruins, talking about their most painful experiences, their most proud moments, talking about all their stories since they were young.

In that moment, the two of them were like best friends who spoke about everything, and most of the time, it was the Mantis who talked while Garen listened.

The wind grew stronger, the rain grew lighter, and the Mantis' voice grew softer and softer.

By the time the rain had stopped completely, the Mantis was no longer breathing at all, sprawled quietly beside Garen, its body already stiff and cold.

"The weather tomorrow might be clear." Garen did not look at the Mantis, just staring at the sky calmly, "Too bad it doesn't matter for you and me."

He patted the clothes on his body, and stood up. The Mantis' corpse was already shattering slowly, soundlessly turning into something like black ash, flown away and scattering in the wind.

"Now it's just me…" Garen laughed self-condescendingly.

He rolled up his sleeves, the small and clear Imprint on his arm was still there, so he pressed it lightly.

The surroundings darkened.

After a moment, it lightened up again.

He was still standing in the doorway of the house, the scarlet-red banner straight beside him. Some of the floating leaves froze in the air on his right, some raindrops had dripped from the roof and were about to crash into the ground, but they never could.

The world seemed to have stopped in this moment.

Garen looked around him, there were silver rings hanging all around him in the air, each huge ring swaying occasionally, and then they soundlessly began to shatter and fall, turning into countless metal shards.

And after the old rings collapsed, some new silver rings appeared slowly, but they still could not match up to the speed of collapse.

Garen did not look at the whole inner world, he just reached out his hand, and a trident like an ice-blue water mirror gathered in his hand.

Psst!

The bottom of the trident pierced into the ground, upside-down.

"Have you come?"

A deep man's voice came from the forest in front of Garen.

"Kid?" Garen raised his head and looked forward, the Imprint telling him he was not mistaken.

That ancient man walking out of the forest in front of him, was the one who was once Kid.

He looked obscenely old, not at all like a person in his sixties, but more like an ancient monster who had lived for several centuries, the wrinkles on his face were as deep as gutters, his skin was like tree bark, and covered with tiny black spots.

He wore grey cloth, holding on to an old wooden staff, and walked out of the forest like it was only natural.

"I waited a long time for you." Kid leaned on his staff, standing quietly in front of the forest, and watching Garen.

"What on earth happened here?" Garen walked up to him, standing in front of Kid. "Why did the totem power vanish?"

"This is the image I left behind in the Imprint." But Kid ignored Garen completely, just saying his own thing. "The real me, and everyone else, have died in the thirty-two years since that battle."

He paused. "If you can wake up at the very end, and see this, then perhaps you are considered lucky. This image can only last thirty years."

Garen shut up, he had already noticed that although Kid's eyes were looking at his direction, his pupils were not concentrated at all, and seemed to be looking through him, at the things behind him.

"The world is collapsing. Totem power is collapsing." Kid said deeply, "This is the result of our research. Because I am the youngest, I lasted until the end. But soon enough, all unnatural things will be expelled by the Door to Heaven, including me."

"Expelled?" Garen's heart gave a jolt.

"That's right, you didn't hear wrong." Kid nodded. "The Door to Heaven is not a dead thing, after that Battle of Heaven that time, it felt threatened, so totem power began to be eliminated. All unnatural power began to die."

"Only those who have truly escaped the shackles, the Form Six who have escaped the control of totem power, might perhaps be able to escape the effect of the Door to Heaven completely."

Garen listened to Kid's explanation quietly.

"But, in the world that no longer has totem power, even if Form Six fighters would probably be unable to touch the Door to Heaven ever again."

Garen nodded despite himself.

Totem power was indeed a unique power that only this world had, and after eliminating totem power, without the support of the surroundings, even if the Form Six secret techniques succeeded, forming a highly-compressed soul Seed, it would still only have the power of a Form Four during the totem era, maximum.

But even so, in such a world without unnatural power, his power was already definitely the most powerful, unrivaled existence around.

"Be careful, the Door to Heaven won't let you go, it will surely try everything it can to expel you." Kid left with that line, heavily, and his whole person slowly began to fade, disappearing where he stood.

"Be careful…"

That last voice was still slowly echoing, and only then did Garen wake from his thoughts.

"The Door to Heaven…"

Before he knew it, that familiar huge set of white light doors had appeared again in the sky.

There were countless mountains, flowing rivers, and flying birds on the door frame, like so many miniature worlds, unbelievably realistic.

The white light shot down like pillars, going past the slowly disintegrating silver rings, and falling onto Garen's body.

A huge complicated will, like that of countless creatures combined, exploded into Garen's heart.

"Leave… Leave… Leave…"

"Leave…"

"Leave…..."

The endlessly repeating will kept assaulting Garen's heart, as though countless people were constantly howling softly into his ear.

This combined will had no consciousness, it was just the will of countless creatures mixed together. It was a bleary, muddled will.

Garen seemed to hear the whole world in it, animals, people, fish, birds, everything with life, all gathered into a huge current, and wrapping him up in it.

In that moment, he seemed to feel, as though he was the last poisonous tumor in this world, and the whole world seemed to be desperately trying to expel the existence of such a tumor.

From the dark sky, there was just one clean white light pillar surrounding Garen, falling from the sky, like a staircase to Heaven.

Garen smiled slightly.

This world actually had a conglomeration of wills like the Door to Heaven, and he clearly remembered that the worlds before this, the surroundings of Earth and the Secret Technique World, did not have such an existence, or perhaps they did, and he just did not notice.

The universe sure was mysterious.

"If possible, I'd like to go back to the place I had come from." He lightly sent out his own will. If the Door to Heaven had a consciousness, perhaps…

Soon enough, a scene appeared that took him completely by surprise.

The images and memories of his initial arrival into this world abruptly appeared in his mind.

Chapter 550: Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Lightning sparked in the dark, cloud-laden sky, and a red comet fell towards the ground with its long, long tail. This meteor was too small and too weak, so nobody could have noticed it at all.

The meteor pierced through the clouds amidst the clapping of thunder, rushing into an estate on the earth, that was what had once been the Vanderman Estate.

Barroom!!

With a clap of thunder, everything in front of him vanished in an instant.

Garen’s eyes went black, and he was suddenly no longer standing in the forest town from before.

In the next instant, it was as though he was being yanked by an unbelievably huge force, his whole person turning into a blood-red meteor, flying into the sky of the inner world from the surface of the ground.

Red flames burned around his body, forming a thin layer. Looking down through the layer, the ground became further and further, smaller and smaller.

The Door to Heaven in the sky became larger and larger, closer and closer. The pitch-black mirror surface in the center was like a huge mouth of darkness, as though waiting to swallow him up.

But strangely, a sense of familiarity surged into Garen’s heart.

He paused, giving up the energy he had gathered in order to struggle and escape, and instead felt that familiar sense closely.

"The Black Smoke Pot...:"

That was the feeling he had when he was leaving, pushed out of the Secret Technique World by the terrifying force of the volcano.

Everything changed so fast, that it was like a dream.

From meeting the Divine God Palace Master, to the sudden change in the inner world now, Garen was completely not mentally prepared for any of it.

Whoosh!

In an instant, the meteor shot into the Door to Heaven.

Instantly, everything around Garen turned completely pitch-black, there was no light whatsoever, when he turned around to look, there was not even the Door to Heaven’s white light, it was equally nothing but endless darkness there.

His whole body was covered by a crimson-red flame. That flame seemed to be coming from inside his own body, gentle and warm.

The darkness around him slowly changed, turning into the limitless and vast starry space.

Countless silver twinkling stars were scattered all over the universe, and the nearer blue and white planets flew past him quickly like bowling balls.

Garen could feel his speed pick up, becoming faster and faster. The blue stars around him all had long silver threads behind them, brushing past him constantly.

He had actually been sent straight out of the planet by the Door to Heaven, and under its immense protection, he was sent flying alone in an unknown direction. It was all happening so fast, much faster than even when he arrived.

Countless stars twinkled and flowed past him, the time passing slowly.

After goodness knows how long, Garen suddenly saw a pale blue planet ahead of him grow closer and closer, becoming larger and larger. Soon, it took up his entire field of vision.

The planet was being magnified in front of his eyes at a high speed, and just ahead was the pale blue ozone layer, just as the red meteor that was Garen nearly touched the ozone layer, a pitch-black whirlpool suddenly appeared in front of him, swallowing him directly.

The whirlpool rapidly vanished, and the universe continued on as though nothing had ever happened.

*******************

Between two of the three continents, the Fivestar Continent and the Azure Continent, on an unknown stretch of sea.

A scarlet-red meteor appeared in the air above the ocean as though it had teleported there.

Boom!!

A wave several tens of meters tall suddenly erupted in the middle of the big blue sea.

The white pillar of waves rose high into the air, and then scattered down with a whoosh.

A ton of seawater was spinning, forming a huge deep-blue whirlpool that was several hundred meters deep.

In the middle of the whirlpool, a tall and lean blonde-haired man was standing above the water’s surface quietly, his eyes closed tightly, his arms lightly drawing a circle around him.

The deep-blue walls of the whirlpool around him abruptly reached out two tentacles of water that looked like snakes, twining gently around his waist, and lifting him up lightly.

The deep-blue whirlpool shattered explosively, a large current of water surging out to form a wave several meters wide, surfing under the figure’s feet and using the momentum of the whirlpool to take him towards the distant sea.

Just then, Garen’s eyes were closed, and he was rapidly checking the side effects of this journey through space. His attribute pane was clearly showing the changes in his body’s condition right now.

Compared to the last time, when his body had been destroyed in the flames, this time, with the help of the Door to Heaven taking the initiative to send him off, as well as his power being much stronger than it was before, he had somehow only sustained extremely light injuries. His organs had internal bleeding to different degrees, but after channeling his secret technique for a bit, these wounds had been completely frozen up.

Opening his eyes abruptly, Garen looked at this blue ocean far, far away, from a distance.

Everything was an endless sea of deep-blue, but in the direction of the ocean surface that Garen was looking it, there seemed to be a hint of a white dot.

It was a white cruise ship, a steel cruiser!

There were even words printed on the side of the cruise: Fivestar Continent General Merchant’s Alliance, Farsea Company.

Those were the Weisman words that Garen was absolutely familiar with.

In that instant, the images from back then appeared in Garen’s brain one by one, the ambitious Weisman Empire had set a trap for the peak-level elite fighters who entered the Black Smoke Pot Island, and eventually released that terrifying explosive that seemed to be an atomic bomb.

The Immortal Palace, Behemoth Gate, the Number One Divine Warrior…

The memories and images were flashed past Garen’s eyes like a temporary illusion.

His figure moved, falling into the water, and rapidly swimming towards the steel cruise ship.

********************

On the white cruise ship

Lindsay Whitman hugged a novel about legendary figures as she yawned out of boredom, leaning on the rails by the side of the ship, she yanked her hair that was growing longer, her long dark brown hair gone from ear-length to falling over her shoulders, flying messily in the sea breeze and irritating her.

The high noon sun was rather piercing to the eyes, but felt warm and cozy on the skin, making her whole body feel relaxed and comfortable.

She was only twelve years old, but she followed her father out to sea a lot, sailing the seas between the Azure Continent and the Fivestar Continent, selling all sorts of ceramics, silks and tea leaves for the company. Ever since her mother died in an accident when she was three, she had been living her life on cruise ships.

On the wavy white ship deck, several sailors were carrying large buckets of water and washing the floor.

This was the stern of the ship, and underwind as well, so the sea breeze blowing from ahead brought with it the aroma of fragrant and spicy stir-fried squid.

Lindsay could not help but swallow some saliva.

She wanted to resist her hunger, but her saliva kept coming, making her empty stomach feel all the hungrier.

She was not pretty, and she had bad skin, her features coming from her ship captain of an old man, so she had thick brows and large eyes, thick lips and a short nose, with none of a girl’s gentle beauty. Her figure was not nice either, slightly chubby around her waist, and her skin was absolutely dark, after so long living on the sea, all her skin had been baked into a glowing dark brown color, although it looked healthy, it was nothing like that fair silkiness she desired for so much.

"Excuse me." Suddenly, a clear man’s voice came from behind her.

Lindsay instantly turned around, and as soon as she saw the person behind her, the pupils in her eyes dilated rapidly.

This person was completely soaked from head to toe, and was clambering over the railing to climb onboard from the side of the ship, all his clothes were completely dripping wet, and plastered tight to his skin. Even more strangely, there was some seaweed left on his body.

"Y-y-y-y-you…" Lindsay felt her voice shaking, but she could not control herself. She pointed at the other person, her whole body shaking.

This was the deep sea! The deep sea!!!

There was not even an abandoned island without several thousand nautical miles of here, and even sailing alone, it would take more than ten days before they saw any land! More than ten days before seeing land! What did that mean?

Wasn’t this deep sea area a part of the ocean that you could see either whales or sharks, either sharks or eels, and nothing at all else?

Oh! My God! Could this be the legendary humanoid sea monster? Humanoid sea monster!? How could I have stumbled across one of those legendarily terrifying things, wasn’t that something only the main characters in those legends came across? Without a world-ending divine weapon, or a super precious sword, anybody who met one of these would die without a question!

Wait! What if this wasn’t a sea monster, but was instead a fairy tale mermaid prince? She wouldn’t be that unlucky, would she?!! They said mermaid princes loved eating children under the age of fifteen the most, and they would skewer them with iron poles, eating one in each bite, and usually putting away more than twenty a day…

It’s over… it’s over, it’s all over…

"Excuse me…" Garen looked at the little girl in front of him, watching her face go green and then white, and was suddenly slightly confused. "Could you lend me a set of clothes? I’m a traveler who got in trouble, the passenger vessel I took from Stonecliff Continent was in a storm, and I was tossed overboard, thank goodness I met you guys."

The little girl pointed at him woodenly, her chest rising and falling drastically, but when she heard these words, she finally recovered her senses.

Phew…

She released a long breath.

"So you’re a traveler who got thrown overboard… You… you scared the heck out of me… Don’t you know that climbing up the side of someone’s ship suddenly from the middle of the sea isn’t something just anyone can do?"

"Sorry, my young friend, I gave you a scare." Garen smiled apologetically.

His aura as an upper-level noble from the Totem World, as well as his own beautiful looks and behavior, made Lindsay’s heart skip a beat.

He spoke very good Weisman, it was just that his vocabulary was slightly outdated here and there, sounding slightly awkward and unnatural, but that gave this man an even stranger sense of charisma.

"Are you a Grandmaster of Combat?"

"Grandmaster of Combat?" Garen paused slightly, it had been a long time since he heard this term, and he felt something strange yet familiar surge into his heart.

The other crew members had also noticed the situation over here by now, and more than ten crew members dressed in white who were nearby picked up their weapons and started surrounding them. Their expression all held a slight wariness and caution.

The weapons they held in their hands included shovels, harpoons, large webs, but were mostly long silver machetes and fish guns.

"Lindy! You come over here first!"

A sailor with a large beard yelled towards Lindsay. His gaze on Garen was extremely nervous and wary, as though he was not seeing a person, but a terrifying ocean beast.

More crew members surged out of a tower in the distance, and they surrounded a middle-aged man in black clothes and a round cap, that person was holding an intricate silver handgun, his expression dark as he jogged over to them.

"Don’t worry, I have no ill intentions." Garen smiled as he raised both hands. "I’m just a traveler who was thrown overboard, I floated for several days before I was just lucky enough to encounter your ship."

Just then, some of the other passengers onboard the ship also came out of their cabins, watching the action from afar.

Chapter 551: East Continent 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Traveler?"

The people around them began to make a commotion.

In the midst of the chatter, Lindsay left Garen carefully, going to stand beside the man with the big beard. Her old man the Captain also separated from the crowd, walking towards Garen with silver gun in hand.

The man’s face was covered in bristles, and he wore a blue round cap, his eyes bulging out somewhat, so he looked at others like a frog looked at insects, his gaze icy cold.

"You’re a traveler?" He did not wait for Garen’s reply, continuing, "I don’t care if you really are a traveler or not, since you’re on my boat, you’ll have to follow my rules."

He observed Garen’s clothes and appearance carefully, his expression relaxing ever so slightly.

What he did not say was that although there were many navigation routes through this part of the sea, there would not be ships going through the same area within at least three days of each other.

In other words, if this person really was a traveler who had been thrown overboard, then he must have survived alone in these waters for at least three days, soaking in the seawater for three days. What a preposterous thing… haha.

Putting aside how corrosive seawater was, it was very harmful to soak in it for long, and even drinking water here was a problem. Besides, there were periodically sea sharks in this area.

But he had heard that some strong martial artists had bodies that were exceeded normal limits.

"You are… a martial artist?" He thought about it, and asked quietly.

"Uh…" Garen did not understand that term for a moment, but after he translated it, he nodded slightly. "That’s right, I have trained before in martial arts."

"If you’re a martial artist, that makes sense." The Captain’s expression instantly softened, "May I ask, your name is…"

"Garen, Garen Trejons." Inwardly, Garen quietly added on that familiar last name, Garen Trejons Lombard.

******************

After some simple explanation and verification, Garen very ordinarily took on the identity of a lost traveler, and joined this ship, becoming one of the ship’s passengers.

The Weisman Captain seemed to have a lot of respect for martial artists, and asked no more about Garen’s identity. He did not ask Garen for any passenger fees either, even arranging a room for him enthusiastically, and getting his own daughter Lindsay to serve him in terms of food and drink.

After boarding the ship and settling down, Garen had not thought that just showing a little of what he could do with throwing knives, instantly arranging three throwing knives into a straight line, was enough to make the Captain’s attitude change so much.

Compared to the confusion and suspicion of the surrounding crew members, the Captain’s reaction was more surprising to him, this was evidently a person who knew the world and had knowledge of many things.

Two days after boarding the ship, Garen was arranged to stay in the VIP room in the passengers’ lounge, there were even some navigation books inside that he could read. For the past two days, he had been living, eating, and resting in his room, the injuries on his body recovering rapidly.

"Mr Garen." After tidying up the room, Lindsay looked at Garen with a look of anticipation, "Could you tell me some stories about you martial artists?"

This was not her first time serving martial artists, but although her attitude was very proper, her potential and appearance were also very important, her appearance missed the mark by a long shot in every way, and her talent was not particularly good either, so no matter how good her attitude was, most martial artists would just tell her some stories about basic knowledge, and that was to thank her for her good attitude. As for taking her as a disciple, they did not even consider it. As for those slightly weaker ones, she herself did not want them, those normal dojo masters probably could not even defeat her own old man.

"Stories?" Garen sat in the room, holding a ship captain’s journal as he drank some specially-imported black tea. "Speaking of stories, do you know about the Battle of the Black Smoke Pot Island?"

"Of course I know the Battle of the Black Smoke Pot Island." Lindsay nodded hard, "I heard that it was the peak of the era of Grandmasters of Combat, the two Kings of the Century faced off on the very peak of that island, but in the end the volcano erupted, and a nuclear bomb exploded, so they all fell there."

"Oh? You know it so well?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"Of course I do!" Lindsay answered matter-of-factly, "It was about more than sixty years ago now, that was the peak-level incident in the martial arts world. The Immortal Palace’s strongest fighter in history, Sylphalan, died in that battle."

"You even know the Immortal Palace?" Garen was suddenly interested. "More than sixty years?" He abruptly noticed that key term, and instantly fell silent.

"Of course I know, the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate, they’re the two strongest powers in the combat world, they’re the two holy grounds of combat. They are the joint organizers of the Combat Festival tournament that happens once every three years. Our ship has ferried martial artists participating in the Combat Festival more than once!" Lindsay said, with a hint of pride.

"The Combat Festival?" Garen heard a new term again.

"It can’t be? You don’t even know that?" Lindsay’s eyes widened.

"I’ve always been training hard in the wilderness… So…" Garen shrugged to indicate that he truly did not know.

"The Combat Festival is an important tournament that the two powers use to rank and choose new generations of Grandmasters of Combat, not only do these include the Grandmasters of Combat in the traditional sense of the world, they also include mysterious martial artists who combine technology with their killing moves. It is held once every three years, and by now it’s been held more than ten times. I heard that the truly strong competitors will even be chosen by the two powers to become their official members." Lindsay walked to the chair opposite Garen and sat down, explaining patiently.

"More than sixty years…" Only then did Garen know, in the process of him returning, he also seemed to have used up far too much time.

As for the Combat Festival or whatnot, that was just the method the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate were using to find new talent as well as weed out potential threats.

That Demon Gate was probably what used to be the Behemoth Gate, and that Immortal Palace might be the same Immortal Palace from back then, but he had not expected these two to grow so strong.

"Other than the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate, are there any more powerful sects in the combat world?" He continued asking with a slight hint of anticipation.

"Other than these two… there are also the Black Fist Gate, the Crimson Sand Sword, and the Celestial Circle Gate. I don’t know the others, but these should be the main few."

"Is there a White Cloud Gate, or a Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate?" Garen paused for a bit, and asked.

"White Cloud Gate? That powerful sect that joined the Battle of the Black Smoke Pot, huh…" Lindsay seemed to remember now, "After that battle, the White Cloud Gate fell into obscurity, they only had that one extremely powerful Gate Master, after that the people from the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate took revenge on them, apparently the losses and casualties were great, and most of their important legacies were lost as well. There is still a White Cloud Gate now, but it was a sect rebuilt by the some of the previous members, they don’t have any complete legacies from before, so they’re only considered a lowest-end sect."

She thought back carefully. "I used to want to watch the Combat Festival very badly, but I was blocked outside and could not go in, so I just wandered around outside for a few days, but afterward I bought a book introducing the different combat sects, and they mentioned a little bit about the White Cloud Gate.

"What about the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate?" Garen fell silent for a moment, and continued asking.

"I’ve never heard of it before…." Lindsay shook her head, "That sect’s name sounds super impressive, are you from this sect, Mister?" She asked somewhat curiously.

Garen smiled, but did not reply.

In terms of his position, not only was he the White Cloud Gate Master, he was also the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate’s number one Divine General. Sadly… these identities that were once so striking, after a mere sixty or so years, had become utterly unknown.

The White Cloud Gate had already fallen to such an extent, and the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, that had peak Grandmasters of Combat such as himself and Palosa, must have been suppressed by the Immortal Palace and the Behemoth Gate until it was unrecognizable.

******************

In the distant Azire Continent, a small town by the sea.

In a dilapidated old dojo’s old wooden halls, several young men and women stood in a row, obediently listening to what their young senior brother was saying in a loud voice.

"In the history of White Cloud Gate, we were once glorious as well."

The senior brother pointed at the sign above them proudly, facing his junior brothers and sisters.

"In our history, we once had two Divine General level Grandmasters of Combat, and four Divine Marshals, our power was definitely absolute, so as disciples of this gate, we must always remember the pride and glory of the past… Always remember the Three Prides and Three Sins as dictated by our Teacher Ancestors, do not forget our sect rules, be disciplined, shoulder the responsibility of developing and strengthening our sect, take pride in your identity as a disciple of this sect, you must…"

The senior brother continued on and on up there.

The few young girls and boys below him were all groggy from the lecture, but this weekly ideology class was compulsory.

Divine Generals, Divine Marshals? Nobody knew if those legendary levels actually existed before, they were just too far away from normal disciples like them. It was probably their Teacher Ancestor blowing their own horns.

These days, which small sect did not make up their own glorious history? If they had nothing to say even when bluffing, and could not intimidate those rich people into a daze, who would send their sons and daughters into the sects, and pay the tuition fees?

That was how the four or five young men and women down there were tricked into it.

Two were children from a small-time merchant, one was the daughter of an out-of-luck noble, and two of them came from normal families in town, one boy and one girl.

Out of these children, the youngest was only thirteen, and the oldest nineteen, having all entered the sect at different times. At first the White Cloud Gate had several dozen disciples and members, but the Iron Leg Gate nearby challenged them once, injuring some of the old masters and even grievously hurting the old Gate Master. So the disciples left and scattered, and after a few years, only these few were left of those from back then, added together with the newly-recruited ones.

Most of these children were here because of the cheap school fees, if it were not that they truly could not afford the other expensive dojos, nobody would be willing to be a disciple under this old and dilapidated lowest-level sect.

The First Senior Brother was still up there chattering away, as he thought about what the old man told him before he left. Good for that geezer, he had taken some of the sect’s senior and junior sisters to meet the Crimson Sand Sword’s invitation, helping out preparations for the Combat Festival next March.

Just thinking about it made this First Senior Brother really mad, that damn geezer kept bringing those few pretty ladies with him everywhere, there was no time to bond at all. Wasn’t the whole reason he joined in the first place because the White Cloud Gae had many pretty ladies?

The geezer’s three granddaughters, especially the youngest Lolloa, were practically white cabbages in this black mud, so tender and sweet…

"First Senior Brother, you’re drooling."

He instinctively wiped the corners of his mouth, but the First Senior Brother immediately noticed something amiss, his gaze sinking as he stared harshly at one of the blonde-haired boys beneath him, that boy was hiding behind a cool-looking young girl with black hair, his expression mischievous.

"Sit back in your own place! As a man, is it right for you to keep hiding behind your older sister!?"

The First Senior Brother scolded him, but his gaze was quietly wandering over the cool black-haired girl.

He had to admit, that old geezer’s eye for beauties was pretty good, and his taste was the best as well. Ever since the geezer took over as Palace Master, he had started adopting baby girls from all over the place, they looked all wrinkled and ugly when they were young, but after they grew up, each of them turned out to be pretty and tender young girls.

Putting aside their potential, there were several young male disciples who joined just for these pretty girls, if the Iron Leg Gate’s challenge had not chased away most of them, right now the sect would probably be expanding like anything.

Sigh… Who knows when that damn geezer is coming back…

Although the First Senior Brother was preaching ideology, his thoughts had long since flown away from here, floating towards those three cute ladies with the old geezer.

Chapter 552: East Continent 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After listening to Lindsay’s explanation about the combat world, in the next few days, Garen asked her about the relevant situation every day.

More than sixty years, Ying Er might still be alive, but his parents…

Garen sighed inwardly, time was still the strongest weapon of all.

He suddenly had the urge to return to the White Cloud Gate and take a look. But it was obvious that the current White Cloud Gate was probably no longer in the Stonecliff Continent’s Yalu Confederation.

However, since all the famous sects will join the Combat Festival, then the old sects like the Crimson Sand Sword and the Celestial Circle Gate would definitely be there, if he went there, he might be able to meet some of his old friends from back then.

Andrela, the King of Nightmares, the members of White Peacock from back then, were they still around now?

If he could meet some of his old friends, he might be able to find Ying Er as well.

Just then he was sitting in his own room, listening to Lindsay recall some of the combat world stories she knew, and he could more or less deduce the changes in the state of the world as well as their technological level.

"...After the Battle of Black Smoke Island, the second to grasp nuclear bombs were the Yalu Confederation, and then it was the Republic of the Tulip. After all three superpower countries controlled such intimidating power, there basically were no more great wars, only a few military exercises and constant small-scale skirmishes. That was when the true value of Grandmasters of Combat could be seen."

Lindsay spoke about all of this logically, after following her father on the sea for so many years, she had seen all sorts of people, and had many sources of information, plus she was bright enough, so Garen understood everything unnaturally well.

"More than ten years ago, a special forces team made completely out of Grandmasters of Combat infiltrated the Republic of the Tulip, in a mere ten days, they assassinated fifteen province-level high officials consecutively, and caused a huge international uproar. That mission was the famous Flash Operation, as though teleporting in a flash, they moved from one place to another, killing instantly, meeting no resistance. This made all the countries in the world understand the terrifying power of Grandmasters of Combat in a special forces unit. And because of that, the Demon Gate and the Immortal Palace began to grow dramatically stronger, bringing the whole combat world with them. Each country began to understand the Grandmasters of Combat more, and more combat-related activities blossomed, until training in combat became a popular trend. Now, all of the countries determine the strength of their special forces according to the number and quality of the Grandmasters of Combat in their countries."

Lindsay finished saying all that in one go, then she picked up her tea and chugged from it, moistening her throat.

Garen watched the little fella talk and talk in front of him, acting like a little adult, and he could not help but find it slightly funny.

"Then the Demon Gate and the Immortal Palace have their own territories, right?"

"That is for sure, the Immortal Palace is mainly in Weisman where we are, and they have countless connections with the military. The Demon Gate is mostly based in the Yalu Confederation, and the Republic of the Tulip in the Azure Continent is the weakest, although the Crimson Sand Sword and Celestial Circle Gate are very powerful, they are still too far away from the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate."

The Crimson Sand Sword and Celestial Circle Gate were both forced to the Azure Continent.

Garen understood now, the old Yale Confederation had been utterly conquered by the Behemoth Gate, while the Immortal Palace were in cahoots with Weisman. If the White Cloud Gate really still existed, and was still teaching their legacies, then they were most likely in the Azure Continent.

Picking up the tea cup and sipping from it, Garen fell into deep thought, when suddenly he felt the cup in his hand sink a little, the hardworking young Lindsay had refilled his cup with tea.

She had been cleaning his room and serving him tea every day for these past few days, and this young one carried out her duties respectfully, her service detailed and first-rate.

"Is the Combat Festival held in a fixed location?" He picked up his cup and sipped again.

"It’s not, they choose a different place each time. Mr Garen, are you planning to join the Combat Festival?" Lindsay asked carefully.

"That’s right, after training for so many years, I thought I should go out and meet the people outside." Garen put down his cup, "I bet you’ve practiced some things with your old man, right?"

Lindsay’s heart brightened, and she pressed down her excitement.

"You mean…"

"I won’t take you in as my disciple, but I can teach you a thing or do." Garen smiled. "Get up and show me everything you learned before. The one you practice the most."

"Yes!"

Lindsay was instantly overjoyed, and she hurriedly moved the chair away, opening up some space.

Standing in the empty space, she pressed her arms forward slowly, and then she raised a knee, the tip of her foot moving slowly at first, but then kicking quickly, her upward kick drawing an easy and beautiful arc.

Turning around, side kick, forward kick, spinning stomp, warhammer downward chop, both her legs in the air as she kicked consecutively.

In that little two meters worth of space, the girl nimbly demonstrated all sorts of different kicks in a very short time, her actions light and quick, her control excellent.

The whoosh of her kicking kept spinning and resounding in the small room.

"Attack me!" Garen said suddenly. "At full power!"

Lindsay’s heart was filled with joy, she knew that this was his real test for her. Her right leg was pulled back, and instantly bounced up again like a poisonous snake, turning into a black shadow and aiming for Garen’s throat with a whoosh.

Smack!

Garen caught the tip of her foot steadily in his hand, so she could not move at all, and all the momentum seemed to have been kicked into the empty air, making Lindsay feel unspeakably uncomfortable.

"Your basics are not bad, but they’re just for show, without the secrets of blood qi, you can only beat up normal people at the most."

"Blood qi secrets?!!" Lindsay’s eyes instantly lit up, "Are you going to teach me blood qi secrets!?"

Blood qi secrets were something only secret techniques had, and the true secret techniques among secret techniques, were the essences of all sects and true martial arts. No matter how the fist- or kick-fighting techniques were, without the secrets of channeling blood qi, they would still only be normal people, unable to reach their limits.

And once they had this secret, only then would they truly step into the world of secret techniques, the world of martial artists.

Garen laughed out loud, blood qi secrets were the core of secret techniques, so they were indeed precious, but he had too many secret techniques stored in his brain, and yet any low-level secret technique would be a priceless treasure to this fellow, it was a core item that could be passed down for a lifetime, and used to strengthen a family.

Besides, even if it was just one of the low-level secret technique secrets that Garen remembered, to Lindsay, it would still be a huge opportunity.

She knew it best herself, this was different from the era where several hundred families clashed with their secret techniques, now countries were paying a lot of attention to the power of Grandmasters of Combat, and had strict regulations over secret techniques, and especially so over the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate, they would not allow the large-scale spreading of secret technique secrets at all, and they had strict rules over the other sects as well. As a result, other than joining the Combat Festival, those who were not chosen and did not have the opportunity, would never be able to learn true secret techniques.

"I'll teach you a simple leg technique. Practice more of this yourself." Garen went through some options, and found the Snake Style Leg secret technique that he had recorded under the White Cloud Gate.

"This secret technique tip is called the Snake Style Leg, it has tremendous power, immense speed, allowing you to extend and retract your leg quickly, so you can land one hit before the enemy could even react. It's not really a secret technique, at the most it's only really an explosive blood qi technique."

"It's enough, it's enough!!" Lindsay’s smile was going to turn her face into a flower, she was so happy it was turning her silly.

She was deeply in love with martial arts since young, but unfortunately she did not have the conditions required, so she could only keep repeating her old man's few moves.

After that, Garen got up and showed her the key to the Snake Style Leg, the moves, and pressure points regarding blood qi and will.

Lindsay was indeed no prodigy, and she was barely even bright, she was just average at best. After hearing it three times, she still barely understood, so Garen had to explain it to her again in detail, analyzing the Snake Style Leg in parts, and setting several goals and steps for her, so she just had to train towards these daily goals.

This was his way of repaying her food and accommodation services.

Time passed by day after day, Garen stayed deep within Lindsay’s family ship, just teaching Lindsay a bit about the kicking technique every day, while he spent the rest of his time alone in his room, reading books, and listening to the radio Lindsay had brought him.

Soon enough, the ship also approached their destination -- the East Continent.

The east side of the three continents was called the East Continent. In truth, the whole East Continent was the East side that Garen's master, Fei Baiyun, mentioned back then. In other words, it was the place the White Cloud Gate was initially founded. For his whole life, Fei Baiyun wanted to return to the East Continent, to see his old hometown and school, but unfortunately he never managed to fulfill that wish of his, so he passed it on to Garen on his deathbed.

Back then he had thought he would not be able to fulfill it either, but now he had somehow returned to the East Continents, though it was several decades later...

*************

"Hahaha…!"

Amidst the hearty laughter, a large man with a black beard hugged Lindsay’s old man hard, patting his back loud enough to for others hear the clapping.

"Safe sailing, Captain Whitman! And I thought I'd only see your ship next week, but to think you're here today!" The large black-bearded man was shirtless, revealing his powerful and healthy dark skin.

The two of them stood on the jetty, surrounded by the laborers carrying the cargo back and forth. It was dawn, the air was clean and cold, with a faint hint of mist, veiling the whole jetty in a foggy blur.

"You kid, Brother Feng, this time I brought a large cargo with me, if I don't move faster, I'd regret it if all the cargo had been taken away by others!" Whitman chuckled as he added on.

While the adults chatted on that side, the children were gathered elsewhere.

Lindsay was standing aside, facing a boy and a girl.

"Big Sis, this is the fifth edition of the ‘World’s Combat History’, I bought it specially for you." The little boy's face was all swollen and his nose green, but he handed her a neatly-wrapped book respectfully.

"This is the ‘Transmutations of the Kick’ that I found." The girl handed over a book she had found as well.

Both of them seemed about ten years old, their faces childish, but even the girl's face was covered in bruises.

"What's up with your faces?" Lindsay’s voice grew angry, and she asked softly. She was the Big Sister of the captains’ kids here on this jetty, and because she liked martial arts, she often beat these kids into submission. The two small ones in front of her now were her ‘true disciples’, not everyone dared to touch them.

Seeing as the two of them weren't speaking, Lindsay humphed coldly like her father.

"Was it Zhao Qinglan!?"

The two of them stuttered but did not dare to reply.

If it was the Lindsay from before, she would not dare to rush and find that Zhao Qinglan either, that person was new to the jetty, and had been studying martial arts since young, she was even better at it than Lindsay, although she was also a girl, she already weighed more than sixty kilograms despite her young age, and had tremendous strength.

But now that she had gotten the secret of the Snake Style Leg, Lindsay was full of confidence, and was sure of her powers, so she had the urge to give it a try.

Chapter 553: Situation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Let’s go! We’ll find that damn fatty!" She pulled her two subordinates and headed towards the street deep within the jetty fiercely.

Within a few minutes, the three of them saw Zhao Qinglan, who was showing off by beating up another little boy in the street, she was tall and heavy, her face covered with flesh, and her hair tied up into two swirls, she wore a powder-white coat, that intimidated anyone who looked at it.

"Yoo-hoo! Lindsay, you finally got the guts to challenge me?"

"Cut the crap, this fight decides who’s stronger!" Lindsay jumped straight towards the side of the street, as soon as she stepped out, the young children who were surrounding and watching them instantly opened up some space for them.

Heh!

Zhao Qinglan spat some saliva onto her palm, rubbed it, and pounced forward, dashing at Lindsay will a speed and agility complete unlike her appearance, moving extremely quickly.

As soon as the passersby looking over at them noticed that she actually had some rhyme and reason to her moves, some others stopped walking and began to watch.

With that pounce, and according to Zhao Qinglan’s strength, it should be more than enough to knock Lindsay to the ground. Once she had the other person pressed down, and unable to get up, that would mean Lindsay could only lie down and be pummeled blindly.

Seeing Zhao Qinglan pounce at her, Lindsay panicked for a second, she had not thought that her opponent would be so fast despite looking so fat.

Before she knew it, her right leg was pulled back abruptly, hiding behind her left leg, and her blood qi, wound up like a spring, was pressed into her right leg in pace as she adjusted her breathing.

Psst!

Like a released spring, in that instant, her right leg naturally shot out, like a black whip, but even more like a pouncing poisonous snake. The tip of her foot was the fangs, making a hissing sound as it swung through the air.

The Snake Style Leg that she had been training constantly these past few days was used ever so naturally.

Bam!

The leg touched the right side of Zhao Qinglan’s pouncing body, and her whole body rolled away, falling at the empty space by Lindsay’s left foot, still swaying.

"Ouch!" She heard a cry of pain.

That Snake Style Leg only had one percent of its true power, mainly because Lindsay used it with the power of a child, and she was extremely unfamiliar with it, so it was far from actually embodying the shape of a snake, and hissing like one.

But that one hit was enough to make Lindsay’s heart jolt.

For the first time, she truly knew for the first time, just how powerful this Snake Style Leg actually was.

The kids around her cheered, these captains’ children who had grown up with Lindsay had disliked Zhao Qinglan for a long time, and seeing her fall now, they all jumped with joy.

"This is the secret you learned from that punk you picked up halfway?"

Suddenly, a deep middle-aged man’s voice came from beside Lindsay.

"Snake Style Leg? Hehe, to think there would be someone who would simply teach others secrets!" The man’s voice suddenly sounded happy at their misfortune.

**********************

"You surviving vermin from the Southern Sky Gate! Die!!"

With a boom, the man in black flew into the sky, a terrifying humanoid pitch-black aura rioting behind him.

The woman stiffened for a second, and his palm hit her directly, sending her flying and coughing blood. She spun several times in the air with a groan, before finally falling hard onto the ground.

The woman stumbled but finally managed to steady her footing, and she actually began to run slightly faster, borrowing the momentum from before. Like a graceful swallow, she darted into a copse of trees beside her, and disappeared after a few turns.

"Get her!!" She vaguely heard a low yell from the man in black behind her.

The man in black took a hand towel offered by the subordinate beside him, and wiped the fresh blood off his hands, his expression hard and cold.

"She can’t escape! We finally managed to catch that little rat, I have set down an inescapable trap, and the main players inside can never escape!"

A short woman in black laughed beside him. "Once the Divine Master(1) leaves the palace, we will just nicely have the leader of the Southern Sky Gate as a present. The Young Divine Master Jessian has personally promised, that as long as we, the North-West Nine Iron Gate can complete this matter, they will personally help us conquer the Bronze Gate’s copper mine, I wonder if this is true?"

As the two of them spoke, large groups of strong black-clothed fighters rapidly rushed into their woods, looking everywhere for her.

"The Demon Gate Demoness Lola is also about to re-emerge from her meditative retreat, the Young Divine Master is probably doing this to prevent any future threats, as long as he settles this matter with the Southern Sky Gate completely, perhaps the Divine Master might place more importance on him." The man in black nodded.

"I heard that the Young Divine Master has already entered the fifth level of the Omniscient Eye, and is now only two steps away from the highest peak-level. once he re-emerges this time, he will surely go toe-to-toe with the Demoness Lola. Add that to the Divine Master’s tremendous power, once he comes out of his meditative retreat this time, he will surely achieve the highest peak-level, the Demon Gate is surely in trouble this time." The woman in black pressed her voice down low.

The man in black instantly looked thoughtful.

The Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate were the two main holy sites of the combat world, controlling countless powerful battle skills and secret techniques, so they had the highest position in the combat world. The Divine Master and the Demon Soldier were the two strongest fighters of the whole combat world, but now the Divine Master was coming out of his meditative retreat soon, and allegedly had the biggest breakthrough, achieving the highest state of secret technique training.

But regrettably, on the Demon Gate’s side, the Demon Soldier had sealed himself into a meditative retreat, but it was said that he had failed and died, so with the rise of one side and the fall of the other, the Immortal Palace had practically become the strongest power in the combat world.

Before this, the survivors of the Southern Sky Gate had managed to live because the Demon Gate was holding them back, but now the chase was getting tighter, with Grandmasters of Combat looking for them everywhere.

*********************

Garen got off the cruise ship slowly, looking at the jetty in front of him.

This was evidently a decently-sized jetty by the bay, the whole jetty was like a circle, an oval with a hole in it, and the path into the ocean was that only hole.

There was a faint mist over the ocean, and nothing could be seen in the distance, but he could vaguely see rows upon neat rows of Chinese-style houses and buildings, on the streets between the houses, the red-skinned strong men carried their naval cargo, but there were mostly fishermen wearing their hats and preparing to go to sea. There were also quite a few bull- and horse-drawn carriages, mostly parked beside the many large ships.

The ship that Garen himself was alighting from was already considered a large ship here, and by now there were already several horse- and bull-drawn carriages stopping beside it. The merchants and travelers getting off the carriages were discussing something with the crewmembers from the ship.

"Mr Garen, may I know if you have any plans after getting off the ship?" Captain Whitman said from behind him, after he found out that his daughter obtained a secret kicking technique from Garen, he had gotten even more passionate.

He would fulfill each and every one of Garen’s wishes, evidently taking him for a legendary Grandmaster of Combat.

Garen shook his head.

"I have no plans, but I’ve come out this time to see the Combat Festival happening soon."

"The Combat Festival is naturally something everybody passionate about combat and martial artists will want to see." Captain Whitman chuckled, "But I heard that the location this year is on a small island in the ocean. It is not too long from now, that the Festival will begin. Why don’t you stay with us and be greeted together with our Navy Alliance, Mr Garen? What do you think?"

By Navy Alliance, he did not mean just his own ship, but the large alliance of the sea formed by the merchants trading and buying here in the East Continent. This huge power had also recruited several power martial artists, and although they did not know exactly how many Grandmasters of Combat there were, even the pirates by the sea had to be wary of such an alliance of over a hundred merchants. As large ocean alliances would sometimes come across rich targets, they would also take down their merchant flag and put up pirate flags to perform the fastest deal to earn money. Nobody could truly differentiate merchants and pirates.

"That sounds fine too." Garen thought about it, his return this time was only to see how Ying Er and the others were doing for the last time. And then, if he had the chance, he wanted to see if he could discover the mysteries of the Black Smoke Pot.

Over the past few days days, he had also tried to use his Listener’s Imprint to enter the inner world, but it seemed that there was no inner world here at all. When he was in the Totem World, his Listener’s Imprint could feel something mysterious. It was a feeling, as though the world itself was living.

And it was soon proven that the Door to Heaven, as the representative final product of the Totem World, did indeed have its own life and instincts.

But once he returned to the Secret Technique World, Garen could not feel any of that sense of life. The whole world’s air seemed dead and stagnant, the Listener’s Imprint did take effect, and was not affected by this planet, so he could feel the waves from inside, but this place simply did not have any inner world, so Garen had no way of getting in.

He had a theory, that these planets were all different, the world of the Totem Planet had a planet’s will, which was the Door to Heaven. And this place, the Secret Technique Planet, probably did not have such a thing.

Perhaps not all planets were the same type, once he thought about it that way, he felt that it was understandable.

The universe was endless and powerful, containing space, time, and everything else. It was probably only natural that there would be different planet systems and conditions.

His thoughts turning instantly, Garen looked at the bearded captain in front of him.

He was utterly penniless, but he could not always depend on the charity of others, so it was convenient for both of them if he was recruited by this Ocean Alliance.

"Before the Festival begins, I’ll have to continue bothering you, Captain Whitman."

"You’re too kind." Whitman hurriedly replied in a low voice, intense joy filling his face.

Martial artists who had secret technique secrets these days were all powerful people, they moved quickly, and any normal person with a gun within ten meters would be sitting doves to them.

The two of them chatted a bit, when suddenly they heard the soft sounds of an argument nearby.

Garen looked towards the direction of the noise, and vaguely saw Lindsay facing off against someone else in the fog.

"Something seems to have happened, I’ll go over there and have a look."

****************

"Who taught you the Snake Style Leg?! Tell me!" The middle-aged man with the cold eyes glared hard at Lindsay, his right palm was at least twice as thick as his left hand, shining with a faint purple glow, as though all of his skin was dyed with a layer of purple. This man wore a grey-green military costume, and there was even a young man about as tall as him standing next to him.

The East Continent was currently in a state of warlordism, these private soldiers and gangsters were all over the place.

That person was just walking past the jetty at first, but he happened to notice a child performing a prohibited secret technique, the Snake Style Leg, and was instantly overjoyed.

Ever since the Immortal Palace declared the Martial Prohibition, anyone who caught the practitioners of those secret techniques involved, would have the right to exchange them for a secret technique or secret of equal level. Although the Snake Style Leg was only one of the lowest-level secret techniques, but for some reason, it was also one of the secret techniques that the Immortal Palace had strictly placed under prohibition.

Of course he would not know that the Immortal Palace hated the White Cloud Gate and the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate to the core, especially the White Cloud Gate, back then the White Cloud Gate Master Garen was unrivalled, using a normal secret technique to make it all the way to the peak, such a story seemed like a legend, no matter how you looked at it.

And so the descendants of the Immortal Palace began to think that it was highly likely that the White Cloud Gate and the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate had something special which allowed Garen to skyrocket upward. After a hard chase and intense search, they still could not find any clue, so they decided to put all the White Cloud Gate’s and the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate’s techniques under prohibition, since they could not find the reason, then they might as well make sure that nobody could learn those martial arts techniques.

This was actually the very foundation of the Prohibition. It was also the reason the current White Cloud Gate did not even dare to practice their own inherited secret techniques.

Translator’s note:

仙主, lit. Deity Master

Chapter 554: Situation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There were several dozen types of secret techniques under the Martial Prohibition, some stronger and others weaker, but most of the martial artists had memorized all of them, since these things could be traded for Immortal Palace Secret Techniques. Everyone wanted a secret technique that was most suited to them, but it was always difficult for martial artists to find a secret technique that fit them well, and the secret technique offered by the Immortal Palace were extremely numerous, so they would definitely find the one they wanted there.

Lindsay was completely panicked and lost, she was only a twelve-year-old child after all, she might have been at the top of her age group, but when faced with an actual military punk with a gun at his waist, her heart was instantly confused.

"I… I…" She stuttered, at first she wanted to say some tough words, but she just could not form them. The more she could not speak, the more panicked she got, and so she was even more tongue-tied.

"Heh." The man with the cold gaze laughed coldly, and came up to her.

"Master Zhao, why are you still joking around with a child? I know this child as well, she’s the Ocean Alliance boss’ daughter, we’ll inevitably meet each other all the time, so please be patient if there were any misunderstandings or if she was rude in any way." A jolly short and fat man walked out of the riotous crowd, his face all smiles as he greeted the other two with one hand over the other fist. "How about I treat you two sirs to a few drinks at Jade Garden?"

"Fat Lan, you stay out of this matter." The cold-eyed military punk Zhao pushed the fatty away, and walked straight up to Lindsay. "Pretty bold of you, to secretly learn a demonic secret technique under Prohibition!"

Before he finished speaking, he made to grab Lindsay.

Smack!

Lindsay instinctively kicked him, blowing his hand away.

"Oh-ho, you still dare to resist!" The military punk Zhao was instantly furious, and kicked towards Lindsay hard, his foundations were naturally much stronger than the girl’s, plus he was also an expert at kicking, so he instantly calculated a few ways she could dodge, his right leg kicking forth at a strange angle.

"Master Zhao, please let her go!""Master Zhao, she’s just a child!"

Seeing that he was actually attacking her, some of the familiar faces in the crowd instantly reacted, they were all Captain Whitman’s close friends, so there was no way they could just stand by and watch their niece get bullied.

In this chaotic world, most of the people on the jetty were huddled into groups, even if normal people did not go against officials, but they still took pride in justice, and could not help but stand up to stop him.

Bam!

Lindsay was kicked hard in the stomach, and she fell forward onto the ground, in too much pain to get up.

The two men who had pounced out beside her were also kicked far away by the military punk Zhao, and stumbled before they finally steadied their footing, but their faces were pale and they could not catch their breath for a while.

"Serves you right for goddamn interfering with me! Go ahead, block me! Block! Go on blocking!!" The military punk Zhao seemed to have been provoked somewhere else, and was now taking all of his anger out on Lindsay.

He kicked Lindsay’s waist again and again, sending her rolling back and forth as though she were a toy.

The people around them were riotous in the beginning, but they began to fall silent afterward, just standing around and watching him kick her. The few who were brave enough to stand out had been settled by this man in a few hits, and still had not recovered.

"Stop!!" There was an explosive yell from nearby.

The military punk Zhao’s expression grew cold, and he stomped on Lindsay’s head even harder.

Of course he would not kill her, he still wanted to give her to the Immortal Palace in exchange for a secret technique, but it was more interesting to destroy this girl’s face than it was to kill her.

He had gotten used to dominating the streets, and did not think he would nearly be humiliated by this young thing today, plus he had just taken a harsh scolding from his senior officer, so his heart was burning with rage. When he hit her, he immediately started putting more force into it.

Garen walked over to them with Whitman, and just glanced at Lindsay, who was lying on the floor, as well the pale children beside them, sensing that Lindsay was in no great danger. He then immediately moved his gaze to the two military punks.

The situation around them was similar to that of the Huaxia period in China on Earth(1), the crowd gathered around to witness the spectacle were completely numb and expressionless.

But for some reason, when he and Captain Whitman walked over, the gazes of everyone around them were instantly dyed with a hint of respect, including those two military punks.

After some careful observation, he noticed that their fear and respect was not aimed at Whitman, but him.

To be more precise, it was aimed at his shining long golden hair.

Garen had just asked Whitman about the situation here on the East Continent, and the information he got was that it was similar to the Republican era(2).

The place had been split up by regional warlords, as soon as the feudal dynasty collapsed, the foreign allied armies had divided up the profits on the East Continent, and there were settlements from other countries everywhere, becoming an eternal trauma in the hearts of Oriental scholars.

The war from a few years ago and the debts they accumulated had utterly shattered the East Continent’s dream of becoming the strongest country in the world, and had also torn away the veil of mystery and mythic respect that the foreign countries had historically had for the East Continent. They were hit as soon as they went down, the East Continent armies with the soldiers on horseback and their sand cannons were basically weak as lambs in the face of the foreign gunpowder cannons.

After they terribly lost several patriotic wats, the blatant conflicts and division of territories began.

The Yalu Confederation, Weisman, Tulip, and some other middle- or even small-scale countries.

Each of them supported their own representatives and ambitious leaders, doing their best to grab as much profit and supplies as they could by politically manipulating the area.

That was also when Whitman’s family had gone onto the ocean and contacted foreign merchants, doing their business in trade. As locals from the East Continent, they had made contact with many foreigners over the years, and this did improve their standing somewhat. But all that was not as shocking as an actual foreign friend.

Foreigners always looked down on the East Continent, especially ones from the strong countries. For Whitman abruptly brought a young blonde man here, it truly shocked everyone and left a huge impact.

Such pure golden hair could only be found in some of the strongest countries on the other end of the sea. Such as Weisman, such as Tulip, such as the Yalu Confederation…

Those were the three strongest countries…

The military punk Zhao did indeed pull back a little, and looking at the little girl on the floor, he noticed that blood was leaking out the corner of her mouth. Evidently, this was getting complicated.

But even if there was a foreigner here, he still did not want to let go of his long-awaited dream, to get a secret technique that truly suited him. His dream of many years could finally be fulfilled, such an intense temptation rapidly forced down his urge to run away.

"It is a serious crime to secretly learn a Prohibited secret technique! This is the Prohibition from the Immortal Palace, a law supported by the Weisman authorities, you would know that as well, right, sir?" The military punk Zhao thought hard, and forcefully found a wordy excuse for himself. It was just that he was using the local language of the East Continent, so he had no idea if the other party could understand him.

Garen smiled slightly, revealing a mouthful of pearly whites. Beside him, Captain Whitman was prepared to translate for him.

But it was not as though he had done nothing over these past few days on the boat, so as soon as he spoke, it was in fluent East Continent language.

"Prohibition? The Immortal Palace’s Prohibition? What is that? Could you explain it to me?"

"Uh…" The man Zhao hesitated.

"I was the one who taught her the martial arts, do you have any opinion about that?" Garen immediately declared that he was the one who taught Lindsay.

He did not care about any Martial Prohibition, or any warlordism, as the terrifying ruthless killer from the Black Swamp Palace, a legend even in the Totem World, that was even more so in this Secret Technique World with its lower combat level.

Be it the Immortal Palace, or the Demon Gate, if they got in his way, then they had better be prepared to pay in blood.

He was not one of those old-fashioned justice warriors, in order to achieve his own goals, although he was not completely immoral, it was still only natural that he would choose the most effective way to solve a problem.

He stood here and traded useless words with these two, just to express two things.

One, the Whitman family was not extremely close to him, as proven by the question he did not care about Lindsay who was lying on the ground. That was also to prevent that family from getting too involved with his problems.

Two, Garen still thought it was necessary to bequeath a dead person with a few words.

The man named Zhao was already feeling something ominous, his right hand reaching for the gun behind his waist.

But all of a sudden, his whole body gave a jolt, his movements stiff and unable to move. It was not just him, the other man beside him who had come with him had also stiffened, and could not even speak, even his expression did not change. But he could see the same terror and fear in the other person's eyes.

They could not move at all!

It was as though all the blood in his body would not listen to him.

Demonic arts!! This was demonic arts!!!

No wonder the Immortal Palace declared the Prohibition, such a terrifying martial arts… It was like there was an avalanche in Zhao’s heart, his wariness from before collapsing instantly in the face of extreme terror.

Garen smiled at him slightly.

"What a coincidence, I was just looking for you, come with me. Let's discuss this properly."

He said a few words to Whitman softly, and led the way directly to a small teahouse outside the crowd. The two military punks followed him quickly, not saying a thing.

"Alright, break it up, everybody, break it up!!" Behind him, Whitman’s subordinate was yelling, and only then did Whitman wipe the sweat off his head, carrying the unconscious Lindsay off to find a doctor.

**************

The three of them sat down on the second floor of the teahouse, taking Garen's favorite position closest to the window, and nobody dared to take any of the three places around them, the owner forced a smile as he served them a pot of high-quality tea, and then hurriedly rushed downstairs, too afraid to say anything more.

Garen very naturally controlled the blood inside their bodies, taking away their wallets, opening it up and counting the money inside. There were only seven or eight pieces of silver inside, as well as some scattered copper coins, he wondered how much that would buy.

He put them all into one pouch and kept it carefully, tying it to his waist, and then Garen smiled at the two of them.

"Don't be scared, you will always come across some obstacles in life, this is just a small trial in your lives."

He slowly released the control he had over their faces.

The military punk named Zhao opposite him had a smile that looked worse than if he cried. He was already a hundred percent sure that he had bumped into a person from the Demon Gate that truly hated the Immortal Palace, or perhaps even a demonic martial artist who was wanted by both sides!

"My lord, please tell me if there's anything you need, we will definitely tell you anything we know, everything we can!"

"Is that so?" Garen smiled slightly.

"Then, please tell me everything about the Martial Prohibition…" The smile on his face grew deeper and deeper.

They dare to declare a Martial Prohibition, prohibiting the White Cloud Gate’s martial arts…

Hahaha… Immortal Palace, how dare you!

Translator’s notes:

A late Neolithic period in ancient Chinese history.

From 1912, after the fall of the Qing Dynasty, to 1949 in China.

Chapter 555: Gather 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After sitting in the teahouse for more than half an hour, Garen quickly found out most of the information in even more detail thanks to this punk Zhao.

The East Continent was too far away from the three main continents, the martial arts world here was relatively independent, but the influence of the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate was still prevalent here. The Martial Prohibition was still the best way for regular martial artists to obtain powerful secret techniques.

After hearing all the information this guy had, Garen fell into deep thought.

His motive was very simple, he just wanted to find Ying Er first, or anyone related. But now the Immortal Palace’s Martial Prohibition made this thought slightly harder.

Then how could he find the people he wanted as soon as possible?

The best way was to borrow other powers, if he could borrow a pre-existing large-scale power, he could accomplish whatever he wanted to do with half the effort.

"How is the situation here in the local martial arts world?" As he thought it, Garen decided to just ask.

"L-Locally, there are three main sects, the White Dew Gate, the Black Killer Gate, and the Dragon Gate…" The military punk Zhao hurriedly replied. "If you're looking for the elite fighters of the three main sects, I can also help you, I know an outer ring disciple of the Black Killer Gate, they would definitely be of use to…"

"And then? Since there is already a self-made system here in the East Continent, then there would surely be someone with as much influence as some of the Immortal Palace’s or the Demon Gate's power here? Otherwise they would surely have been swallowed up, right?" Garen asked calmly.

"Naturally, naturally, the White Dew Gate’s Yue Qingdi is one of the East Continent’s Three Absolutes, and there's the Dragon Gate’s Yu Qingzi, and the Black Killer Gate’s freelance guest, Master Sanshan, oh, they are all what you martial artists call Aura Condensation level fighters."

"Aura Condensation?"

Garen had heard some natural-born elite fighters use this term back on Earth, to think it had the same meaning here.

White Dew Gate, Black Killer Gate, Dragon Gate, these were the three strongest martial arts factions here on the East Continent.

"That means they can almost liquify their aura, the combat classics mentioned three states, gas, liquid and solid, these states represent the levels of the Grandmasters of Combat. Other than that, the three main sects are all in cahoots with three of the main military warlords, forming alliances, of the four military warlords, Kong, Lin, Zhao, and Hu, only the Hu army does not have the support of a martial arts family." The military punk Zhao spilled everything he knew, telling Garen everything at once.

Garen mused slightly, he knew the levels of aura very well. The White Dew Gate, based on the name itself, it might have some connection with the White Cloud Gate, so that might be worth a visit. The only problem was what excuse he should use to go there. Should he just pull out his own White Cloud Gate identification, or he go over there quietly?

Garen found it troublesome, so he decided to forgo thinking too much about it, he would just find the White Dew Gate first.

"Take me to the White Dew Gate, I'll let you go once we get there." He looked at the military punk Zhao in front of him calmly, "What's your name?"

"Zhao… Zhao Jun…." The military punk Zhao kept shaking all over, watching as Garen's expression grew calmer and calmer, there was an ominous feeling in his heart.

Whumph.

Just then, his friend beside him fell forward onto the table and remained there motionless, as though drunk.

Zhao Jun’s heart skipped a beat, and his face went instantly pale. He could feel, his friend's body beside him grow colder, and colder…

He saw Garen, who was sitting opposite him, smile slightly, revealing eerily white teeth.

***************

Between the green ocean of trees, amidst the rise and fall of the.mountains, the uneven tide of the trees seemed to have been covered by a green carpet.

In the middle of it was a twisting small white road, like a grey-white cotton thread in the sea of trees.

"Sixty years of Ying Xu, each as temperate as a cold summer’s day."(1)

Garen frowned as he looked at the red words on the white mountain cliff. Even standing on a small path and looking from a distance, he could tell that the words were written with steely power and depth. They gave off the air of being carefree but also delicate.

Zhao Jun was behind him, pulling two healthy black horses, his attitude timid and respectful.

"This is Ying Xu Valley?" Garen turned back and asked.

"Yes, yes it is." Zhao Jun nodded hard. "This is the place the White Dew Gate receives guests!" he said very certainly.

"Then why isn't there a single person here?"

"It's morning now, someone will probably be coming soon… And the White Dew Gate’s standard is unnaturally high, many people have given up on being accepted as disciples." Zhao Jun replied without hesitation.

These days, he had to withstand the feeling of his body temperature lowering every night, feeling as though he was on the verge of death, that feeling as though he was sinking into an endless darkness had increased his respect and fear toward Garen to the highest possible degree. He was even nicer to Garen than he was to his own father.

Garen nodded nonchalantly, and strode down a fork into the forest beside the stone wall.

There was a cool green bamboo forest on either side of the branching path, the light was slightly dim here, and the air was rather cool, making the whole place somewhat creepy.

One in front of the other, the two of them walked slowly down the path while pulling their horses beside them, and in no time at all, a grey-black wooden square mountain entrance appeared in front of them, with the sign of the Ying Xu Valley hanging over the entrance.

There was a flight of stone stairs beneath them, leading directly down and deeper into the mountain entrance. They could see that the steps kept extending upwards, reaching for the top, and the peak was veiled with a white mist so that the end could not be seen.

There was a young man in green at the mountain entrance, sweeping the floor lightly with a broom.

Garen saw the sweeping young man, his eyes narrowing slightly, he could vaguely see a hint of the White Cloud secret technique blood qi channeling method in the boy's actions, with the power of his Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, he could not miss any movement of liquids within a two hundred meter radius. Naturally, he would be very clear about the movements of this young man's blood.

"Spare me, sir! Spare me, sir!" Beside him, Zhao Jun suddenly howled, turning around and running away.

Garen did not even look at him, flicking his finger towards the back.

Psst!

Zhao Jun collapsed on cue, red and white blood fluids flowing slowly from the back of his head. He never moved again either.

The young man who was sweeping over there paled instantly, screaming and throwing his broom down as he immediately ran up the mountain.

"Somebody, help!! Somebody!! There's been a murder!!"

The young man practically scrambled away on all fours, disappearing in an instant.

Garen did not bother with him either, and just walked up the stairs himself. Before walking for too long, he heard the clanging of a bell from above, followed by the sound of many disorganized footsteps.

Garen sped up, climbing more than ten steps in one stride, and soon enough, a green-black temple appeared in front of his eyes.

There were clouds and mist surrounding the temple, as though he was in a divine mist, and just then the doors opened wide, several elderly people dressed in black striding out of the door, surrounded by their disciples in green, walking towards the stone steps.

Seeing Garen appear, the elders in black all froze for a moment, and immediately looked wary.

"This layman…"

"Haha… There really is a shadow of the Behemoth secret technique…" Garen's eyes lit up slightly. "Summon your leader."

"Dear sir layman, for what reason doth you come?"

One of the old men asked wordily.

"I'm looking for your White Dew Gate for something." Garen grinned.

"How insolent…" There was a dissatisfied voice from the crowd. The people moved slightly, it seemed like the disciples of the White Dew Gate were growing restless.

"I am the person in charge here, Bai Yuqing." Suddenly there was a flash of a shadow, and an old man with snow-white hair appraisers between Green and the others, wearing white Taoist robes and holding a horsetail whisk in his hand. He looked thin as a deity, as though he was separate from the mortal world.

"Sir layman, you have a deep gaze, it is obvious from a glance that you are no simple person, so why don't we all sit down for a cup of cooling tea, and exchange some of our martial studies experiences?"

"Bai Yuqing, is it?" Garen smiled slightly, "Looks like you're the strongest person here."

Before he finished speaking, his figure flashed, disappearing from where he stood.

Bai Yuqing’s heart tightened as well, and he also disappeared from the spot.

The two figures instantly clashed once in the empty space in front of the Taoist temple, brushing past each other.

Garen's figure slowly appeared at the temple entrance, and behind the crowd, while the old priest Bai Yuqing’s face was deathly pale, standing in front of the steps and wavering on his feet.

"Im-impressive Qinggong(2)..." He raised his right hand, the sleeve on his right forearm had had a large chunk shaved off, and he only noticed afterward. "I thought that learning up to Triple Floor Qinggong was already impressive enough, to think…"

As one of the White Dew Gate’s elders, he was a powerful old elite fighter even amongst the Grandmasters of Combat, so even his bodily functions had decreased with age, his experience had increased instead. The kungfu he took the most pride in was his ultimate Qinggong called the Triple Floor. But he did not expect that this young man who suddenly showed up today would break past it.

The people from the temple watching them all had terrible complexions now, shocked speechless, even their ancient Grandmaster of Combat had lost in one move, that meant nobody in all of this mountain sect could stop him, if they were to accidentally provoke this man…

In this chaotic world where lives were worth nothing and people killed without batting an eyelid, anything could happen.

Instantly, it was absolutely quiet around the temple entrance, all the gazes were trained on Garen.

"Your Excellency…"

"I need the White Dew Gate to help me find some people." Garen voiced out his demand straight away, "The people from the old White Cloud Gate back on Stonecliff Continent, as well as, the people from the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate."

Before his words stopped reverberating, everyone’s pupils instantly dilated.

The Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate!

"You are a filthy survivor of the Southern Sky Gate…"

Before that voice in the crowd finished his sentence, there was a bam and his head exploded, red and white brain parts splashing everywhere like a watermelon.

A filthy survivor of the Southern Sky Gate!

"I am the White Cloud Gate Master, the number one Divine General of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, Garen Trejons Lombard, and I hereby summon all my gate members, be it the White Cloud Gate or the Southern Sky Gate."

Garen’s voice shook the whole temple, like rumbling thunder, and some of the weaker young people had gone all numb, nearly falling to the ground.

"The Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate!! You… you…" Bai Yuqing’s face twisted, the others had not experienced that era, they did not know the terror and vastness of that battle, only they of the older generation knew, back then he had been one of the martial arts disciples who had headed to the Black Smoke Island, and he had personally witnessed that earth-shaking battle with his own eyes.

"Ga-Garen?! You're Garen?! The King of the Century!!" Bai Yuqing's scalp had gone numb, all the strength he had gathered in his body instantly scattering, his gaze on Garen as though he had seen a ghost.

"Spread the word for me." Garen's face was calm, "There's no problem, is there?"

There was a loud booming noise.

With Garen in the center, a terrifying blood-like aura exploded in an instant, in just that moment, it had utterly engulfed the whole temple.

The blood-like aura seemed to dye even the sky red, and a strange eerie wail began to ring out.

Translator’s notes:

Raw ‘盈虚一甲子,寒暑六月天’, ‘Ying Xu’ from the name of the valley also means change, turbulence, deterioration.

轻功, lit. light technique. A Chinese gravity-defying martial arts technique extremely common in wuxia. It’s the stuff that makes people zip around like they’re on wires.

Chapter 556: Gather 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Several days later…

Boom!!

A fist covered in a black metal fist glove instantly pierced through a tree barely thick enough for one person to hug with the length of their arms, creating a perfectly round and smooth hole, as though a high-speed diamond-tipped drill had gone through it.

"The White Cloud Palace Master…" The man wearing the fist gloves panted hard, his eyes reddening.

He raised his head abruptly.

Ahhh!!!!

The howl of frustration and anger instantly reverberated throughout the whole valley.

"He’s not dead… not dead!! Hahahaha…" The man threw his head back and laughed, "Not dead! Teacher! He really isn’t dead!!!"

"Even if he really isn’t dead, that person had been at the level of King of the Century even back then, do you really think you can take your revenge?" The man’s expression changed instantly, and he smiled strangely, his voice even turning to that of a piercing woman’s voice.

"Teacher died, but he didn’t!? He didn’t die?!" The voice instantly changed again, becoming a man’s voice once more. The man held his head and stumbled a few steps back.

"If that person is the real deal, you won’t be able to kill him." The woman’s voice appeared again. "You are still one step away from King of the Century."

"Why don’t you ask about that guy’s level?" The man’s voice gave a low laugh."

"That’s right, what if it’s a false alarm?" The girl’s voice laughed softly. "Unfortunately, the name Garen had long been completely silenced, the only ones who know this name are all from the older generation, and the young ones have no idea what the name means. Even if someone impersonated him, an elite fighter who could defeat the White Dew Gate elder, who looks young, knows that name, and can say even Garen’s surname without mistake, when he stands out like that to gather his gate members, he could invite enemies first if he’s not careful. In that case, that person would either be a fool, or truly a survivor of the Southern Sky Gate, y’know~~"

"A hidden expert, is it?" The man’s voice said coldly.

"Who knows?" The woman’s voice slowly fell silent, and spoke no more.

In the forest, only the man was left standing quietly alone there, not moving at all.

*****************

"How’s the Divine Master’s condition?"

In a white gazebo, two people dressed in black were playing chess, talking in low voices as they listened to the howls and roars from the forests, neither of them seeming particularly bothered, evidently used to it.

"Not too bad, last time there was someone who impersonated the King of Nightmares, and this is even better, they even dare to impersonate the King of the Century, aren’t they bold…"

"Not necessarily, with that kind of aura, that person does not need to impersonate any elite fighter, it would be too easy for him to just make his own name for himself."

"He is directly declaring war with our Immortal Palace. Or rather, this could very well be a ploy from the other factions directed at us."

"Interesting…"

The two of them took turns with their moves, moving extremely quickly, but with every rise and fall of their hand, the mill-sized chess board still kept on staying in play, remaining in a strange state of balance.

"It is most likely that there really was an expert born from the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate. There might even be a shadow of the Demon Gate in there."

******************

In the thick forests of the East Continent

The young woman in the skin-tight black clothes stumbled, leaning on a tree bark after a few steps, lowering her head to pant as she rested, then she continued laboring her way forward.

The light of noon was bright, the golden sunlight coming down through the leaves, making the whole forest hot and humid.

The girl’s vision was growing blurred, she rubbed her eyes hard, and continued looking forward as she rushed forward.

The sweat on her body had already totally soaked her black clothes, plastered to her body, and onto the wound on her back, making it sting with pain.

Suddenly, her foot lost its footing, as though she was tripped by something, and she fell forward slightly, dropping to the ground with a bam.

"Cherry!" Suddenly there was a panicked woman’s voice from afar.

A woman with white clothes and black hair made a few hasty leaps, landing beside the girl and hurriedly helping her up.

"I’m fine." The girl was slightly dizzy for a while, but now she opened her eyes again, pushing the woman away, as she stood up on her own, leaning onto a large tree beside her.

"Aunt Nora, how’s the situation up north? I was ambushed here too, so it must be even worse up north!" She forcefully steadied her head, dizzy from blood loss, and asked quietly.

The black-haired woman frowned, and looked at her worriedly, but had no choice except to reply hurriedly.

"In the north, with the protection of Arielle and the others, they managed to evacuate most of the people, but there were still three people who… fell…"

The girl fell silent.

"That damn Immortal Palace!" She smashed her fist onto the tree trunk next to her, looking down so that her expression could not be seen.

"The Immortal Palace pulled off this ambush splendidly, it was arranged and directed by the Young Divine Master Jessian himself. There were fifteen different-sized sects surrounding us, they are all led by the best Grandmasters of Combat." The woman in black, Nora, replied carefully. "Thank goodness we still have news of you, Miss, or else this time we’ll truly have…"

"I need to hurry back, if this goes on for much longer, Daddy and the others will be in danger." The girl said softly.

"But with the news leaked this time, you’ll be suspected, Miss! If you go back now, and if your injuries are discovered…"

"Say no more!" The girl’s expression was determined, she raised her head, revealing a fair, pretty, and pure young girl’s face, her eyes were actually a rare wine-red color. Her shoulder-length purple-black hair was tied into a ponytail, well-defined and handsome. Her body was well-balanced in its curves, but she looked no more than fifteen or sixteen years old, so no matter how she acted mature, there was still a hint of childishness.

"If I don’t go back for too long, the Moon Star Gate’s young gate master will definitely suspect something, and then Father and the family will be involved as well!"

"But, if it is discovered that you got the news from the Moon Star Gate’s young gate master…"

"I will handle it myself, don’t worry." The girl’s back was against the black-haired woman, "Aunt Nora, please help me put on some medicine, I can’t reach it myself."

"Sigh…"

Nora saw the mess of flesh and blood on the girl’s back, and her heart twinged in pain.

The fate and responsibility of the White Cloud Gate and the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate were all on the shoulders of a mere fifteen-year-old girl to bear alone, even if she was from a family that had borne the King of the Century, even if she herself had outstanding martial talent, even if she had just reached the level of Grandmaster of Combat right now, and was mature beyond her years.

But she was still a little girl that had just turned fifteen.

Her parents, and siblings, all of them had died at the ends of the Immortal Palace. She wandered around since young, and then in order to take revenge, she had given herself up to adoption by a family of good Samaritans. On the surface, she was a rich young heiress, but secretly, she was a powerful Grandmaster of Combat with great talent and a family legacy. And every day, she had to interact with her suitors to gain information…

After hurriedly bandaging up the girl’s gruesome injuries, putting on some specially-made medicine, and taking out the clothes that had been prepared beforehand so she could change into them, Nora finally released a long breath.

"Your injuries are too serious, you must not fight within a month, nor can you activate your aura, or you run the risk of becoming paralyzed…"

But the girl seemed not to hear her.

"I’ll go back now. With the help of Big Sister Arielle and the others from the Azure Continent, make sure nobody comes out for anything these next few days, as for your daily supplies, I’ll have my maid secretly send them to a fixed place, be careful when you come to receive them."

"Got it."

"Alright, go." The girl said calmly.

"Cherry… be careful!"

"Mn."

The girl watched Aunt Nora leap away, and quickly picked up the clothes she had changed out of, disappearing into the forest and feeling instantly relieved.

"There really are threats on both sides… Grandma Ying Er, if it were you, how would you solve this right now…" She muttered, lost in thought.

*********************

White Dew Mountain Green Cloud Temple

On a large square plaza in the middle of the temple, a white cement square, there were about a hundred elite fighters gathered in the plaza, the hot golden sunlight sparkling, but none of them felt hot.

Each of them felt ice-cold in their hearts.

In the middle of the plaza, there was a man with blonde hair dressed in tight black clothes, he stood in the center with a calm expression, surrounded by four elites of the gate with their floaty white beards. All four of them wore green, but just then, their clothes had been soaked in sweat.

An old man in white sat beside the plaza, his eyes lowered, but his hand was trembling slightly on his horsetail whisk, indicating how extremely disturbed his heart was.

The two middle-aged man behind him were already gripping their fists tightly, their nails digging into their palms but they did not even know it. Their gazes were just fixed hard on that handsome young man with shoulder-length blonde hair in the plaza.

"Your Excellency Garen, we have already helped you pass on the message you wanted us to, may we know if you have any other requests? You can just speak them all at once." The old man in white who was sitting in the chair spoke in a low voice, his expression solemn, but the weakened tone in his words unhidden.

Garen also felt that bullying these average elite fighters had no point whatsoever, with his prowess in his Evil Technique, he just had to use a little force, and these people would not be able to resist at all, their blood would be controlled by the Evil Technique in an instant, becoming his own puppet. Although they had trained their secret techniques for many years, and the blood in qi in their body was a lot more stable, but to Garen, even a larger ant was still an ant, and could still be stomped to death without him noticing.

Before he even released his presence, the elders around him were already too scared to move, and even too scared to fight.

"I had wanted to borrow your White Dew Gate’s power for a bit, the people from the Immortal Palace and the Demon Gate will reach here sooner or later, so I would still need you, Gate Master Yue, to arrange a location for us."

"Do you really have that much confidence, Your Excellency?" Yue Qingdi could not tell how strong Garen was at all, he felt Garen’s blood qi was as vast and limitless as an ocean, but how could a human’s blood qi reach such a level? This was evidently an illusion caused by his secret techniques. But he had never heard of such a secret technique effect!

He did not dare to make a move, he was one of the East Continent’s Three Absolutes, the strongest Grandmaster of Combat, once he made a move, it was normal for him to win, that would be fine. But once he lost, that was a fatal blow to the reputation of the White Dew Gate.

"Confident? Haha." Garen raised an eyebrow, this was not a matter of confidence at all, it was just that they were not on the same level to begin with.

"Regarding the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, I have some new information here." A white-haired elder next to Yue Qingdi spoke suddenly.

"Do speak." Garen looked at this person.

That elder glanced at the Gate Master, received his approval, and immediately spoke again.

"The Immortal Palace’s Young Divine Master is gathering elites to surround and exterminate the… members of the Southern Sky Gate, and there is also the cooperation of the Lin family army, we don’t know what the results are. I just received the intel as well."

"Extermination?" Garen’s eyes narrowed, "Location?"

"I don’t know… but we can go investigate!"

Chapter 557: Hurried 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The blistering midsummer period has arrived. Do you have any plans to beat the heat, Xiao Ying?"

Within the three southern provinces under the jurisdiction of the Ling Army, inside Great West City, one of the provincial capitals of the south.

Inside a large square courtyard on the outskirts of the provincial capital, numerous maids in white skirts accompanied Xiao Ying while she changed into a Western school girl's uniform of a white shirt and black skirt. She walked with an effeminate boy slowly, strolling through the little flower garden in the courtyard.

The weather was scorchingly hot, forcing the people in the garden to constantly spray themselves with water mist from the sprinkles to cool down slightly.

Xiao Ying suppressed the pain from the wound on her back and pretended to casually observe the flower pots in the corner of the courtyard instead.

"Beat the heat? Father said that he has already ordered some ice blocks from the Zhao family's shop. Once we put them inside the house to distribute cold air, we won't have to suffer blistering hot days anymore."

"Ice blocks, huh? That's not a bad idea," said the young man with a smile. "But I heard that the Zhao family's shop is going to move soon. Do you know the whole story?"

"I'm unsure…"

"Rumor has it that the tracks of Demon Warriors have been discovered nearby recently. These individuals won't shy away from any form of evil; they live to kill and burn. Not just the Zhao family, but many other merchants plan to move further away as well."

"Does Moon Star Gate not have any way to help?" asked Xiao Ying in a slightly surprised tone.

"Of course we have our ways. However, our plans were leaked last time, allowing the Demon Warriors to escape. Therefore, before we find the source of their information, we will not act rashly," whispered the Moon Star Gate Young Master.

He gazed at Xiao Ying's side profile longingly.

"The world has been troubled with chaos recently. Xiao Ying, uncle, and aunty should move into the courtyard beside my house temporarily. It would be good to be taken care of."

"Won't this… be very troublesome for Lord Gate Master?"

"Of course not!" laughed Moon Star Gate Young Master. "After the information was leaked previously, I'm afraid that the Demon Warriors may find out the relationship between Xiao Ying and myself. If you don't move over, I'm worried that you may be in danger sooner or later…"

He implied something by lowering his voice for an extended period of time.

Danger?

Xiao Ying felt a chill creep down her spine and realized that he was threatening her.

Dangerous Demon Warriors? Afraid that if she didn't move in, the experts at Moon Star Gate would not hesitate to invite the Demon Warriors over for a bit?

"I will discuss this with Father for a while." Xiao Ying combed through her long hair, allowing it to curl around her fingers.

"Xiao Ying." Young Gate Master reached his hand out and attempted to raise the girl's chin, but failed to do so when she dodged slightly. "You know my true intentions."

"Young Gate Master, please behave!" Xiao Ying took a small step back while her face turned red in embarrassment.

"Hahaha…" laughed Young Gate Master loudly as he turned around and left with his subordinates.

The noise could be heard across the courtyard gates for a while, before disappearing into the noisy murmurs of the faraway street.

Xiao Ying stood on her original spot and inhaled deeply. Only one maid, Xiao Yu, remained at her side. Currently, this little girl who was a year younger than herself was currently looking on at her mistress worriedly.

"He's suspicious of me…" said Xiao Ying softly.

"That can't be… Wasn't he prepared to protect milady?" asked Xiao Yu quietly in a surprised tone while she glanced at their surroundings immediately.

She was actually a disciple of Southern Holy Fist Gate and had trained there ever since she was young. After meeting Xiao Ying at Southern Gate, her life was taken over, and she had been with her ever since to take care of her daily life.

"This person seems gentle and courteous on the surface, as well as humble on all fronts. However, he must have been a secretly ruthless and cunning individual in order to receive Young Divine Master Jessian's admiration. Since the information was leaked, they will definitely investigate everyone individually, and I'm certain that I have been listed as one of the suspects," analyzed Xiao Ying calmly.

"Then… Then what do we do??!" Xiao Yu turned pale immediately.

"Moon Star Gate Young Master is viciously cruel to the bone. He is only doubtful now but has yet to confirm anything. If this was not the case, he would not waste time speaking but would have captured me immediately instead." Xiao Ying paused. "There's no need to panic now. Go and arrange for some manpower immediately and prepare a way out for Father and Mother. We don't have much time to think this over."

"Alright! I will contact them at once."

"Be careful not to be found out."

"Understood."

As she watched her maid Xiao Yu leave, Xiao Ying twirled a few strands of her own hair gently while standing in front of a pot of three-petaled white flowers, looking on pensively.

That fellow definitely had his doubts. As Moon Star Gate always carried out their tasks seriously, their Gate Masters would comprise of two Elders and three Grandmasters of Combat. Meanwhile, my wounds would make it impossible for me handle them and even if I healed completely, I would not be on equal footing with these senior experts. In my current condition, not only would I be unable to fight the Grandmasters of Combat, successfully defeating that perverted Young Gate Master would be an uncertainty as well.

She would need to think of a surefire plan…

Suddenly, the sound of many people's footsteps echoed faintly from outside the courtyard.

Bang!

The courtyard gates were swung open at once before the maid Xiao Yu's half-naked body crashed inside. She used both of her arms to shield her pale, trembling chest but remained as an erotic sight nonetheless.

Xiao Yu sobbed helplessly.

"Milady!"

"Just a little maid. I was wondering who leaked our secret movements. I never expected that it would be her…" said Moon Star Gate Young Master in a gentle voice as he walked into the courtyard slowly with Xiao Yu's white undergarment in his hand.

"Xiao Yu!!" Xiao Ying's face was deathly pale as she rushed towards Xiao Yu and held her. "Yannen! What are you doing?!!" She raised her head and looked at Young Gate Master angrily while using her own body to shield Xiao Yu as best as she could.

"I'm clearly rebelling against you…" Young Gate Master Yannen smiled gently. "This girl is a spy that the Demon Warriors hid beside you. Since she leaked my Gate's secrets, she might have plotted against you as well, Xiao Ying. I'm just here to help you."

"Demon?? I don't know of any Demons! She is only my maid and my closest sister!" Glistening teardrops appeared in Xiao Ying's eyes faintly. Half of it was fake, but the other half was real.

"I only have your best interests at heart, please don't blame me…" Yannen's expression remained unchanged, but the corners of his lips curled upwards slightly.

Whoosh!

He opened a white paper fan in his hand.

Suddenly, two young women ran through the gates and forcibly carried Xiao Yu out.

"You! Put her down!" Xiao Ying merely thought of striking them, before a sharp pain pierced through the pit of her stomach at once.

The injuries that she had sustained from the previous trip were not limited to the surface wound on her back. Instead, her heart and internal organs had suffered the heaviest injuries from the internal shock of the force. Her opponent was a refined Grandmaster of Combat who was an expert in palm destroying moves. Therefore, ten of those moves were enough for him to strike her back with his palm.

"Don't blame me, Xiao Ying. Matters that involve Demon Warriors will not be handled by me." Yannen sighed under his breath.

"Milady!!" Xiao Yu was a fourteen-year-old maid who used to be an orphan that was trained by Southern Gate ever since she was young. However, she had yet to display any hidden talents even until now. "I'm sorry! I hid the truth from milady…"

"Take her away."

The courtyard gates were closed with a ‘bang' again before Yannen allowed someone to drape a coat around Xiao Yu to protect her modesty.

"Send her to my room tonight after you've tied her up."

"Yes," replied both of the female guards quietly and obediently.

Xiao Yu closed her eyes in despair as she already knew what fate had in store for her.

Yannen seemed refined and gentle on the surface. Moreover, his appearance, talents, and fighting skills were all first class. However, his true nature revealed a deranged pervert. During troubled times like these, it was rumored that he had once used two thirteen-year-old maids as playthings and killed them during the night, and although the incident was covered up, his bad reputation continued to spread around.

The Gate Master of Moon Star Gate was also a perverted devil who liked bathing in the fresh blood of young people in a vain attempt to rejuvenate himself and retain his youth. Once she entered this place, her future days would be…

Her heart sank as she bit the inside of her mouth suddenly.

Inside the courtyard.

Xiao Ying covered her abdomen in agony while supporting herself against the wall. Her body seemed unable to move and her vision darkened slowly while the stabbing pain in her stomach felt like a saw that was slicing through her determinedly.

*******************

Within a bleak and desolate black wasteland.

Two White Dew Gate Elders escorted a white horse carriage as it traveled forth quickly. The carriage was surrounded by two groups of lightly armed knights who wore white leather gloves. They were all dressed in white clothes with the symbol of White Dew Gate on their backs in large white letters.

They were the White Dew Gate squad that was escorting Garen on his quest to find the Young Divine Master. Their current moods were now different from when they were at the headquarters. Currently, the older guys from White Dew Gate were respectful while both of the Elders had calm expressions on their faces as well, as if they were not dissatisfied with anything.

Garen's casual pointers during these past few days had helped many of their disciples upgrade themselves while two of their expert-level Grandmasters of Combat received benefits as well. The feeling of almost breaking through a bottleneck situation and Garen's continuously courteous attitude that was not only present when they entered the mountain gate had a positive effect on everyone's demeanor, allowing both parties to respect and admire each other more.

Inside the carriage.

Garen sat in repose with his eyes closed while both of his hands were subconsciously pressed into a triangle in front of him. Shrouds of dull blue auras rotated around his hands slowly like little blue airholes.

A good while passed before Garen opened his eyes suddenly while the auras in his hands dispersed slowly and disappeared into the air.

"White Dew Gate's Airhole Tactic makes some sense now. It seems like it has somewhat gotten close to the Living Secret Technique already…" pondered Garen in slight satisfaction. Hundreds of years had passed but no one in White Dew Gate had learned this Airhole Tactic successfully. As Garen had promised to help the Gate amend and perfect their Secret Techniques, Gate Master Yue Qingdi had also agreed to open up his entire depository to Garen in exchange, allowing him to examine it as he pleased.

The numerous remaining Secret Technique exercises and battle skills increased Garen's reading and memorizing abilities. However, he was most concerned about the Secret Technique that no one had been able to learn in hundreds of years: Airhole Tactic.

This Secret Technique had neither attack effects nor defense abilities. Moreover, it was not a powerful internal energy Secret Method that would be able to increase one's state and potential temporarily.

Its only use was to condense one's own physical strength and blood qi to form a purer aura that would burst forth.

Garen was very interested in this because his Living Secret Techniques had already condensed themselves into the most compact Soul Seed, which was deeply rooted in the most distant corner of his soul. The revolving Airhole Tactic would condense the Soul Seed further, and although the effect was slow, he could truly feel that the Soul Seed was being condensed right now.

The difficulty of this Secret Technique lay in the extremely accurate control of that alternated one's aura, blood qi, and physical force. All of these came naturally to Garen, but to the other Secret Technique Users of this world, it was more difficult than touching the sky.

"I never thought that I would be able to reap these unexpected rewards just by flipping some random pages…" Garen moved his palms away. "Stop the carriage."

The carriage began to stop gradually at once, and although the coachman had yet to signal the horses to halt, he could see that the two white horses had already stopped in their tracks on their own.

Chapter 558: Hurried 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two of the Elders that accompanied him were the first to react before they all scanned their surroundings vigilantly.

The White Dew Gate experts around them tensed up while their powers circulated around, a display that they were ready to make a move at any time.

Suddenly, they heard a demure and charming female voice in their surroundings.

"You are truly worthy to be called the hidden experts of Southern Holy Fist Gate. I thought that I had concealed myself well enough, but never expected that there would be people who would be aware of my whereabouts from twenty meters away."

The female voice spoke in a strangely accented East Continent language, but before she had finished speaking, a bewitching woman in a black veil and a tight fitting short black silk dress had appeared on the black earth in front of the plains suddenly.

The woman's black hair was tied up and she held a long, thin sword in her hand. She was poised gracefully as she stood in front of the carriage alone, blocking its path. She had a pair of eyes that were as bright as stars, while the corners of her eyes were turned upwards slightly, making it look as if she were smiling.

"Demoness Lola!!" One of the two Elders could not help but yell in horror when he recognized her.

"Has Demon Gate come into being?!" The other Elder flipped his hands over before two silver daggers appeared in his palms suddenly. An extremely grave expression remained on his face.

The accompanying White Dew Gate experts had never crossed paths with people from Demon Gate before, but when they saw the stern looks on their Elders' faces, their hearts sank when they immediately realized the true power of their opponent.

"To the hidden expert who calls himself the White Cloud Gate Master, are you really unwilling to come down and meet me?" Demoness Lola smiled daintily as she walked towards the carriage slowly.

Pop!

When the tip of Lola's foot stepped within ten meters of the carriage, her expression changed suddenly while her gentle smile stiffened instantly.

Bang!

She stepped back immediately and leaped into the air like an arrow before flying backward a few moments later. Apparently, she was escaping even though she had just arrived.

Shh!

The curtains of the carriage were lifted gently while a light breeze blew past. A hand reached out in midair and caught the Demoness immediately.

Lola retreated a few meters away frantically but fell on the floor once before leaping backward quickly again.

That hand seemed as if it was able to pass through space because of some strange magic. It also attracted everyone's attention as no one paid any mind to the owner of the hand itself.

The large hand traveled a distance of more than ten minutes within a few moments before grabbing the Demoness by the throat gently while her pale, pretty face looked on in fear.

There was a sudden flash in their surroundings.

Lola's vision became blurry before she realized moments later that she was already sitting inside the carriage despite being unable to move her body at all. She was lying down on the knees of the man inside the carriage obediently while her black hair fanned around her like a waterfall.

"Black Orchid, are you alright…?" Garen reached his hand out to stroke Lola's long hair gently.

Lola, whose delicate form was still trembling moments earlier, now shook awake suddenly. She raised her head with much difficulty before laying her eyes upon a man who was as handsome as the Sun God.

Marshall Black Orchid had once planned to poison someone, and that night was etched deeply into Garen's memories.

Although Lola's appearance did not resemble Black Orchid, their quick-witted temperaments were eerily similar, meaning that if Black Orchid had not trained her personally, it would be impossible for both of them to have such similar qualities.

"Proceed with the journey."

The White Dew Gate experts looked at each other before realizing that the woman had been captured in that moment earlier, and was now unable to resist at all.

"Perhaps that person was not from Behemoth Gate… But merely an imposter…" said someone quietly.

Both of the Elders swallowed their own saliva and glanced at each other before noticing the apparent astonishment in the other person's eyes.

Although they had already anticipated that Garen would be powerful, they had never expected that he would actually be this strong. Other people would be unaware of this, but as Grandmasters of Combat who could detect Lola's presence, once they felt the heavy blood qi that surrounded her whole body and realized that she truly belonged to the Grandmaster of Combat level, they knew that she was definitely stronger than themselves.

But now she seemed like a baby chick in Garen's hands that could not rebel against him at all. Such powerful strength… Wouldn't it mean that he was undefeatable?!!

Moments later, the carriage began to move slowly again.

The control he had on Lola who was in the carriage was finally lifted.

She seemed to be unable to get up and continued lying on Garen's body instead. She also pressed her ample breasts against Garen's knees intentionally. A faint sweet smell wafted from her body and permeated throughout the carriage slowly, making everyone feel relaxed and joyful.

"Don't tell me you know Teacher Black Orchid?" she asked softly in a gentle voice, giving off a strong pitiful feeling as if she was an adorable little animal that could easily evoke the man's desire to protect her.

"You're very much like her." Garen allowed Lola to lie on his knees while he ran his hand through her smooth, shiny black hair, combing through it gently.

"Don't tell me that you're truly the legendary White Cloud Gate Master, First Heavenly General of Southern Holy Fist Gate?" asked Lola daintily. She knew that she was unable to fight back, but her opponent currently had no ill intentions towards her either. Therefore, she decided to clear up the situation before saying anything else.

Garen smiled slightly but did not reply. Instead, he turned his face away and looked out of the carriage window.

Boom!! Boom boom boom boom!!

Suddenly, series of explosions could be heard from a further distance away while the ground shook slightly.

"The soldiers from the Hu Army are practicing, huh…" Lola's eyes darted around. "I wonder what Gate Master's plans are for coming into being this time? Chief Hu Qingzhi of the Hu Army has a good relationship with my Behemoth Gate, perhaps he can help Your Excellency."

"The Hu Army, hmm?" Garen looked in that direction. "My goal is very simple, I just want to find someone from Immortal Palace."

"And after you find them?"

"Well, what plans did Behemoth Gate have for you to pay me a special visit like this?" Garen smiled without answering her directly and asked her another question instead.

When Lola heard the words ‘Behemoth Gate', her heart trembled slightly suddenly.

"The Marshall chief soldier perished and caused our Behemoth Gate to decline. Lola had no other choice but to come out and search for one that could support our Gate. Once I heard that Gate Master had left the mountain, I rushed over immediately."

She made a pitiful face.

"If Gate Master could promise to be my Gate's diplomatic Elder, then Lola… Lola would do anything you instructed…"

She lay on Garen's legs with her slim waist pushed back and her buttocks raised up high, exposing her beautiful, black silk covered long legs underneath her short dress.

This kind of naked seduction in the form of a beautiful woman with a kitten-like obedience was currently curled up on Garen's lap. Most men would not have been able to resist the temptation and would have granted her wishes right away.

"You've truly learned Black Orchid's tricks and tried to poison me when I wasn't paying attention." Garen's smile disappeared quickly before he patted Lola's buttocks gently.

The faint sweet scent in the carriage subsided completely before a gust of cold wind blew past them suddenly, before disappearing as soon as it came.

"Gate Master…" Lola's whole body shivered while she begged in a fragile voice. "Lola didn't do it on purpose…"

While she begged, her blood qi continued to flow throughout her body slowly, while a small crack appeared in the sword in her hand.

Clap!

Garen's hand slapped against her buttocks lightly again. A strong numb sensation could be felt this time, instantly causing the blood qi in Lola's entire body to shake furiously before scattering it completely.

Lola raised her head while a look of disbelief appeared in her eyes.

Within Immortal Palace and Behemoth Gate, other than Divine Master and the Demon Soldier Marshall, the strongest individuals were Young Divine Master and herself. The remaining Grandmasters of Combat were all ranked below them. Both of them were true experts with high aura condensation levels.

Her lack of prior preparation had probably resulted in her accidental capture, or perhaps it was a temporary oversight on her part. However, the blood qi in her whole body had been activated at once, and although she had secretly used a few Secret Methods to strengthen herself, she never anticipated that a single pat from her opponent would result in the complete scattering of all of her own blood qi, without him injuring himself at all.

The ability to use various Secret Methods to move and gather blood qi would only be able to scatter one's blood qi, despite the fact that her opponent was an expert that was stronger than her. This Secret Method would usually cause the user to suffer reverse blood qi damages, but this person was apparently able to scatter all of her condensed blood qi easily, without suffering any harm at all.

This ability… This strength could only be used under the circumstances that one completely understood the Secret Techniques and Secret Methods that they practiced, was clear about the flow of blood qi and possessed strength that was at least one level higher. However, it was still not as simple as what the man in front of her had just displayed.

Shock jolted through Lola's mind like waves that drifted in and out constantly.

She contemplated her current skills and realized that even if her master had still been alive, she would not have reached this far. Perhaps the Divine Master from Immortal Palace would be able to do it after he broke through…

Divine Master? Could it be that this person in front of her was actually…

The wheels of the carriage moved slowly while both of the people inside the car fell silent.

Garen smiled while looking at Lola who was leaning against him. He gently sniffed the sweet smell of hormones that were released from her body naturally while listening to the rhythmic chimes of the carriage bells, allowing his emotions to fall into an unprecedented state of calmness.

"I know where the Young Divine Master of Immortal Place is located!" whispered Lola suddenly.

A smile flashed in Garen's eyes suddenly.

*****************

Jessian held a short black blade in his hands and scrutinized it carefully.

"The technique is slightly stronger than the previous one but it has not achieved my desired standard yet." He flung the short blade away but it landed on the right side of the black platform slowly, as if it was supported by an invisible force.

One of his subordinates in black clothes came forward to store the short blade properly, before turning to leave.

Moon Star Gate Master kept watch beside him respectfully. Aside from the guards in the courtyard, the only other person there was an old man in black tight-fitting clothing who was waiting with his head lowered.

"We will definitely do everything in our power to find your desired blacksmith, so please wait a little longer," implored Moon Star Gate Master with his head bowed respectfully, much unlike the arrogant way he acted when he was in the provincial capital.

"I understand your difficulties and I know that this speed is considerably fast. Therefore, I don't mind waiting a few more days," nodded Young Divine Master Jessian faintly. "That's right, why did the remaining members of Southern Sky Gate leave? Do you discover the reason?"

"Yes, I found out that one of the remaining members of Southern Sky Gate planted himself as a spy within the city. He was probably hiding in a secluded place when they noticed one of our dispatched members…"

"I won't ask about the whole process. Can you assure me that the next ambush will not be leaked?"

"Yes! I will submit to your commands and put out the military orders at once!!" announced Moon Star Gate Master while clapping a hand against his chest.

"Then that will be all." Jessian turned to leave.

"That's right, Young Divine Master, recently at White Dew Mountain…" Moon Star Gate Master began to speak but stopped himself.

"Just say whatever you need to say. My subordinates have always spoken as they wished," said Jessian as he turned around and stood in place.

"The person who is pretending to be the White Cloud Gate Master over at White Dew Mountain is currently on his way over here, and might be charging towards you…"

"Charging towards me?" Slight changes finally appeared on Jessian's face. "Hehe, interesting. I won't go looking for him since he's already brave enough to come find me."

"He's suppressing White Dew Gate, and I'm afraid that he's not good news," Moon Star Gate Master reminded him frantically.

"It's better if he's an expert. Inform Nine Iron Gate and the other numerous, delighted factions and allow them to return with their teams."

"You mean that you want them to gather here on their own before capturing all of them with one go?" Moon Star Gate Master was a knowledgeable person and could ultimately guess Young Divine Master's intentions.

"It will be too troublesome to search everywhere. Wouldn't it be better to let them see a glimmer of hope on their own, gather them in one place, before reaping the wheat in one go once it has all ripened?" Jessian smiled gently. "Also, get your son to hurry up and settle the problems with that girl. If he dares to hinder my grand plans again…"

Moon Star Gate Master's face turned pale suddenly.

At the same time, Moon Star Gate Young Master who was waiting by the doorway turned pale as well, before he quickly sank to his knees on the ground with a ‘thump'.

Chapter 559: Declaration 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The carriage was accompanied by the sound of ringing bells as it moved forward.

Inside the carriage, Garen and Demoness Lola sat opposite each other. A short square table stood between them, and the dark red tabletop was currently filled with Go pieces. Garen chose the white pieces while Lola picked the black ones.

The player of the black pieces would usually be on the offensive side and the younger player would start the game, while the white pieces would be played by the senior player.

Garen had never expected that a game which resembled earth's Go would exist in this world with the exact same rules as well.

The white pieces had currently occupied most of the spaces on the checkerboard. Lola tried relentlessly to find an opening but could not find an empty space to place the black piece in her hand.

She raised her head and looked at Garen who sat on the opposite side of her, and pouted her lips.

"I don't want to play anymore!"

"Wasn't it your grand plan to dominate the board?" Garen smiled and asked softly. "Why aren't you going through with that?"

"What grand plan?! What's the use of a grand plan that involves dominating the board when I'm just going to die immediately?!" said Lola unhappily. "You don't even have a proper plan. You just come charging over directly before immediately destroying the layout that I planned painstakingly!"

Garen's route did not involve any grand schemes or layouts at all. His annihilation abilities were abnormally strong, allowing him to swallow his opponent's pieces whenever they came into contact. If the placement of his pieces were any better, it would be impossible for him not to win the game…

Lola put in a lot of effort to find a method that would allow her to drag her opponent out and occupy the board at the same time. Unfortunately, she spent too little time luring her opponent out, while Garen's precise calculations were too accurate, making it impossible for her to delay his moves. Moreover, her frazzled state of mind caused her pieces to be killed even faster…

"Is this a typical example of using strength to defeat skills?" said Lola in sudden realization. "When the difference between strength levels are too great, incidents like these will occur."

"It's good that you understand," nodded Garen. "In theory, skills can be used to make up for the difference in strength levels, except that there are limits to that. When you reach the stage where someone's each and every move and word requires you to rack your brains just to decipher them, that strength difference means that they can use force to defeat the skills of others."

Lola understood this principle naturally, as her master had mentioned it before.

"Wisdom needs to be used as a form of leverage and influence against an opponent to reach its full potential, is that right?"

"Wisdom is actually a form of strength as well." Garen smiled and began to sweep the pieces back into their own baskets slowly. "If your wisdom is sufficient to transform the world into your chessboard and everything else into your chess pieces, you would have achieved one of the strongest powers."

"But there are too many variables between heaven and earth. In order to reach this level, one must have basic knowledge of everything, terrifying control over information, as well as extremely powerful strength, right?" Lola asked again.

"Therefore between one's mind and strength, both of these paths have their own advantages and disadvantages. One will strengthen the physical body, while the other will give you leverage over everything. It depends on what others choose for themselves. The scientifically advanced guns and cannons of our current era are the results of the second path."

Both mind and strength were the final answers that brilliant martial artists of the past generations had been searching for.

Centuries worth of advisors, tyrannical generals, and first-rate strategists who lacked physical strength but were able to command great forces easily were once normal people that had no leverage over armies before they came into being.

Powerful generals and elite fighters that could wipe out a battlefield would ultimately face physical limitations as well, and would never be able to exceed the combined strength of multiple people.

Only the integration of the mind and strength and their mutual advancement and evolution, such as the balance between light and darkness, would be able to produce a harmonious state that was also the strongest state. From Garen's perspective, the strongest state was a strength that was powerful enough but also possessed sufficient wisdom and intelligence.

If it were compared to a measurable strength as its baseline, a strength that depended on intelligence as its leverage would not add up to much.

But when thousands of other powers were used as the baseline to be altered by intelligence, the effect would be truly terrifying.

Garen understood this. Therefore, his path had always comprised of prioritizing the advancement of his physical strength while supplementing it with wisdom. He chose this path because his talents and abilities allowed him to surpass limitations that most people could only dream of.

"Human strength will always have its limits…" said Lola regretfully while she pondered momentarily.

"That's right… The heart and mind can move the strength of countless people and gather them together, greatly exceeding the strength of an individual," nodded Garen. "That's why intelligence has no limits, while physical strength will always be limited."

Neither of them spoke for a short while, allowing the carriage to fall into silence slowly.

Garen felt somewhat emotional. Other people assumed that the road towards strength had ended, while he believed that the road was endless.

Clang… Clang…

Time ticked by before the white cuckoo clock that was hung inside the carriage rang suddenly.

Both of them glanced at the clock that read: 16:00.

Lola crouched beside the short table with a somewhat changed expression.

"Gate Master Garen, if you are truly the King of the Century that fought the final battle with the previous Divine Master, then that little girl in the provincial capital is your little sister's granddaughter…"

"Oh?" Garen was shocked.

"I've met her a few times," said Lola softly. "That little girl is the current Southern Sky Gate Master. During the battle on Black Smoke Island when you disappeared, Southern Sky Gate separated internally and the Sky Warriors formed their own groups and left the school of thought. Southern Sky Gate was once the result of the integration of twelve southern groups, but once they lost their unifying symbol and leader, a separation was inevitable. Some of them joined Immortal Palace while others joined Behemoth Gate. The ones who remained integrated themselves with White Cloud Gate, forming the current Southern Sky Gate.

"Continue…" This was the first time Garen had heard a full explanation regarding the developments of Southern Sky Gate. He had never expected that it would still be a result of the fusion with White Cloud Gate.

Lola rearranged her train of thought.

"Since they were no more Holy Fists in Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, they changed their name to Southern Sky Gate. Under the guidance of Celestial Circle Gate and King of Nightmares, their leader Ying Er was able to run everything smoothly. However, Ying Er later died of illness and left an adopted son and daughter behind, causing Southern Sky Gate to split again because of a power struggle. Since they had no ties to the new leaders, Celestial Circle Gate and King of Nightmares did not look after them anymore, while Divine Master took the opportunity to take action. Although Behemoth Gate tried to take care of them to the best of our abilities, still… Still…"

She made a sympathetic face and spoke with great sentiments. Anyone who had heard her speak would have noticed that someone who was so concerned with the developments of Southern Sky Gate had obviously tried to assist them wholeheartedly.

When Garen heard that Ying Er had passed away from sickness, waves of emotion flashed in his eyes.

"That's how the Martial Prohibition came out?"

"Mhmm," Lola nodded. "Nobody expected that senior Ying Er would place her true hope in her young granddaughter. When they found out, Immortal Palace's great forces had already been established and although Behemoth Gate wants to help, it is difficult enough to protect ourselves now…" Lola looked like she was about to burst into tears at any moment.

"Then what's going on at the current White Cloud Gate?" Garen, on the other hand, seemed unusually calm.

"Are you talking about the little school of thought in the Azure Continent?" Lola regained her composure hurriedly. "It is true that it was built by a previous White Cloud Gate disciple, but no one inherited it from long ago, and they only practice declining Secret Techniques." She was very knowledgeable, making her a worthy leader of Behemoth Gate, and also the first person in command of the soldiers there as well.

She sneaked a glance at Garen.

"You want to rebuild the ancestral gate?"

Garen smiled but did not reply.

"Andrela and King of Nightmares, are they still well?"

"Senior Andrela is currently the strongest Sword King in Celestial Circle Gate. He has been overseeing the entire group and has not shown his skills for many years. As for senior King of Nightmares… his whereabouts are unknown, but you already know that… This senior has unpredictable moods and is full of changes. Therefore, nobody has been able to track his movements… The only thing I know is that he's still alive." Following the local customs, Lola explained these matters in the East Continent language, sounding unusually fluent while using the appropriate terms.

Garen had only learned the East Continent language by speaking to that military punk Zhao. Therefore, he was not as fluent as her.

Andrela and King of Nightmares had been a pair of good friends since long ago. They had always been inseparable, and deep down in his heart, Garen knew that if he were to find one of them, the other would definitely be nearby.

"Also, please inform the members Celestial Circle Gate that Andrela and King of Nightmares should get over here right now!" said Garen indifferently.

"Using your original words?" Lola's heart beat frantically in her chest. The Celestial Circle Sword King and Nightmares were first rate masters, and although they had not made a move in many years, their powers were unfathomable. Even Divine Master tolerated Celestial Circle Gate's repeated protection of Southern Sky Gate. Some people even said that both of them would be able to defeat Divine Master in one strike if they formed an alliance.

"Of course." Garen turned his head and looked out of the carriage window. The black wild grasslands that they kept passing by formed layers of dark green ripples when the wind blew past.

Suddenly, a black pigeon flapped its wings and flew inside the carriage before landing on Lola's arm gently.

Lola glanced at Garen before lifting one of the pigeon's legs and removing the black scroll that was tied there.

She pulled the black string off and opened it.

She had only scanned through it briefly when her expression changed slightly.

"Gate Master, I'm afraid that we need to hurry up now. There have been changes in the provincial capital. Southern Sky Gate Master may be in danger."

"Give me more details." Garen's expression became faintly serious.

"Southern Sky Gate Master Xiao Ying has been put under house arrest. I'm afraid that Young Divine Master has realized her true identity."

Before she could finish speaking, Lola felt her waist tighten suddenly while her whole body became faint. Her vision was blinded momentarily before she realized that she was being held in Garen's arms. They had left the carriage and were rushing through the black wilderness hurriedly.

The sound of the wind whooshed beside her ears. She could faintly hear the sharp whistling of moving air. The scenery in front of her turned into a complete blur, and she was unable to see anything clearly despite her dynamic vision.

"Show me the way." Garen's voice was right next to her ears.

Lola was overwhelmed. When she looked in front, she could only see the wilderness, stones, and winding ashen path passing by quickly. When they rushed past a little stream by some grassy plains, she realized that the speed they were traveling at was faster than anything she had ever experienced on her own before.

"I… I can't see clearly…" said Lola in embarrassment. She was the highest ranking master in Behemoth Gate, but she could not even see her directions properly right now… Now, she had truly believed that Garen was indeed the King of the Century. Although she did not know why his appearance did not match her previous account, that was not an important matter. It was rumored that Immortal Palace's Omniscient Eye possessed the Secret Methods to memorize one's soul. Therefore, if a suitable body could be found, it would be disguised as rebirth.

Garen could only slow down temporarily so that Lola could find her bearings.

Chapter 560: Declaration 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Within Great West City, one of the provincial capitals of the south.

Xiao Ying sat on the stone bench in the courtyard, her face frozen stiff. Her foster parents sat opposite of her with worried expressions on their faces.

Her foster father was a middle-aged man with a black goatee who looked like a slender schoolmaster. Meanwhile, her foster mother was a wealthy-looking noblewoman who was usually dressed in red clothes and wore a necklace with large pearls on her neck.

Two maids stood around the three people with equally anxious looks on their faces, with gazes that occasionally darted outside the courtyard wall.

"Xiao Ying… Those people outside who say they're from Moon Star Gate, who are they actually…?" asked the man with the goatee quietly in a trembling voice.

Xiao Ying glanced outside the courtyard gates. The sound of the footsteps of the Moon Star Gate guards that were patrolling outside could be heard occasionally.

"I'm not sure either." She felt guilty for involving her foster parents.

"Moon Star Gate Young Master will be here in a moment. He said that he wanted to invite you to Moon Star Gate," said her foster mother quietly.

"There's no rush, I will go with them in a little while. Please don't worry, nothing will happen to Father and Mother." Xiao Ying forced a smile. Her current priority was to ensure her the safety of her foster parents, while the second-most important thing was to prevent the people from Southern Sky Gate from coming forth to look for her.

This was a trap!

She had been completely certain of that since the beginning. Perhaps they were unaware that she was the Gate Master of Southern Sky Gate. However, they would surely know the relationship between her and themselves. It was highly probable that their plan involved using her as bait to lure the other members of her Gate.

As Xiao Ying was still young, her intelligence had not matured fully yet. When faced with dangerous situations like these, she was unable to find a way out of harm's way even when she racked her brains. Meanwhile, Xiao Yu had also been captured, and in order to save Xiao Yu, she would also…

"It is realistically impossible, but pretend to yield to that person so that we can find an opportunity to observe the situation before making our escape," said her foster father in a hushed voice.

Xiao Ying smiled bitterly. If only it was so easy to just escape like that. It was difficult enough for Xiao Ying to use her enhanced Grandmaster of Combat senses to eavesdrop on the guards' conversation to find out that the current provincial capital was now a large prison. Furthermore, out of the manpower that Young Divine Master had gathered, more than ten of them were Grandmaster of Combat level experts, greatly exceeding their wildest dreams.

Bang!

The courtyard gates were pushed open.

Two brawny men from Moon Star Gate walked inside.

"Miss Xiao Ying, our Young Master has invited you over," said the brawny man who stood on the left loudly.

Xiao Ying shivered as she stood up and consoled her parents quietly before following both of the muscular men out of the courtyard.

She was surprised to see the captured Xiao Yu standing by the doorway with red swollen eyes. She had wanted to commit suicide but failed in the end. As a commoner who was under the surveillance of many experts, it was impossible for her to find an opportunity to kill herself.

Currently, almost twenty people from Moon Star Gate were standing around in the courtyard while an Elder with a cold gaze who was dressed in white waited on the side.

"Please, Miss Xiao Ying," said the Elder faintly.

Xiao Ying glanced at him and stiffened her face as she held Xiao Yu's hand, before sitting in the white sedan chair that was waiting for her.

"Go!"

The bearer carried the sedan chair as his feet moved quickly throughout the remote and quiet area.

After almost ten minutes, the sedan chair stopped again, before the bearer pulled the curtains by the door open.

Xiao Ying was dressed in a white dress that matched the color of the sedan chair slightly. She stiffened her expression and pulled Xiao Yu out, before noticing that she was now in a different vast courtyard that did not resemble Moon Star Gate at all.

She had been to Moon Star Gate and seen their courtyard, it was nothing like this.

There were fake mountains and a pond in this courtyard. There were golden carps inside the pond that were swimming around slowly and happily.

A blue haired youth in a white suit stood beside the pond and scattered fish food into the water slowly, smiling as he fed the carp. This person was clearly not from Moon Star Gate!

The moment she laid eyes on this person, Xiao Ying's pupils dilated when she recognized his true identity.

Jessian!

Young Divine Master Jessian, the true assailant who had assembled the Southern Sky Gate elimination team!

At the first moment, Xiao Ying had already guessed that something was amiss.

This entire courtyard was devoid of a single outsider, and even the bearer who had brought her here earlier had left quietly as well. Her acute five senses told her that there was no one within a hundred meter vicinity of this place except for the three of them.

Jessian… He was giving them a chance on purpose, a chance to rescue Southern Sky Gate. It was not a trap and there was not going to be an ambush. This was a covert plot to strike them until they collapsed completely.

He wanted to defeat the entire Southern Sky Gate's forces with nothing but his own strength!

He had openly withdrawn all of his manpower and was clearly giving Southern Sky Gate a chance to ambush him and save their own members.

But Xiao Ying's instincts told her that something was wrong because the rumors said that Jessian was not such a straightforward person who definitely had an ambush hidden somewhere deeper.

"You thought that I was waiting for you?" Jessian smiled. "How wrong."

"I don't know what you're talking about," said Xiao Ying calmly.

Jessian did not pay her any mind.

"This arena was prepared for the fellow that would appear at any moment."

Clap!

The faint sound of a footstep could be heard from the shadows of the courtyard suddenly.

Simultaneously, numerous figures in black clothes walked out of the shadows within the courtyard slowly.

Xiao Ying was able to recognize the people who had appeared. There was Aunt Nora, Teacher Yue Jian who had rushed over from the Azure Continent, Uncle Ling Feng, and Big Sis Arielle. All of the remaining Southern Sky Gate masters had also arrived.

But only Aunt Nora and Teacher Yue Jian were Grandmasters of Combat, the others…

Her heart fell into the bottom of her stomach at once.

Teacher and the others were completely unaware that Jessian had assembled an entire assassination team! Without any information from her, they were now standing in front of her blindly.

The masked members of Southern Sky Gate in black clothes moved quickly before circling around Jessian.

"Jessian, surrender yourself!" Aunt Nora held a double-edged sword in her hands and a worried expression on her face. However, out of all the people on site, the legendary Young Divine Master would probably have a certain amount of power.

Aunt Nora and Yue Jian were considered as masters within the Grandmasters of Combat who belonged to the level of liquidized auras. Young Divine Master would probably belong to the level of solidified auras. Therefore, since there was only one level between them, they might have a chance to ambush him.

She had once crossed swords with a solidifying aura master, and although there was a huge gap between their powers, Young Divine Master was still juvenile, making it highly unlikely that he would have achieved a high level.

Jessian smiled slightly.

"All of you can come forward at once."

Before he had finished speaking, he raised his right hand immediately and blocked the front of his body.

Bang!

A black whip appeared suddenly and formed a ring around the legs of the people that approached him. The ring resembled an oval that was formed by two whips, bringing the people from each side towards his temples.

Two clapping noises could be heard before Jessian brought his fingers together and aimed them directly at his opponent's ankles. He turned around before two twinkling stars flew out silently, forcing Nora who had attacked him from the other side to move backward, while a chain of fragmented shadows appeared around her body the moment she was pushed backward.

Tch!

He raised his right hand and a silver line shot out suddenly. The sound of little bells could be heard before the silver line exploded into twinkling stars that dispersed throughout the entire courtyard. They fell down like raindrops until the walls, floor, pond, and fake mountains were all covered with tiny silver steel needles.

The people from Southern Sky Gate could barely evade the hidden weapon. Just as they were about to pursue and attack Jessian, they realized that he was no longer standing in his original spot.

Whoosh! A dull noise could be heard before a man in black clothes held his shoulder and rushed off, staggering as he left.

"Southern Sky Gate! This is barely acceptable! Hahaha!!" Jessian turned into a translucent shadow that pranced around the courtyard quickly like a flash of lightning. The dots of silver light disappeared hurriedly after landing precisely on a black-clothed person every time they appeared.

Within a few minutes, four black-clothed people had suffered injuries. Although Nora had to protect Xiao Ying and Xiao Yu, she was still embarrassed when two flying needles had successfully stabbed the back of her shoulders.

It was fortunate that there was nothing unusual about the needles and that their injuries were not too serious.

While they were fighting, a large group of soldiers in yellow military uniforms filled the courtyard suddenly. The Grandmasters of Combat from the ambush team had appeared around the courtyard walls. They were surrounded by martial arts firearms, while ten mortars were placed in the vicinity.

An officer in a yellow military uniform was accompanied by a Grandmaster of Combat as they took large strides into the courtyard. Moon Star Gate Master, two other Elders, and Moon Star Gate Young Master Yannen arrived as well.

The members of Southern Sky Gate were forced into the center of the courtyard, while ten guns were pointed directly at them.

"Young Divine Master is truly wise! You anticipated that they would surely arrive at the last minute!" praised the officer in the yellow uniform happily. "These Southern Sky Gate scum commit crimes everywhere they go, and they don't shy away from killing people or setting fires. By capturing all of them in one go today, Young Divine Master truly made a great contribution towards the security of my jurisdiction!"

"You flatter me, Chief Ling," replied Jessian with a smile while a group of people gathered behind him. There were thirteen Grandmasters of Combat on site, including those from Moon Star Gate, which were probably the most powerful forces throughout the three provinces. Attempting to break out from an encirclement of such strong forces were but a fleeting dream.

"If it wasn't for my previous apprehension, Southern Sky Gate would not have existed until today." He glanced contemptuously at the group of injured black clothed people. "A simple trick was enough to capture them in one go. There wasn't a single fuss…" Boom!!!

Suddenly, a flash of black light pierced through the wall like a broadsword, passing through the large army before creating an opening in the courtyard walls with a ‘bang'.

"You waited until the final key moment to appear, can this still be considered as coping with the emergency on time?" A charming female voice echoed through the clouds of dust that filled the sky.

"It's fine as long as we achieve our goal," replied a male voice.

The sound of gunshots filled the air while worried expressions appeared on the faces of the soldiers when they realized that the finest Grandmaster of Combat had arrived.

The military officer in the yellow uniform took a few steps back quietly, allowing the other Grandmasters of Combat to shield him.

Grave looks appeared on the faces of the Grandmasters of Combat who stood beside Young Divine Master because they knew that the first-rate master had arrived. Even though they had prepared themselves mentally much earlier, they were still worried when they encountered him in the flesh.

"Demoness Lola, are you trying to interfere?" Jessian's expression changed slightly.

"Interfere?" Lola smiled daintily. "This humble lady would never dare to disturb the Heavenly General's good mood."

The clouds of dust subsided, gradually exposing the two figures.

The Demoness was dressed in a short black silk dress. Although she should have been the center of everyone's attention, they were currently focused on the golden-haired man instead.

There was a handsome man with golden shoulder length hair, a calm face, and wine red eyes whose body was currently shrouded in dark blue mist.

The moods of the encircled Southern Sky Gate members became more joyous at once. Meanwhile, Lola quietly released her grip on the thing that she was holding tightly moments earlier.

"Too weak." The man's gaze fell upon the crowd of Southern Sky Gate members.

"Too weak indeed…" Jessian smiled and opened his mouth before his expression changed instantly. The face of the golden-haired man flashed before his eyes quickly.

Tch!!

He felt a sharp pain in his forehead while he stared off into the distance blankly in his original spot. A pool of blood shot out of the back of his head before landing on the back wall quickly, as if it was shot through by an arrow.

Cold air wafted out from both of their bodies.

"Omniscient Eye… How I missed you."

Garen retracted his fingers slowly, exposing the bloodied eyeball that he had gouged out of Jessian's head.

"Divine Master… Will not… Forgive you…"

Bang.

Jessian's dead body collapsed on the ground stiffly.

The entire audience fell deathly quiet.

Chapter 561: Fame 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!

A soldier fired his gun unintentionally.

The bullet hit the ground below Garen's feet, forming a little hole in the courtyard's wet soil.

Garen pinched the eyeball in his hand. The source of telekinetic abilities, the Omniscient Eye seemed to possess unusual magical powers. It struggled in Garen's hand and tried to escape but was caught in his tight grip.

A Grandmaster of Combat would possess an abnormally tenacious Life Force. There was once a master from Celestial Circle Gate whom Garen met before he became a Grandmaster of Combat but unfortunately forgot his name, and that fellow was able to struggle for a long time before dying even though he had been gravely injured. Currently, Jessian could still move to a certain extent despite his cracked head, but Garen was not surprised at all.

However, this was not important. The incident that truly surprised him was the fact that the gouged out eyeball was consciously struggling and clearly displaying signs of abnormalities.

His thoughts stirred slightly before a shroud of deep blue cold air covered the eyeball in his hand suddenly, before freezing it into an ice bead.

He glanced at his surroundings before fixing his gaze on Xiao Ying who was standing in the middle and stared at him blankly.

"Ying Er…?"

"Move!!" A loud roar could be heard suddenly before all of the surrounding soldiers pulled the triggers on their guns at once.

An exploding noise could be heard from the faraway mortar at once.

Moments later, all of the Ling army soldiers charged forward simultaneously.

Seemingly endless torrents of bullets and cannons were fired at the center of the courtyard frantically, as though the cost of ammunition was a small price to pay for their eradication.

Boom!!

Crashing noises rumbled throughout the center of the courtyard, causing humming noises to echo in everyone's ears while the gunpowder smoke, soil, and rubble flew about everywhere, blinding everyone's vision for a moment.

"Water."

A calm voice could be heard softly within the courtyard.

Suddenly, a gust of cool breeze blew outwards from the center of the courtyard. It was a slightly moist, light breeze that blew around silently like cold winds that brushed past the surface gently.

The Ling Army officer had retreated far away and was now looking on as the remaining Grandmasters of Combat were separated into different batches. One batch rushed over to retrieve Jessian's corpse before retreating, while the other batch had fled off to a distance of more ten meters long ago. Only a few of them were stupid enough to stick around and confront Demoness Lola.

A strange scene appeared at the moment when the breeze blew past.

Whoosh!!

At the same time, the gunshot and explosion noises ceased before all of the soldiers were suddenly covered in deep blue flames. They stood frozen in place but the flames did not burn their bodies. Instead, a crystal clear layer of blue ice began to freeze over, covering them quickly, before forming more than ten blue ice sculptures.

Within the courtyard, almost ten soldiers, including a few Grandmasters of Combat were suddenly set on fire with the blue flames. They resembled blue torches that stood upright next to the walls and on the floor, while the deep blue flames illuminated the surrounding areas and cast them in blue light.

Gulp.

Demoness Lola's little face was now pale. She swallowed while her skin was illuminated in blue light by the flames. She took a look around and felt as if time had stopped for a moment.

Numerous bullets and cannonballs had formed holes of various sizes on the ground below Garen's feet. They were scattered everywhere, yet none had harmed his body.

Bang!!

Suddenly, countless ice sculptures cracked and formed colored crystal shards as they scattered on the ground.

The ice sculptures on the wall fell down and crashed on the ground. The ice sculptures in the courtyard collapsed one by one as well, forming blue ice shards that were tinged with blood.

Unlike regular people, the ten Grandmasters of Combat retained more than half of their bodies after the shards of blue flame ice disappeared. However, none of them showed any signs of life anymore.

Moments later, the only ones who survived within the courtyard were the officer in the yellow military uniform and the group of Southern Sky Gate members which stood in the middle.

Pfoo.

Both of the officer's legs were shaking before he fell on his knees at once. His face was pale and he was unable to speak as his lips could only tremble.

Garen returned his gaze indifferently.

"I'll let you decide what to do with him. Meanwhile, I'll control the military forces in this area."

Nora, Yue Jian, and two other people stood in front of Xiao Ying to shield her, while worried expressions were plastered on their faces.

"May I ask who you might be?" Old Yue Jian stood out and asked quietly.

Garen smiled and outstretched his hand while the blue ice crystals around him melted quickly into flowing blue water that gathered in his palm, before finally turning into a burning deep blue flame.

"Whose disciple are you? Ying Er? Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King? Or Third Senior Brother Joshua?" He asked as he returned his palm. Although he had just done a shocking act, nothing was truly as shocking as the question that had just escaped his mouth.

"You… How do you know Teacher Yoda?" The old fellow stuttered slightly while an emotional look appeared in his eyes as if he had guessed something.

Garen tried to detect it carefully, before smiling strangely suddenly.

"Did you manage to learn some things from Celine and Su Lin?"

"Could it… Could it be that you…?!!" The old fellow took a step forward with an excited look on his face. Other than that person, no one else would know secrets like these!

"My name is Garen." Garen's gaze passed through the crowd and fell on Xiao Ying as he noticed that she was so much like… so much like Ying Er from the past.

It grew silent, but no one dared to stir.

The Southern Sky Gate members could only gulp as everything that they heard was too impossible to believe. They could not comprehend it at all for awhile.

There was no information regarding the existence of the legendary White Cloud Gate Master except in portraits and photos. He had disappeared for sixty years and after he had been hit by the nuclear bomb, everyone assumed that he died. Suddenly, this person had appeared and said that he was Garen. It was normal that no one would accept these as facts so easily.

But other than Garen, no one else would be able to freeze almost ten soldiers within a few moments while more than ten Grandmasters of Combat stood in front of him like helpless babies.

A master of this caliber had no need to trick them.

"After my battle with Cayduran, some strange troublesome incidents occurred. In short, it was a lucky coincidence that I did not die, but unfortunately, I could not return either, until now," said Garen nostalgically as he recalled the previous fight.

He realized that he was looking past the crowd and straight at Xiao Ying suddenly.

"Has Ying Er died?"

Xiao Ying lowered her head and bit her lip but did not answer.

Garen was speechless for a moment. His quest for unlimited power caused him to unknowingly involve the existence and emotions of the people around him. Time raced by and he lost everything that he once possessed. Even if he desired to return, he knew that he had lost his chance.

**************

At East Continent's Southern Sky Gate, First Heavenly General Garen had appeared and killed fourteen first rate Grandmasters of Combat including Jessian, allowing the three provinces that were controlled by the Ling Army to fall into the hands of Southern Sky Gate.

This news traveled far and wide like a hurricane and spread throughout the entire East Continent quickly through the radios. It travelled across the ocean at the same time, and when the masters of Stonecliff Continent, Fivestar Continent, and Azure Continent received this news simultaneously, they could hardly believe it, and chose to send representatives to East Continent to verify the information, while some of the Grandmasters of Combat made the trip there personally.

The governments of the Three Great Countries made plans in secret. Although they were no movements on the surface, they had actually dispatched large groups of spies that traveled towards East Continent with members of Immortal Palace and Behemoth secretly.

The news regarding Young Divine Master's death in battle hit them like an earthquake. Other than Immortal Palace, Weisman Empire, Celestial Circle Gate, and Crimson Sand Sword Gate were also shocked by the news.

The entire Combat World fell into a state of shock, but the first ones to react were Celestial Circle Gate strongest Sword King Andrela.

Meanwhile, after Garen had integrated the army forces of the current three provinces, he gathered the members of White Cloud Gate and Southern Sky Gate. As Immortal Palace's public opinion throughout the years stated that Southern Sky Gate had become a group that gathered Demon Warriors, when Garen came into being, his original title of First Heavenly General was changed into Demon God-General.

After getting to know Xiao Ying, Garen waited in the provincial capital quietly for the arrival of Andrela and King of Nightmares. At the same time, he was also waiting for the invasion of Immortal Palace's Divine Master.

**************

Night breeze blew past the top of a tall dark red tower.

Garen stood on the top of the tower and looked down at the night view of the entire provincial capital from afar.

Throughout the black ground, countless pale yellow lights illuminated the area like glittering stars. Some of them were lit up while others were extinguished, making them resembled a long river of light that flowed continuously.

Garen leaned against the sloped tower top while his black and gold-trimmed cloak bunched up around his body as the wind tousled it.

Xiao Ying knelt beside him and poured him a glass of alcohol in a little white porcelain cup slowly. After they got to know each other that day, Xiao Ying allowed herself to strip off her heavy responsibilities so that she could return to being a lively young girl again.

Garen thought of Ying Er whenever he saw her, allowing him to treat her with the same care. Meanwhile, the little girl warmed up to him as well, partially due to his youthful appearance that made it difficult for her to treat him as an elder.

Therefore, a strange relationship formed between them, as if they were both individuals with the same ranking.

"Gate Master, what are you thinking of? Is it something to do with Grandmother?" Xiao Ying put the wine pot down and glanced at Garen's side profile. The silver glow from the moonlight reflected across his face, making him look like the Moon God.

"I think of her a lot when I look at you." Garen raised the wine cup and sipped from it slowly while a strange feeling filled his heart. "Both of you are really too similar…"

"Are we?" Ying Er smiled. "Xiao Ying had heard Grandmother mention Big Bro Gate Master before as well."

She combed through her hair after it had been blown messily by the wind, and paused.

"‘It felt like a dream. I blinked and realized that my own big brother had transformed into an unimaginably strong person.' Those were Grandmother's exact words."

"To be honest, perhaps I was selfish in the end. I was only concerned about making myself stronger, but I forgot that I would be causing changes throughout the lives of the people around me and that these changes were not necessarily good ones," said Garen softly while he turned the wine cup in his hand and glanced at Xiao Ying guiltily. If Ying Er had remained as a normal person from the beginning to the end, perhaps her life would be happier. The burdens that Xiao Ying was forced to bear, would perhaps lessen as well.

"Grandmother Ying Er never blamed you," Xiao Ying replied with a smile. "I never blamed you either. Everyone has their own decision-making rights, and even normal people are allowed to grasp their own lives. I want to thank you for the changes that you caused in the beginning because they gave me the right to make my own choices."

"You're still so young…" Garen's gaze softened.

"We have a phrase here in the East Continent that goes: ‘Intelligence comes first, regardless of age'," said Xiao Ying frankly.

She hesitated for a few moments.

"Xiao Ying has a strange question to ask, but I don't know if… I already know that this question is impolite."

"Ask away. However, I can't promise that I'll answer it," Garen winked with a smile.

Xiao Ying waited for a moment before raising her head and meeting Garen's eyes.

"Gate Master, can you… live forever without aging?"

Chapter 562: Fame 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Immortality?" Garen snickered, unable to hold back his laughter, "If you just look at my body, it's almost an example of immortality, but…." He suddenly remembered the Cthulhu King from Totem World, and his smile faded away.

"In this world, there is no true immortality. Even if the body does not die, the soul will eventually decay. You have to understand this."

He also thought of his first encounter with Demon Phoenix. That powerful woman who claimed to be immortal, in the end, was sealed until her brain went strange. Maybe it was due to her soul.

"What is truly eternal in this world? Considering all things in the world, even rocks will turn to dust, melted due to high temperature or eroded by acids. Gold can exist for thousands of years but is hardly able to withstand high temperature. Life and death cycle endlessly and reproduces nonstop. Seemingly long, but in the face of the entire universe, it might be that life and death only have a slightly longer expiration date."

"What about thoughts? When knowledge leaves its mark, it might get handed down longer than thousands of years?" Xiao Ying asked after thinking seriously.

"It's still within the cycle of reproduction of humans." Garen patted Xiao Ying's hair and gently pinched her cheeks while gazing at her lowered head and blushing face. "Don't ponder it so much, you're still in the period of enjoying your youth."

"Yes…" Xiao Ying had never enjoyed such a warm and relaxing sense of security. Ever since she was young, Ying Er had always been strict with her, and there had never been any gentle touches like just now. After the sudden changes in her life, although her adoptive parents treated her in a good way, she still had to live in fear every day. With the pressure from Southern Sky Gate, there was never a moment of rest.

In her enjoyment, she moved closer towards Garen. Her complexion was turning redder by the minute. Sneaking a glimpse at Garen, he was looking down beneath the spire. He seemed to have found something interesting as his eyes revealed his amusement.

Suddenly, a blurred white figure flashed by, landing a short distance from Garen's side. That figure had a long sword at the waist, a handsome appearance, a gray beard covering at his chin and a pair of eyes dazzling like the brightest stars under the moonlight.

Xiao Ying had never seen anyone with eyes that could seemingly emit light with glimmers of silver.

That man's short white hair was fluttering about in the wind, yet his eyes were only on the leaning Garen.

"It's been sixteen years, you have also grown old," Garen said.

That man's complexion turned weird.

"I think you have the least qualification to say that."

Garen touched his chin. It was smooth, indeed.

He smacked his lips. His body had Fire and Ice Spirit Evil Arts. Without any interference, his body aged slower than normal people.

"Where's Nightmare?"

Andrela's complexion turned dark. "Have you heard of Genetic Meltdown?"

Garen stiffened.

"After you disappeared for three years, she bled all over her body. I tried everything I could to save her." Andrela said calmly, "Maybe it's Heaven's punishment for recklessly modifying her body."

Garen also felt that King of Nightmares' body was strange. Such frequent changes to the body constitution would cause destabilization. Now that it happened, sure enough…

Andrela was calm as though he'd been talking about people unrelated to him.

"After her death, I immediately took over her forces and acted as though there is still King of Nightmares. This way, the Star Ring Door and Siren Group would be able to be preserved even more. Unfortunately, the Divine Master saw through that ruse. We fought three times. I was heavily injured and he only suffered small injuries. This time, he even went through a breakthrough."

"So intense?" Garen's eyebrows twitched.

"Compared to the old you, it was only one step away, but since you came back, I feel relieved now." Andrela finally showed a gentle smile.

"Rather than Divine Master, I have a much more important matter to discuss with you."

"Oh?"

Xiao Ying at the side stared with her eyes wide open. She could not guess the relationship between these two. They could be said to be good friends but when one member died, Garen showed no sadness, only slight dejection.

Garen pinched Xiao Ying's cheeks and smiled.

Since he met one of his old friends, some things should speed up. Especially after he saw Ying Er's grave, he'd become even more desperate.

"Since you are here, come out then. Playing hide-and-seek was not the style of Cayduran." He looked around, then stood up at the top of the spire, which was tens of meters tall.

He suddenly felt dispirited. With the power he had now, if he had to face against this world's top forces again, it would be like an adult beating up a kindergartener. The gap might perhaps be even larger.

Was it his fate to return here in order to beat up crying children?

With the sound of swishing wind, two more figures appeared at the spires opposite of him.

Under the night sky, there were two men wearing silver clothes outside the tower suspended in the air as though stepping on solid ground.

The two of them stood side-by-side. The man at the left had a weird appearance. The left half of his face appeared manly while his right half appeared feminine. He had a strong body yet he wore earrings and necklace that only females would wear. He also had his nails polished pink. When the wind blew over, there was a strong scent of perfume.

On the other hand, the man at the right side was unrecognizable. His face was marred by numerous burn scars. He only had one of his eyes open while the other seemed to be of no use.

With only a glimpse of this guy, Garen recognized him right away.

"Flamingo?" he exclaimed.

"It's me." The disfigured guy nodded slightly, "I didn't think it was really you, Garen." For masters standing at the top, the dispositions they were familiar with over the years, they could still recognize them easily. asdangixaw

His hand still hold that Sword of the Sprites. Under the moonlight, the crimson sword seemed to have a faint luster of silver.

"I can't believe you're still alive." Garen was angry; the scene of the graves of those sprites was still fresh in his memories.

He scanned the darkness below the tower. Those densely packed hidden figures were like torches in the dark, much too obvious to his senses.

"I'll give you guys a chance, all come at me."

"Arrogant!" The guy who was neither male nor female snapped.

"The so-called Divine Master is only this much?" Garen took a brief look at him. From the level of his strength, he was the strongest among them. To be stronger than Flamingo, then he could only be the Divine Master.

"Never imagine that after Sylphalan died, the successor is this kind of trash."

He clenched his right hand and blue mist wafted through his surroundings.

An ice blue crystal halberd slowly crystallized in his hand.

The halberd was the length of a person and covered in a myriad of fine and exquisite silver runes. A blue-black snake curled around the top, its slender body covered in countless hard scales just like a dragon crawling around.

Divine Master and Flamingo did not reply but the look on their face turned solemn. The pressure released by Garen was like the sea, centering on the eye of the storm and spreading the freezing energy outwards.

"Ancient Secret Martial Skills…" Divine Master whispered, his eyes dyed in the color of frenzy, "King of the Century…it's really the King of the Century!"

The solidification of aura involved real matter and not merely organisms. This realm was the legendary King of the Century. What Garen was doing right now was precisely that.

If they were using telekinesis to float in the air, then the act of Garen materializing weapon without the usage of telekinesis and rely solely on aura could only be aura solidification.

Hong!!

A silver halo emerged out of Divine Master surrounding his body and at the same time a fiery red halo also emerged out of Flamingo's body. The surroundings of the both were dyed in the color of silver and red respectively.

In the distance, the non-Grandmaster of Combat gunmen that were hiding in ambush suddenly grabbed their eyes. ‘Pop, pop' sounds of eyeballs bursting appeared constantly. Among the screams and wails, the top executive of Weisman Empire threw a punch at the wall furiously but did not dare to look at the tower.

For Grandmaster of Combat of the realm of Divine Master, at the moment he released his aura, the sudden changes that came would cause anyone hostile towards him to be attacked.

"Even looking directly…is not possible…" the top executive bit his lower lip, unaware that it was bleeding.

There was no vibration in reality but in the eyes of Grandmaster of Combat that was spectating, it was as though the Heaven and Earth were shaking.

Ji!!

Above the tower, a huge fire peacock and a double-headed silvery white bird appeared. The two monsters flapped their wings and soared towards Garen who was standing at the tower.

Those were illusions created by auras. There was no actual physical damage but it could cause mental damage to living things.

The moment the red peacock and double-headed silvery white bird reached the tower, a line of blue silver lit up in front of them.

The arc-shaped line of fire flashed by. In a mere moment, it had struck countless times against the Flamingo and Divine Master's swords.

There was no resistance. Through the swords, the blue fire on the halberd spread and burned both of them.

Garen stored his halberd. In the Totem World, he had slain countless real monsters, not to mention monsters formed by auras.

He had originally thought that the Divine Master would have some surprise for him. In the end, there were no changes. He did not even bring out a tenth of his strength but the duo crumbled with just a touch.

The fusion power the Living Secret Technique displayed was like a living being. It lit up both of them and burned them like barrels of fuel.

Andrela and Xiao Ying were originally watching alertly at the side but the battle had ended in the blink of an eye. The two were stunned as though they were meeting Garen for the first time. Looking at the two blue flames burning brighter than ever, then looking at the calm look on Garen's face, they were utterly speechless.

Ding.

Suddenly, a silvery white ring fell from Divine Master.

Surprisingly, the ring was not melting under the raging fire. It rolled out of the fire and headed towards the bottom.

Garen waved his hand, sucking the ring onto his palm.

With a snap, the figure of Divine Master and Flamingo froze in the blue fire and shattered into countless blue fragments. The fragments were then blown away by the wind like droplets of rain.

Even the Crimson Sword of the Sprites turned into blue fragments.

The halberd in Garen's hand also shattered at the same time, turning into countless ice fragments and disappeared. He took a look at the ring in his hand. The figure of a double-headed bird was carved on it.

"So, it has always been in the hand of the Divine Master. This thing…" Andrela gave Garen a complicated look.

"What do you want to say?"Garen turned around to face him.

"Still remember the goal that we set?"

"You found a clue?" Garen felt curious.

"A clue that left me helpless, perhaps the way you are now may have a solution." Andrela smiled bitterly.

Chapter 563: Mother Stream 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

April 25th

Lord of Immortal Palace was killed in combat in Dongzhou by Demon God General Garen. Including Weisman Assault Team, Immortal Palace's Grandmaster of Combat elites and Elders, nearly half were annihilated.

Fifteen days later

Southern Sky Gate was renamed back to Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate. Garen summoned back all the disciples, rebuilt the place and restored the techniques to be inherited. White Cloud Gate returned back to White Dew Gate and Garen became White Dew Gate's Great Elder. Together with Celestial Circle Gate, Crimson Sand Sword, and Demon Gate, an alliance was formed. Together, they maintained the Combat Festival.

When the news spread out, the combat world was shaken. Numerous martial artists went to Immortal Palace to verify the authenticity.

Weisman Empire's higher-ups declared Garen as a terrorist, gathered the remaining forces in Immortal Palace and dispatched more than ten thousands of people to subjugate the Dongzhou's Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate.

　　

*********************

The sky was clear.

From the endless blue sea, on the horizon, numerous white navy ships slowly appeared as tiny dots. Among the densely packed dots, a middle-aged man wearing black aristocratic clothes and a captain's hat was looking through his binoculars on the largest navy ship.

Huala!

The sea water crashed ashore against Garen's legs and droplets splashed around. He stood in the sea with the sea water passing by, remaining motionless.

Gazing at the emerging fleets of Weisman navy ships, Garen slowly raised his right hand.

Silently, a white fog materialized and spread through his surroundings. Within seconds, the fog grew thicker and larger and soon covered an area of several hundreds of meters.

Halberds crystallized and appeared from the mist repeatedly, suspended in mid-air with their tips aiming at the distant navy ships.

Boom!

Fiery red dots appeared among the navy ships. The dots flashed, and waves and jets of water splashed around Garen's position.

Peng Peng Peng Peng!!

The incessant bombardment appeared like rain, but strangely, in the area of fog surrounding Garen, every single shell that went in disappeared soundlessly, as though there was a bottomless abyss swallowing up everything.

Red dots lit up again on the navy ships. A second bombardment began.

"Go."

Out of nowhere, a crystalized halberd appeared in Garen's hand and he gently pointed it at the fleet.

Weng…

Countless crystal halberds trembled, as one by one, they were covered in bluish light.

Bang!!

At that instant, all the halberds disappeared. In the distance, numerous fireballs appeared above the sea.

Garen absentmindedly gazed at the sea of fire across the sea then turned around and walked away.

Between the rocks on the shore, the people from White Dew Gate and Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, elders from Celestial Circle Gate and representatives from Crimson Sand Sword all kneeled down. Their faces showed passion, excitement, and amazement.

This kind of combat martial arts realm was not something a human could do. This was the highest realm that all martial artists coveted; using the force of an individual to crushed every single resistance.

Those numerous crystal halberds were like legends and myths coming to life, piercing through the heavens and crushed all the Weisman navy ships instantly.

Garen glanced at the crowd that kneeled down. In his heart, there was no delight in defeating the Weisman navy ships. He did not even see clearly that fleet of ships that came full of enthusiasm and had simply annihilated them dozens of miles away.

To him, it was only materializing tens of halberds through his Secret Techniques and throw those out. After that, he only needed to enjoy the spectacle of fireballs that appeared one by one.

Totally meaningless.

Back on the shore, he tuned out the passionate cheers from the crowd and turned his gaze at Andrela who was standing at the right.

In a complex mood, Andrela looked at this once-best friend of his. That kind of overwhelming strength that could not be concealed had already left the realm of martial artist and reached the point of a legend. At his peak, he knew himself that settling this fleet of navy ships was no big deal but when there were numerous elites from Immortal Palace on board, it became a different matter, not to mention there were even hidden masters from Weisman Empire and customized heavy artillery in the hands of specialized Grandmasters of Combat. Not even he could resolve all of that.

They looked at each other and nodded simultaneously.

After a few simple sentences, the figures of Garen accompanied by Andrela disappeared on the shore.

After this battle, the alliance had an all-new experience on the terrifying combat strength of Garen. Some people who had conflicting views about him had let go altogether. Any and all sorts of undercurrents that emerged died down completely. In the face of absolute strength, everything else paled in comparison. Any schemes would be crushed effortlessly.

　　*****************

A few days later…

Endless seawater with no land in sight splashed around, while seagulls soared up in the sky and sunlight glittered off the surface of the sea.

Garen and Andrela were boarding a small blue boat with a white trail behind it heading towards the same place as the seagulls.

One was sitting at the front and the other at the back with their hair tousled by the wind.

Some time ago, the sea wind had begun sounding like the weeping of a lady.

"There's a small island in front. The islanders all called it the Sea Demon Island, and the island is surrounded by winds that are harsh and piercing on the ears. Normal people have no way of approaching it." Andrela introduced while controlling the boat.

"The island has caves that are like honeycombs on the mountain. When the sea wind blows, it creates a sound like how we whistle. Maybe because a special frequency was created, those piercing sounds can mislead senses. If you lose concentration, you will lose your way."

Garen turned serious. The sensation from Living Secret Technique made him become slightly alert.

Standing up, he stared far ahead across the sea.

A U-shaped green island appeared on the sea in front.

Seagulls flocked around on the island. On the desolate yellowish green beach, not a trace of humans could be seen.

"That's the Sea Demon Island." Andrela also stood up. Both of them looked at the island.

"More than ten years ago, under certain circumstances, I heard rumors about this island. The descriptions of this island's environment and topography resembled a hidden sacred place that I found in a book from a religion."

"Hidden sacred place?"

"That's right." Andrela slightly recounted, "In the record, this Sea Demon Island was once one of the places the Ancient Endor's Mother Stream runs through."

"Mother Stream? You are talking about the origin of streams described in the legend?" Garen recalled.

In the legend, all the Ancient Endor's origin of life and great warlocks such as Mother Earth would return into the embrace of the Mother Stream when their life depleted.

"Yes, that Mother Stream." Andrela nodded. "After years of researching, guess what I found?" There was yearning in his eyes but mostly helplessness.

"No way, did you found that Mother Stream?" Garen was stunned, "On this island? A place surrounded by the sea?!" He felt it a bit unbelievable, this place was in the middle of a sea a few days away from Dongzhou and considered a place where no one cared. Now, someone told him that there was a river on this island and it was the legendary Mother Stream, the origin of life.

"Wait until you take a look at this Mother Stream, then you will understand." Andrela smiled bitterly.

The both of them no longer spoke and waited in silence for the little boat to reach there, nearer and nearer.

The sight of the yellowish green beach was getting clearer.

After about half an hour later, the little boat stopped in a crevice between some rocks on the island. Garen froze a big chunk of ice and stoppered the crevice to stop the boat from getting washed away by the sea.

The two of them stepped down from the boat on the island.

The area of shallow water was of crystal clear blue. It could be seen that in the water, there were blue lights reflected on the ripples.

Shells, marine fish, black reefs, translucent shrimps, and crabs were vibrant all around.

Garen stepped on the soft sand beach and picked up a white conch wrapped in seaweed. To his surprise, a few white tentacles came out of the opening of the conch and started struggling around.

"The organisms here is a little weird, take note," Andrela whispered after tying the rope on the boat.

Standing on the island's beach, in front of them was a lush green forest.

From the direction of the shore into the island, the trees became even more closely compacted with their colors getting darker from light green to dark green. This showed the distribution of the plants on the island

Standing on the beach, the weeping sounds of the wind became even clearer and even sounded demonic.

Garen wrinkled his eyebrows; for him, the sounds had started became piercing.

For the normal people or even average Grandmaster of Combat, this might be the limit for them. Heading in any further would become dangerous for them.

For him and Andrela who had reached the level they stood at now, even the most vulnerable eardrums would have a certain degree of enhancement, not to mention their internal organs which were a lot tougher than the normal people. This little bit of sound was no different from listening to a radio.

Wearing black tight-fitting cloaks, both of them headed deeper into the island.

Andrela led the way as he was the most familiar with this island. He led Garen on a barely discernible forest trail and advanced into the dense jungle.

The forest felt slightly hot and humid. Whether it's the top, bottom, left or right, all around them were plants. Some plants grew crooked to the left and right, barring their way and were snapped by the both of them.

From the gaps that could be seen, there were small insects that flew here and there, among which some of them had a blood-sucking ability and were buzzing around.

A mixture of sour scent with the fresh scent of the plants was in the warm and humid air, making the whole thing quite strange.

Following the trail and winding left and right, the terrain was getting lower as though they were walking into a humongous basin.

In the forest, excluding the chirping of birds and the sounds of unknown animals, there were only the swishing sounds of both of them traveling through the forest.

After some time, a yellow mountain was revealed before them and a small dark cave was nestled among the vines climbing around.

Andrela stopped in front of the cave.

"It's here." He whispered.

"We're going in?"

Chapter 564: Mother Stream 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"No, not exactly in there. If it wasn't by accident, no one would have thought to enter from that passage." Andrela smiled mysteriously and led the way into the cave. Garen hurriedly followed along.

Soon after he had advanced into the cave for some distance, he stopped. He no longer moved after standing beside a spring.

"It's here. I'll lead the way, you follow."

Once he finished speaking, he jumped straight into the spring.

Water soon splashed around the spring with a width longer than a meter.

Garen was confused but he also jumped into the spring.

The moment he entered the spring, something soft and warm covered his whole body as though soaking in a hot spring.

Strangely, the temperature of the spring was not high, only about the temperature of the sea.

Bubbles floated up. Through the cloudy blue water, Garen saw that Andrela was waving a bright green glow stick at him at the bottom.

He hurriedly swam like a fish in order to keep up. After training for so long at the sea, water became a second nature to him. He swam at a moderate pace behind Andrela.

The two of them had already swum in the spring longer than ten minutes yet they were still heading further down. The surroundings of the spring were dark and it was still extending as though there was no bottom.

Finally, the tunnel in front of them made a horizontal turn and no longer went deeper.

After a while, another passage that turned upwards appeared.

The whole spring was a U-shaped passage, just like the shape of the island.

Following the passage upwards, the two of them could not help but swim faster.

Huala!

Inside a small dark cavern, two heads emerged out of an oval spring at a corner.

With a loud splash, two dark figures leaped out of the water and landed firmly by the side of the spring.

Garen snapped his fingers and a freezing white mist circled around both their cloaks and soon dissipated.

All the moisture in their cloaks became ice and with a gentle shake, all the ice fell off on the ground.

The water on both of them had dried instantly.

"This is already out of the scope of Secret Techniques." Andrela sighed.

Garen smiled without replying and only silently scanned the cavern.

"This is the place where the Mother Stream ran through, the only point where Mother Stream can be seen" Andrela sighed, "You definitely cannot imagine what Mother Stream looks like."

"In this cavern?" Garen was piqued by curiosity. What did the legendary Mother Stream look like in reality? He could not guess.

"Follow me."

Andrela walked ahead, away from the spring towards one of the cavern's stone wall.

Garen only noticed when he came near, the stone wall was, in fact, a hole that got blocked. The stone piece that blocked the hole was too similar to the surrounding with no apparent flaws. If no one checked properly, there was no way to know that there was a hole here.

He also noticed that on the ground at the left side of the stone piece laid a pile of white bones. It did not seem to belong to humans. It was more like lizards' bones put together but there was no rotten smell that drifted out.

"I lived here for five years. Previously, creatures similar to lizards lived in the spring but it was all eaten by me." Andrela shrugged and placed all ten of his fingers on the stone piece and pulled outwards.

With the rumbling sound of rolling stone, the stone piece moved out of the way and a hole with the height of a person was immediately revealed.

Andrela did not go in. He only stood by the entrance quietly peering inside, his eyes showing a trace of obsession.

A green light from inside the hole was also reflected on it.

Garen could not help but hold his breath, similarly stunned by the amazing scene inside the hole.

A large cavern was connected to this hole on the other side.

Inside was a stream running from left to right with no sound whatsoever. No matter it was the sound of water, the flow of air or creatures swimming inside it, there was none.

It was a stream dozens of meters wide.

It was no normal stream water but some sort of glowing green fluid. It gushed out from a gray vortex on the left and rushed into a gray vortex on the right.

The light from the stream glowed, dyeing both of them green.

The hole they were at was located high up in the large cavern, just like one of the many holes of a beehive.

"This is the Mother Stream…" Andrela muttered.

"How are you so sure?" Garen finally snapped out of it. He could see such a spectacle in the Secret Technique World, but even if he had been through all sorts of thing, he still felt that it was incredible.

"It's that I'm sure…once you get closer you will understand." Andrela smiled bitterly.

Slightly puzzled, Garen went inside the cavern.

Only a step, a gentle and warm aura covered him and expelled gently.

"This is …aura!!??" He looked at Andrela, startled.

"That's right." Andrela nodded. "Aura is a product of Spirit. In the Ancient Ender civilization, it was also called Power of Life. In the legend, Mother Stream flows out from an unknown void into another unknown void. It contains infinite Power of Life. This is why even if this stream is not the Mother Stream, it is at least a branch of it. There is no other explanation which I could find from the records."

Garen suddenly thought of something and adjusted his vision.

Closing his eyes and opening it once again, the glowing green stream in front of him disappear. There was nothing in this large cavern except a vague flow of gentle air. He totally hid all the aura in his body, using the eyes of ordinary people to observe.

Sure enough, the whole Mother Stream was unable to be seen. The location where the Mother Stream situated was originally a dried up river with nothing inside it and both sides were blocked.

"I see, the Mother Stream in the legend can only be seen by the chosen ones. No wonder it was explained like that." Garen nodded. Releasing his aura, the green light filled his vision again.

"You also discovered it." Andrela nodded. "I have examined it from various perspectives and basically confirmed that this is the Mother Stream."

Garen did not reply and went silent.

"What are you planning to do?"

Andrela smiled bitterly.

"I don't have any plans. I can't even get near it, what else can I plan?"

"You lived here for five years, there should at least be some results."

"This is natural." Andrela nodded, "I looked up all the information on Mother Stream. Whether it be myth legends or folk tales, none was spared. Pieced together, I had a thought."

He leaned against the wall and explained while gazing at the Mother Stream.

"Mother Stream, also known as Stream of Life was said to contain a secret. Rumors had it that ancient warlocks nearing their death walked into the embrace of Mother Stream. There must be some meaning to it."

He took out a silver ring carved with a double-headed bird.

"I found out that all the warlocks who entered the Mother Stream would wear an accessory made of silver stone. I don't know the reason."

"This is a ring made of the silver stone?" Garen also took out the double-headed ring he got from Divine Master.

"Yes. I don't know who got their hands on this material and made double-headed rings out of it. These might be the last two accessories made from silver stone in this world." Andrela regretfully said.

"I guess that when the warlocks lost all hope, they gambled everything they have to have the one last chance."

"What chance?"

"The chance to reach a higher level."

Andrela said in low voice.

"The legend of warlocks ended with a legendary expedition. For unknown reasons, they went to war with powerful invaders from another world. Finally, both sides suffered great losses. Various gods fell. I found out that whenever great warlocks suffered grievous injuries, someone would put them into the Mother Stream to have their injuries healed. Then, they would enter into battles again."

He paused for a while.

"Later, the enemies found out about it. They used some sort of means to stop the healing abilities of the Mother Stream. Maybe this is the original way the Mother Stream should be. It was a Pyrrhic victory. Not long after, both sides disappear from history."

"Your speculations are very detailed but this is all built on the fact that all the myth and legends are true." Garen nodded.

"I tried to eliminate any interference to the best extent, sorting out all the data and compiling them. This final result should not have too many distortions." Andrela shook his head.

"Mother Stream…" Garen looked at the running stream emitting green light, feeling out of this world. This feeling of standing before and looking at something that should only exist in legends, normal people would not be able to imagine it.

Imagine looking at the Egyptian pyramids from Earth. That kind of heavy feeling from looking at history enshrouds your mind and leave nothing else in your head.

"There must be a great secret hidden inside there. The warlocks have lifespans approaching thousand years and godlike powers. What is there on the level above them? There can only be immortality!" Andrela said seriously, then a bitter smile surfaced. "But I can't even get close to it."

He turned to look at Garen.

"What I can't do, maybe you can. Your strength already reached a level out of my imagination." His eyes contain hope and anticipation.

Garen looked at Mother Stream, uncertainty in his eyes.

Suddenly, he took a large step.

Pa!

His boots stepped firmly on the ground inside the cavern. A huge force slammed on his body intending to expel him.

This force was vast as the sea. Even the strength of Garen's Living Secret Technique barely held on.

His body was covered in freezing white mist and was about to retaliate.

Suddenly, his view passed through the Attribute Pane and his body stopped.

In the Attribute Pane, he saw an unexpected change.

Chapter 565: Mother Stream 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

All the attributes on the Attribute Pane began to turn blurry, as if covered by a translucent plastic.

This was something he had never encountered before!

This Attribute Pane was actually a mutation, resulting from a stimulation originating from himself. That was to say, the source of Attribute Pane was actually his own body. When this kind of thing happened, it was most likely due to a new and unprecedented stimulation to his body, to the extent of affecting the root of his special ability.

"What’s the matter?" Andrela’s voice came from his rear.

Garen immediately snapped out back to reality and took a step back.

Hu…

As if caressed by a gentle breeze, the blurry Attribute Pane became clear again.

Garen narrowed his eyes. He remained silent, but a trace of seriousness flashed past.

"The ring’s changed!" Andrela’s voice resounded again.

Garen turned his head, and saw that he was holding the silver stone ring with a feverish excitement on his face.

A string of inexplicable words appeared on the ring.

"Words from Ancient Ender, I recognized it." Garen had the attribute abilities. His powerful intelligence attribute allowed him to easily learn any language in the world. He learned the language of Ancient Ender from pieces of passages that he found. Together with his comprehensive analysis, he quickly found the key to mastering it.

At this moment, Garen also noticed that the ring he took from Divine Master had the same changes, but different words of the Ancient Ender language.

"The words from both the rings are different, come and take a look. "Andrela handed his ring to Garen.

The rings combined together to form a complete sentence.

"From where all begins, to where all ends..." Garen muttered a line from the two rings.

"I see." Andrela turned serious, "The Mother Stream was also a symbol of rebirth! The beginning of life yet, also its end."

"There’s still more…he who holds the silver stone, through the Mother Stream’s baptism, shall welcome a new life." Garen said the line from the other ring.

Looking up, both of them saw surprise and excitement in each other’s eyes.

This was an authentic relic left behind by ancient warlocks! To a certain extent, the Mother Stream and the changes on the rings proved that the legends of ancient warlocks were not merely fiction, and were probably true.

"I once saw on a document that Ancient Ender civilization had a ritual that allowed dying people to have a chance at life, taking with them a token from the underworld and passing through various tests, they may resurrect." Andrela said, "Now it seems that Ancient Ender civilization and warlocks are connected to each other."

Garen nodded.

"In other words, these two rings represent two chances of resurrection?"

"It’s not so simple. Otherwise, those dying warlocks would not have provoked Mother Stream. You have to know that Mother Stream had the ability to break down anything, stopping people from entering the cycle of reincarnation." Andrela shook his head.

Garen could feel that these two rings were now emitting a strange radiation. This radiation combined with the power from Mother Stream actually reminded Garen of the Black Smoke Pot.

He suspected that the Black Smoke Pot was actually a large transfer device, created by warlocks using the power of Mother Stream.

There was only one thing different about them.

Standing near the Mother Stream, Garen sensed that although the power from the combination was similar to Black Smoke Pot, but the sense of direction they gave off was not stable enough. From his experience with the Black Smoke Pot’s transfer, he could feel that the Mother Stream had the transfer ability and the rings acted as the compass.

However, the coordination from the rings seemed incomplete.

Both the rings pointed to different directions, and the coordinates on the ring were still changing.

Garen pondered for a moment while waiting for Andrela to calm down before speaking out his thoughts.

"My guess is that the Mother Stream is the source of power for the transfer, while the rings act as a conduit. Perhaps the legend is true, and we can have a chance at resurrection."

"You’re sure?" Andrela’s tone hinted at a different train of thought.

"That time when the volcano erupted, I was transferred far away by the Black Smoke Pot, and managed to return. The feeling from that time is similar to what I feel now." Garen explained, half-truthfully.

"But, I advise you to not jump into it recklessly. I barely survived that time."

Not just barely. When he transferred to Totem World, he had three layers of protection. The first layer was the Eternal Starry Night Pendant given by Old Man Gregor, carved with protection charms combined with his life force. It broke during his transmigration.

The second layer, his King of the Century’s mighty body, strength, aura and Divine Statue Technique known for its defense and healing ability, the first Grandmaster of Combat in history to train a technique only possible in theory to the peak. It similarly crumbled during the transfer.

The third and the most mysterious layer, the reason he reincarnated, was also most probably due to this. The mysterious red attribute, or more precisely the innate ability that resided in his soul that was unknowingly activated, protecting him from receiving serious damage to his soul.

His journey back here was different. Escorted by the Door to Heaven, backed by the whole Totem World, together with strength of his body that exceeded his previous one, getting back here only resulted in some small injuries.

The Black Smoke Pot at that time was most probably a safe passage created and arranged by the warlocks, but even that ‘safe’ passage was perilous to Garen and the others.

Now, entering the Mother Stream was an act dangerous to even those warlocks. A danger feared by the warlocks, for Garen it was even more so, not to mention Andrela, who was far weaker than Garen.

Garen speculated that the Black Smoke Pot was also one of the things that warlocks found using the Mother Stream. Something far stabler than the Mother Stream itself. Even that degree of stability caused Garen’s body to break down completely. If it weren’t for his unique soul, perhaps nothing would be left behind.

If he used the Mother Stream…

"I’m going in to try." Andrela suddenly spoke.

For a moment, the cavern went totally silent. Garen wondered if he had misheard something. He turned to look at Andrela again, trying to see if his face showed any hint that he misspoke. Unfortunately, he found nothing.

"Are you insane!?"

Andrela had never shown a more passionate gaze. "I’m more than calm."

"Did you know how dangerous it is?!" Garen’s voice sounded very serious. "That time when I was transferred by Black Smoke Pot, just a little bit more and there would be nothing left of me."

"I already have no chance of breaking through to the King of the Century realm…" Andrela’s tone was very calm, "Rather than aging and withering away without any hope, I prefer to take this gamble. Even if I have a very low chance of making it out alive, I still won’t give up!"

Garen experienced it himself, and he knew just how dangerous it was. If it weren’t for his peculiar soul, he would not have made it during the transfer of Black Smoke Pot, much less so for this kind of unfamiliar exploration.

"Maybe there’s another way."

"Do you believe it?" Andrela laughed, "In the blink of an eye, since the first time we met each other, so many years have gone by. You know my personality. Pursuing my own goal, I would move forward ceaselessly. Now that I see a glimmer of hope, I would not let slip out of my hand."

Garen frowned and did not pursue the matter anymore. When he first came here from Earth, it was all because of the mutation of his soul. The second time, he successfully went to Totem World, it was also because of his peculiar soul.

If he were replaced with Andrela…

Concerning the exploration of Mother Stream, Garen himself was also curious yet excited. Perhaps, after he did everything he wanted in this world and there was nothing left, he would choose to continue this path.

Although his Living Secret Technique had reached a terrifying level, because this world had no totem power, there was no way for him to change lifespans. At most, he would live for a hundred years or two, maybe longer, due to the attribute of his Secret Techniques, but in the end he could not escape death.

In fact, he was already at the age of between eighty to ninety years. Just like what Andrela said, rather than aging and withering away without any hope, he preferred to take a gamble. Maybe that way, he could grab hold of that hope.

"What are you going to do?" Garen stopped trying to push him.

"Get myself ready for anything. Then go in and grasp that glimmer of hope." Andrela’s eyes almost lit up from the passion in them.

This time, even Garen was unsure if he himself could take on the Mother Stream’s flow. The fluctuations that appeared on his Attribute Pane were still fresh in his mind. This meant that even the special talent in his soul might get affected greatly.

Although he had some confidence after transferring for three times, unless he was left with no choice, he would not enter the Mother Stream.

"Let’s go back first. I’ll have to prepare properly. The harvest this time is a lot greater than expected…" Andrela showed a fervor greater than before.

********************

A few years after the battle at East Continent.

Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was rebuilt and together with White Dew Gate, White Cloud Gate, Celestial Circle Gate, and Crimson Sand Sword. They formed the Five Gate Alliance, ruling over the entire combat world of the East Continent. The power of the alliance spread like cobwebs, covering the entirety of the continent. Even military forces were ruled under the Alliance of the Five Clans.

The East Continent welcomed a brief period of peace.

At the same time, the leader of the alliance, Heavenly General Garen, led the top Grandmasters of Combat in the alliance to go around on friendly diplomatic visitations to various governments, and built friendly diplomatic ties.

Towards that Grandmaster of Combat with a terrifying strength that could annihilate the entire fleet of Weisman navy ships, the various governments displayed the friendliest welcome they could offer. Various resources and ambassadors flowed endlessly into the East Continent, bringing new blood and vigor to the entire East Continent.

The Combat Festival jointly organized by the Five Gate Alliance also became the top choice for the alliance and various countries to pick out elites.

Chapter 566: Mother Stream 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The years continued to pass, and the alliance was now handled by the Garen’s descendant, Xiao Ying. After taking out the Secret Techniques polished by Garen, this young genius Grandmaster of Combat successfully received the support of all the alliance members. Using the carrot and stick approach, members of the alliance grew in numbers and the prospect of development became better.

With the suggestion and support from part of the members, a large organization known as the Combat Association was built. It covered eighty to ninety percent of the world, and possessed the power to assess Grandmaster of Combat candidates, and the certificate that they handed out received worldwide recognition. Even the series of a martial artists’ rank certificates became the qualifications of what employers seek in employing talent.

Xiao Ying became the first President of the Association. Her personal combat skills, under Garen’s tutelage, further improved, and was now only slightly inferior to Andrela. In addition to her charisma, she also had a group of loyal martial artists by her back, cementing her foothold in the combat world.

Garen and Andrela slowly faded away from the view of the world. At the beginning, there were still some Grandmasters of Combat from the previous generation who remembered their legends. Later, talented new generations emerged and powerful martial artists became famous, the both of them then gradually hid themselves behind the scenes.

In the past, when people mentioned a Grandmaster of Combat, the first thing that came to mind would be Garen and Andrela, and only then would Xiao Ying’s name came up. Now, Xiao Ying’s name would emerge first, only then would both their names be mentioned by some old generations.

These years, both Garen and Andrela were hiding their identities, and relied on Xiao Ying’s huge backings to collect things like antiques and treasures from all over the world.

This way, the Potential points that Garen gathered, numbered in the hundreds. This was already the limit, and Andrela on the other hand secretly gathered a few articles that emitted strong telekinetic waves in preparation of entering the Mother Stream.

The both of them stepped onto all kinds of ancient ruins and mysterious lands. Especially after Xiao Ying’s position stabilized, they let go completely and went around searching for various information and treasures.

Over time, Andrela’s condition started to decline. He finally made up his mind, it was time to enter the Mother Stream.

During these years, Garen basically had no more lingerings left.

After all, Xiao Ying was no baby. With the gradual rise in her position and power, she became increasingly infatuated with the power she held. Different from the pure and lovely Ying Er, Garen no longer saw any trace of Ying Er in her.

This world no longer hold anything worthy of his affection. Of the old friends that he knew, only Andrela remained.

Now, he also chose to enter Mother Stream, betting on this one last chance.

Garen decided that he would accompany him. If there was one person in this world that had the highest probability of surviving the Mother Stream, that person could only be him. No one knew better than him, that terrifying danger and crisis of travelling through space and time was something that was unimaginable by normal people.

******************

After nearly ten years had past, inside the underground cave, standing beside the hole looking over the Mother Stream.

Garen and Andrela had done all the preparations they could.

"You don’t need to take the risk with me." Andrela turn to look at Garen.

"I don’t have any regrets left. Besides, with my previous experience, we might be able to increase our chances for survival." Garen smiled and replied. "Furthermore, haven’t we made it clear; the two rings are pointing at different directions? When we go in, we will go our separate ways. Then, we’ll only have ourselves to depend on."

At this point in life, these two only had one last thing left to pursue.

Dreams.

Garen did not know what Andrela’s dream was, but somehow he was reminded of Cayduran, and Totem World’s Hellgate. Dreams were their only motivation and goal.

Now, he felt that he was quite similar to them.

There was no affection for the world, the only hope they had was moving forward, and maybe one day they might be able to achieve their dreams.

Food and wine, women and power, everything was now at their fingertips. ‘The grass was always greener on the other side’, perhaps this phrase was the most apt for them now.

In his heart, Garen mocked himself.

He looked at Andrela in front of him.

There were more than ten pairs of bracelets on his arms, all of them were various relics from mysterious ruins with unknown functions. He drew his face with tattoos from Ancient Ender civilization, wore a shirt made of 5-coloured feathers, and his trousers in silver and in his hand was a skull cane.

What made him even more speechless was that on all of his fingers and toes were full of different kinds of rings, his nose had two rings and he punched a hole on his chin and hung a chain of either bird or pheasant bones…

"This is what I found in all the records, the strongest form from Ancient Ender. Are you sure you don’t want to make the same preparations?" Andrela looked at Garen.

He shook his head.

Garen looked at his getup, speechless.

"Alright then, if you got into trouble, don’t blame me for not warning you." Andrela shrugged, looking at the hole that still had the same repulsive force and settled down his mind. "Are you ready?"

"Yeah."

Garen simply wore a white suit, in his right hand was the double-headed bird ring, his golden hair smoothly flowing down. There were no more preparations to be done.

In fact, what he relied on was the hundreds of Potential point he had absorbed.

This thing was the source that could heal his injuries.

The cavern rippled with bright green light dancing across its surfaces.

Andrela was the first to go in.

Suddenly, he trembled, obviously meeting with that huge force of resistance.

This time was different from last time. He was prepared and took out a black key, only to toss it forward.

Dang.

When the metal key hit the stone wall, that sound rang out.

The sound continued ringing, and strangely, that huge repulsion force soon weakened.

"Quick!"

Andrela rushed to the key, picked it up and toss it once more forward.

Garen followed him and heard the sound again. The repulsion force weakened again.

This key was something they dug out from a ruin in Azure Continent. According to Garen, this key contained a strange power, and when they tested it, surprisingly it could weakened the repulsion force emitted by Mother Stream.

Using the key, the both of them jumped through the hole and landed on the edge of the Mother Stream.

The key keep ringing. Again and again, the repulsion force from the Mother Stream was diverted, forming a cavity around them. However, the force inside the key was also fading rapidly. The closer they were to the Mother Stream, the ringing became shorter.

"Quick! The key can’t hold on any longer!" Andrela rushed.

Garen also knew how the situation was deteriorating, nodded towards Andrela. The key was then thrown violently, one last time, at the ground in front of them.

Dang!!!

In this last ringing, the key was riddled with cracks all over its body.

Garen calmly jumped towards the Mother Stream. On his right side, Andrela did the same.

Splash!

Both jumped into the green torrent at nearly the same time. Before they could even see the bubbles, they were instantly overwhelmed by the green stream and disappeared.

In the instant Garen jumped into the Mother Stream, Garen was unusually calm. His soul did not felt any danger, but his body was weakening rapidly.

He looked around with his eyes wide open. His sight was filled with endless green, as though he had submerged in the green stream. Obviously, he had only jumped into the stream, but he could not see the surface above. It was as though he was at the bottom of the sea.

As though he was in a green space instead of a stream.

Andrela was to his right, not far away. His whole body was stiff, but his eyes showed his pain and struggle.

The various decorations on his body were disappearing fast. The same thing was happening to his body, just like corrosion caused by acid, dissolving and becoming a part of Mother Stream.

Andrela seemed to have seen Garen. He looked at him, his eyes showing no regrets other than his unwillingness.

Garen helplessly looked at his old friend dissolve in the Mother Stream. A pale blue soul appeared, then melted into the stream without a trace.

Facing the mysterious mighty Mother Stream, a Star Ring king among swordsmen like Andrela, who stood at the peak of Grandmaster of Combat, only endured a little longer than the common small fry.

Garen felt no sadness. Witnessing death over and over again, the him now was no longer the person who had just experienced reincarnation.

His body now was still considered intact, only that the Potential points he amassed were descending like a rocket. Soon, it would be his body.

The Living Secret Technique was holding back the decomposition effect from Mother Stream. Perhaps the Living Secret Technique and the Mother Stream had some similarities, and the decomposition power on him was not as severe. However, with this kind of consumption, in at most ten minutes, his body would disintegrate like Andrela.

Time was ticking.

Garen felt as though the ring was connected to a string, taking his body along the flow of the Mother Stream towards an unknown destination.

The Potential points were exhausted to nothing. The rest would depend on the Living Secret Technique.

The secret technique was strong, but in the face of the decomposition of Mother Stream, it was nothing.

Garen’s fingers and toes were the first to disintegrate. An extreme pain soon travelled through his nerves to signal his brain. He was indifferent to it, but without the protection from secret technique, the most vulnerable part of his body, the eyes and eardrums soon disintegrated.

His sight was plunged into total darkness, and his hearing was no longer able to function. Even the nerves on his skin could only feel endless pain.

Chapter 567: Newborn 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

His nose couldn't smell anything, he wanted to shut his mouth, but he noticed that his lips were gone, even his tongue was rapidly disintegrating.

Not long later, Garen had lost all sense of feeling, his sight, hearing, touch, smell, taste, and even his sense of pain, it was all gone.

He had originally planned to give Andrela a hand, but he would’ve never expected to be caught in such a predicament. The power of the Mother Stream was too overwhelming, making it hard for even him to last for more than a few moments.

He felt as if he were floating in an endless abyss, there was nothing around him, he could not feel anything. It felt like the space the totem of the Nine-Headed Hydra existed in at the beginning, an empty abyss.

Garen knew this was his soul’s visualization of his senses, he guessed, his physical body might have already been completely disintegrated, leaving only his soul intact.

Even the strength of his Living Secret Technique had been dissipated by the overwhelming force of the Mother Stream. However, that seed, the seed that contained the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique and his soul, used the protection from the soul and was floating right in front of Garen, perfectly unscathed.

Inside this dark abyss, the seed was the only source of light, silently floating in the center, emitting a soft blue glow.

As time waned on, Garen could only observe this soul seed to occupy himself.

It might’ve been a month, two months. A year, or even two.

He could no longer keep count. He counted the seconds up to the billions, and as he lost count, he started all over again. This process he repeated numerous times.

However, in all this time, he at least managed to confirm one key point.

His soul managed to resist the decomposition capabilities of the Mother Stream, or rather, the immense amount of force exerted while traveling through space and time.

Even after his body was disintegrated ages ago, there was no sign of any damage or harm to his soul. Even though the physical strength of the Living Secret Technique has completely been dissipated, the seed was still here.

The increased soul limit due to Cthulhu’s Origin earlier was still present, and all his abilities related to his soul still remain.

Not only did the soul seed contain the Living Secret Technique seed, after being absorbed by Garen, it eventually assimilated Garen’s style of martial arts, evolving into his personal point of origin.

The physical strength was only half of the capabilities of the Living Secret Technique seed, but the seed’s inert power is the foundation of the Living Secret Technique.

Under the Mother Stream’s decomposition, his physical body had been completely disintegrated, but Garen used the Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique to condense most of his strength, deep within his soul and put up multiple layers of barriers on the exterior.

He didn’t know much about sealing, but only creating barriers of simple defenses by repeatedly wrapping the seed in his strength. Although his soul had already offered a temporary form of protection, he thought it was better to be safe than sorry.

He noticed that, as time went on, the Life Technique seed was slowly changing as well, slowly becoming more and more condensed, small, and bright. As compared to physical strength, the strength of the soul seed was not tangible, it could only affect matter through a physical body, hence the parts of it that could affect matter had slowly been disintegrated by the Mother Stream.

What remained was this abstract, intangible power.

Garen calls this the Soul Strength. From his observations and analyses, he discovered that although Soul Strength could not directly affect matter, it could change one’s physical body through things like neurons, and then, use one’s physical body to affect matter. In addition, the soul seed seems to have another form of functionality, but Garen had not yet figured out the secret behind it.

As for the exploration of the soul, even if he obtained a few items from the Cthulhu King, he was still as insignificant as a weak ant.

In reality, all living things had souls, in other words, without them, we would just be a conjugation of multiple organisms.

Soul Strength was the embodiment of our consciousness, memory, and spirit, our unique form of existence.

But as time passed on, Garen was starting to feel that his soul was beginning to weaken.

Without the support of a physical body, the soul, in its rootless state, no matter how strong, will slowly start to weaken.

"How much time has passed?"

His consciousness was floating in this abyss, surrounded by nothing, only darkness.

In the center of this abyss laid the soul seed, emitting a mesmerizing blue halo, like a beautiful crystal or gem.

All of a sudden, he felt some sort of vibration.

Sound!

In the outside world that he had no knowledge of, under the dark blue water of the Mother Stream, the stone and silver Vector Ring had due to its impure material, after being submerged in the Mother Stream for such a long time, finally cracked. It’s originally clear, streamline path suddenly slanted towards an unknown direction.

The glowing red light emitted by Garen’s soul could also be seen to be flowing towards the new unknown direction.

******

Garen started hearing some sounds, as if people were speaking.

The voices seem to be muffled and unclear, it also seems to be in an unfamiliar language to him, somewhat like German, but with a slightly faster pace.

That’s when it hit him, his senses had returned to him.

His hearing has recovered, so had his sense of touch, but his sight and smell remained unchanged.

He felt like he was curled up in a tight space, surrounded by warmth, as if he was being submerged in water. He could also feel a youthful heartbeat nearby.

As time slowly passed by, his senses started to become clearer. An interesting phenomenon has also occurred - it seems as if he had shrunk a bit in size.

Or rather, not shrunk, but more like he had gone into a sort of embryonic state.

While his eyes were still sealed shut, he felt oxygen and other essential nutrients being pumped in through his belly button. The abnormal act of breathing through one’s stomach seemed to have amused Garen a bit.

Through the information he gathered with his limited senses, he estimated that he reincarnated due to his special soul talents. He most likely has been turned into a baby, a baby that was still inside his pregnant mother.

From outside the stomach, he could vaguely make out a male and a female voice, both which were very gentle, and also a small boy’s voice. Sometimes he would hear yelling, although he didn’t understand the language, he could discern the excitement present in the voices.

Garen’s curled up body silently started to form a vital energy and blood regulatory system while within his mother’s stomach. The baby’s vital energy and blood roadmap started to develop in accordance with the Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique. Under the manipulation of his soul, a series of complex and precise actions start to take place.

Since his old body that was thoroughly trained in the Secret Techniques was disintegrated, and this current body has barely started to develop, naturally, he’d want to strengthen this body as early as possible.

A baby’s body is extremely fragile, but fortunately, he had the Living Secret Technique’s immense regenerative properties, which further sped up the maturating of this body.

However, Garen was still puzzled about one thing; the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, such an overwhelmingly powerful Living Secret Skill, just where exactly did this power originate from?

Normally, secret techniques use the nutrients from food to develop vital energy, then through enhancing one’s vital energy and blood, improve oneself. However, the Living Secret Technique is different, it seemed like it could create a whole new, complex and precise regulatory system within a living organism’s body, almost as if it was a structure formed from countless seals, images, and solids.

These structures are naturally formed through a practitioner’s accumulated daily training. While a single image can bear no significance, when you accumulate them up to a certain threshold, there would be some sort of mystical reaction.

At the start of his embryonic stage, Garen started using his soul to clearly observe the formation process of the Living Secret Technique within his body every step of the way. Since the structure of his body was simple as most organs haven’t fully developed yet, logically, this was the ideal time to observe the formation of the Living Secret Technique. However, after observing it halfway, even Garen’s strong soul started feeling tired. From the dense and complex blood capillaries roadmap of the Living Secret Technique, to its effects and changes on other things like the endocrine system, even Garen started to get a headache from the overload of information.

The effects of the formation of the Living Secret Technique at the beginning was very minor, it was barely even noticeable at first, as it was only simple changes made towards the vital energy and blood. But as time passed, maybe after a month or so, Garen started to feel the difference.

The changes in his body under the influence from the formation of the Living Secret Technique slowly became more and more noticeable.

This change was leaning towards the Living Secret Technique, making the physical body more compatible with the Living Secret Technique’s potential, in turn strengthening it. With that, it also further sped up the changes in the body, as the strengthening reinforced the influence of the technique on the body.

This sort of mutual reinforcement made the changes come faster and faster.

"No wonder the Living Secret Technique is in the form of a seed. It functions just like a seed, starting slowly, then rapidly growing." Garen thought in realization.

However, the question still remains. Where did the power of the Living Secret Technique originate from?

From his close observation, when forming the Living Secret Technique, the baby’s body seemed to have produced a special energy out of nowhere.

It’s almost as if a person started drawing complex non-repeating symbols and images at random, and these images increased to a scary degree, suddenly creating a faint source of energy. This energy, though weak, started to reinforce the imagery, creating even stronger energy.

Although this statement may sound absurd, it was the conclusion that Garen managed to arrive at through his observations.

This was exactly how the Living Secret Technique worked, this influential power seemed to have been created mysteriously, as if it was miraculously created from nothing, completely ignoring the Law of the Conservation of Energy.

His infant body, under these changes, has also become strong and healthy, presenting an appropriate condition for the Living Secret Technique.

Finally, the day he had been waiting for was finally here.

Garren suddenly felt that his body was being forced out by a pushing pressure. From the outside, he started to hear encouraging words, accompanied by a lady’s cries of pain.

The squeezing force exerted on him started to felt stronger and stronger.

It felt as if his entire body was being squeezed through a cramped but elastic canal, moving towards a distinct direction.

He knew he was about to be born into the world.

Garen had a complicated range of emotions he felt at the time. He lived through three lifetimes, but now he was once again reborn from a stranger’s stomach. This lady had once again given him a physical body, given him a new life.

Chapter 568: Newborn 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This complicated feeling made him feel a sense of lamentation, but at the same time, happiness.

His happiness comes from the fact that he was finally able to escape the dark days of his past. As for his lamentation, he didn’t know himself where that feeling originated from.

As the squeezing force became even stronger, Garen just kept moving through the path in front of him.

With the combination of both parties’ efforts, finally, he felt a breeze of fresh air caress his skin. It felt like a tingly, stinging sensation.

He was promptly carried up by a pair of large hands, and was slowly wiped with a warm, damp towel. As the friction from the towel increased, the pain became more and more distinct. His skin was way too sensitive, even a soft and gentle rub would cause an intense pain.

As his umbilical cord still on his belly was swiftly cut off, that further intensified his pain, making Garen scream in pain.

Just as he opened his mouth and tensed up his throat, the amniotic fluid in his mouth came spraying out, dripping into a small basin.

Wa!!!!

The deafening cry of a newborn baby immediately filled the room.

He finally opened his eyes, his light blue eyes, after such a long time, could finally see the real world again. At that exact moment, he felt an indescribable sensation.

This world was filled with livelihood, all of this was real. The rays of light and color gave him a sensory overload, and touched his heart in an indescribable manner.

From the dark days of being locked in a prison, from God knows how long ago, to the exact moment of seeing light again.

Garen felt a sudden rekindling of hope towards this world, he wanted to feel this moved for eternity, forever and ever...

In the pure white hospital room, he saw the person who was carrying him, a nurse in blue uniform wearing a white surgical mask. She had a pair of black eyes and thick eyebrows, although her face did not look pretty with numerous pale yellow freckles, in his eyes, this nurse was the embodiment of joy and warmth.

The nurse opened her mouth and said a few words, then gently placed him in a crib next to the bed. Inside the crib was radiating a sense of warmth, almost as if it was an incubator.

The crib walls were made of clear glass, so he was able to see the bed through the glass. A lady with blonde and curly hair was lying on the bed, even though she could not be considered as a pretty person, she seemed gentle, looking lovingly at the crib.

"This is a newborn." Garen opened his mouth, but due to the fact that his vocal cords weren’t developed yet, all that could be heard was a child crying.

As he slowly crawled up from the crib, moving on the soft white cloth, he slapped the glass wall of the crib. That smooth and cool sensation of the glass had him mesmerized.

In one swift motion, the nurse’s big hands rubbed some fragrant white powder all over his skin, then wrapping him once again, keeping him warm as she gently picked him up from the crib and moved him to his bed beside his mother.

His mother gently touched his cheeks and softly uttered a few words. The warmness radiating from her eyes enveloped Garen with a sense of gentleness.

******

Time flew.

Garen was only born a month ago, and his infant body was still weak. As his brain had not been fully developed yet, it was still not able to support overly complex or clear conscious, thinking.

Thus, he spent most of his time suckling, sleeping, and pooping.

This embarrassing way of life made Garen, once the high and mighty leader of the White Cloud Gate and the Heavenly General of the Southern Holy Fist Gate, utterly lose his sense of self-esteem.

It’s would be fine if it were just being breastfed, but having to have someone change his diaper, that was the most humiliating thing he could experience in his lifetime! An utter disgrace!!

Garen always had a strong sense of resistance when it came to changing his diapers. Unfortunately for him, even though his infant body was strengthened by the Living Secret Technique as compared to other babies, the functionality of the Living Secret Technique was still minute at the beginning, and only gets strong later on.

As such, regardless of how strong his soul or secret techniques may be, the foundations of this current body were still too weak, making him no different from an actual baby. There was no use in resisting.

Without physical matter, the soul has no way of affecting reality, that was merely natural law.

So, no matter how embarrassing this way of living was, he had no choice but to continue as is.

If he were to look past this issue, everything has been going well for him. His body was becoming stronger and stronger, even if he were caught in a cold breeze he wouldn’t catch a cold or fall ill. His facial features were also rapidly developing, and his brain was also improving at a healthy rate. His originally fragile bones have started to become more and more sturdy, slowly allowing his body to support him crawling around.

This was only after approximately a month’s growth.

Garen was originally planning to re-train his Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, but his soul seed’s evil techniques could only do so much for the development of the body at this stage.

There wasn’t much else there was to change, even if one completely followed the training for the art of the Evil Techniques, it would still have some effects, but definitely not significantly drastic changes. Hence, he started trying out different secret technique training methods. He found out that most secret techniques to enhance special abilities have all lost their functionality. On the other hand, some low-level secret techniques, due to only enhancing the vital energy and blood regulation in the practitioner's body, were able to show decent results.

As for the Living Secret Technique, it overall only had made small improvements to the body, nothing else.

In actuality, since Garen was born, he felt there was something off about this world.

It wasn’t the fundamental construction of this world, but rather the environment of this world, it felt as if the Earth, the Secret Technique World, the Totem World, all of them seem to be slightly different.

Especially when he tried out his secret techniques, in his memory, there were easily hundreds of secret techniques that he knew, but when trying them out, he noticed that at a microscopic level, when his blood cells generate friction, or rather when matter generates friction, the amount of heat created was slightly smaller.

To put it simply, the degree of heat generated from friction was definitely smaller as compared to his past three worlds.

As the strongest Grandmaster of Combat, 6th form totem user that with a God-like existence in the Totem World, he definitely has the experience and expertise to notice even these minuscule changes.

However, this world seemed out of place to him.

Friction causes heat, this was one of the most basic concepts of the Laws of Conservation of Energy, if this had changed... It can only mean one of two things: the matter itself had been changed, or the blood cells in his body had been changed.

After two more months, Garen finally developed enough strength, he took his own diaper and started rubbing it on surrounding objects. After being grabbed and swaddled numerous times by his bearded father, he finally arrived at a conclusion to his little experiment.

It was not an issue with his own body, it was this entire world...

Not only that, there were also minor changes to the laws of physics that he once knew. This led Garen to come up with a few hypotheses.

He might be in a whole other universe right now.

Even he found this hypothesis laughable. This might also possibly be the effect caused by a change in the planet itself, but this could only be confirmed at a later stage.

Even if he managed to confirm this fact, what could he do? At this point, he was merely a baby, there was no meaning in pondering about the universe and the wider scale of things, but rather he should focus more on the development of his body and find a suitable gate of secret techniques to start his training in.

In his countless attempts trying out the secret techniques, Garen kept using his attributes ability to check his rate of growth. He also started to observe the environment surrounding this newborn’s family.

As for the issue of language, Garen, who was fluent in more than 10 languages, was easily able to figure out the cadence and linguistic form of the language. Even though his body had not yet matured, just based on an infant’s level of intellectual maturity, he was still able to swiftly grasp foundations of the native language.

His name was decided on the 2nd week, at that point Garen was able to make some simple audible syllables, so he kept repeating the 2 syllables "Ga-ren". After frustratingly declining every new name his parents came up with, they finally saw how insistent Garen was about this name, hence deciding on the name. The name was, of course, "Garen".

The environment of this world, or rather this planet, was normal. It was at the technological level of the Earth, as well as its degree of civilization, but this family seemed to be a bit special.

His father, Emmer Thomas, was a University Professor, he was gentle and wise, a pacifist, had a bushy beard and glasses, and had a soft personality. For the sake of his ecology research, he brought his family to live in seclusion in a small, remote town.

His mother, Trish Jeff, was a Psychologist. She was one of those people who applied her psychological training in her daily life. She was kind and understanding, but had an independent personality and a strong personal stance. She could be extremely kind, but when she got angry, she will be strict and harsh.

There was also Garen’s blood-related brother, Jason Thomas. This lad was 4 years old this year and had on numerous occasions tried to poke Garen with a stick while he was resting in the crib. He had a cheeky personality, at the start, he would be beaten up by their mother Trish every few days. Now that she was recovering on her maternal break, she was going to him daily. Luckily, under his father’s gentle guidance and persuasive education, he spent every day undergoing ideological education. With the combined efforts from both sides, even taking up Jason’s playtime, he finally realized his mistakes and apologized to his parents in tears. He promised to be a good boy from then on and turn over a new leaf, no longer harassing his younger brother, resolving this entire issue.

The Thomas household lived in a remote location in North America, isolated from the rest of the world and surrounded by woods. The air over here was fresh, and definitely made for a great retirement home.

Apparently, in this world, there was also an America. He learned this information while eavesdropping on his parents’ conversations, but he had no other information on this. However, the description feels quite similar to his original world, but there was still no word on the existence of oriental and eastern nations like China.

The small town they were living in was miles away from the city, as in, up to 1000 kilometers miles away. It was the very definition of being in isolation. The name of the town was Grano.

After vaguely getting a feel for his surroundings, Garen returned his focus to regaining his potential and strength.

Remembering the last crisis in the Totem World, he started to suspect that this might be due to the change in the surrounding environment, causing secret techniques to lose their compatibility. The weakening of the Living Secret Technique might also be attributed to the limitations of the environment. Luckily his soul seed wasn’t get affected, and functioned like a perpetual motion machine, slowly emitting influential nutrients deep within his soul as if it were slowly increasing Garen’s soul limit.

One’s soul limit was the deciding factor about the maximum attribute point cap one’s body could achieve at a genetic level.

In the Secret Technique World, he was able to increase his attribute point to multiple times that of an average individual; whilst in the Totem world, he was able to manipulate his body and absorb the consciousness of the Nine-Headed Hydra, increasing his attributes up to 10+ points.

To put it simply, it was precisely his soul limit that decided the final strength he can achieve.

Originally thinking that the soul seed was no longer of any use to him, finding out that the soul seed could raise his soul limit made Garen burst with joy.

If he could increase his attribute limit to 100 points, he would attain unimaginable power.

Unfortunately, the evil technique of this soul seed worked very slowly. According to his calculations, Garen estimated that it would require at least a year to raise just one attribute point.

As the attributes got stronger, the potential points required were also higher, this was an issue that Garen hadn’t found a solution to as of yet. However, this world looked nothing out of the ordinary, and seemed that there weren’t any unnatural powers present in this world. There were only average people around.

Since there weren’t any risky factors, he decided to temporarily take time to decide on his actions. Without the existence of unnatural powers, the source of potential points would be another problem.

Chapter 569: Youth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In a small bedroom with a yellow wooden floor.

A small blue-eyed baby was in a cradle, barely standing with one hand holding the wooden support, looking out the windows at the branches swaying in the wind. Outside the window, there was a giant ash tree, swaying with each gust of wind. On the branches, two palm-sized sparrows were cheerfully chirping about.

The still hairless Garen was just staring at the sparrows, clad with nothing but a towel wrapped around his butt and holding on to a small leather ball, he looked on in a state of distractedness. He was still considering his options for secret techniques.

"From the list of secret techniques I have learned, after sorting them out according to their functionality and then attempting to integrate them into this body, only 53 secret techniques remain. Then, from these 53 gates’ secret techniques, sorting them up by their typings, taking into account their strengths and their compatibility with this body, there would only be 13 gates left."

Garen frowned while rubbing his chin.

"There are essentially a few different methods of secret technique selection. One, based on their special effects, the effects after training in these sets of techniques where one would be able to produce special effects like the Red Jade Palm or the Toxic Sand Palm. Two, based on their base advantage, wherein after training in these sets of techniques, one’s speed, vitality, defense, attack and other stats can attain special enhancements. Three, based on balance, these types of techniques have no extremities, and unleashes the overall potential of the body, gives one longevity and significantly enhances one’s spiritual strength."

"The Living Secret Technique had naturally turned from the first type to the third type, and it has now become a technique purely for one’s health. The only bad thing about this is that it works very slowly, due to the fact that it had to spread out its potency evenly to all attributes, naturally slowing it down."

Garen was looking through the 13 gates of secret techniques he had narrowed down.

"Due to the changes in my body caused by the Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, it’s still best for me to train in Ice-type abilities. I might as well just pick base on special effects. Being able to still use secret techniques in another world should probably still be counted in the categories that are derived from physical laws of this world."

"Within the 13 gates of secret techniques, there were only 2 under the special effects type, the Black Claw of Sethe and Andelina’s Capture. The Black Claw of Sethe has 4 levels, it’s an Ice-Poison attribute secret technique, after every level, the Ice-Poison attribute would be strengthened. As for Andelina’s Capture, although it may sound like a technique to capture targets, in reality, it’s a technique that creates multiple ice needles, creating a wall of Ice Spikes."

After a bit of hesitation, Garen still picked the Black Claw of Sethe.

Squeak...

The room door opened, his mother Trish walked in dressed in a white blouse and gently started helping Garen change his diaper. The 4-year-old Jason was standing at the side, watching with a strange sense of amusement glowing from his face.

Bonk....

Garen threw the ball in his hand without any hesitation, hitting Jason right in the face.

Wah!!!

The cheeky boy escaped the room in tears.

"Jason, Jason! Stop!" Their mother Trish shouted.

"Oh heavens, what a little devil you are, being able to bully your older brother even at this age, I can’t even imagine what you’d do in the future." Trish furiously glared as she pinched Garen’s cheeks. After rapidly changing his diapers, she ran off to chase after Jason.

Thus, Garen was once again alone in the room.

He was still standing in the white cradle, continuing on with his previous thoughts

.

"All of these secret techniques I have narrowed down, they’re all at absurdly high-leveled secret techniques, with power comparable to even the heavenly figures. Even for the Black Claw of Sethe, it’s still not secret technique completely compatible with this body yet, I still need to train in order to understand the details of it. Maybe I can combine it with some concepts from other secret techniques."

He started brainstorming again.

As time slowly passed, Garen lived his life in this boring manner, with his mother Trish beside him, reading the latest International Journal of Psychology on her laptop whilst taking care of Garen who rarely cried or threw tantrums.

Usually, when Garen cried once, it means he was hungry. When he cried twice, it meant that he needs to use the potty, and when he cried thrice, it means that the swaddle wrapped around him felt uncomfortable. As compared to the neighbor’s kid, Serin, who was born a few months earlier, this saved Garen’s parents a lot of hassle.

However, this kind of boring routine lifestyle was absolute torture for Garen. Luckily, after a few more months, his father Emmer made a set of early education resources, planning on starting Garen’s early learning.

******

"Don’t you think it’s too early? Don’t babies usually only start learning phonemes at the age of 2 or 3?" Trish said while folding Garen’s baby clothes.

"Have you ever seen a baby crawling at a month old?" Emmer countered while looking through the prepared materials and resources.

"But I asked one of my friends who was a child specialist, she said that usually a baby should only start engaging in early language education at a few years old. If we start off too early, they will just forget what they learned as they grow up."

"Have you ever seen a baby crawling at a month old?" Emmer asked as he picked up one of the selected books and skimmed through its contents.

"Doing this may lead to the kid being placed under too much pressure, his attention span is still small, he’s only four years old after all!" Trish said in front of Emmer, with her arms crossed.

"Have you ever seen a baby crawling at a month old?" Emmer raised his voice and put down the book he was holding. "I suspect that our child is a prodigy!" He exclaimed seriously.

"Alright, alright. Every parent would want to believe their child is a prodigy, or was a prodigy." Trish helplessly sat down.

"Then, let’s try it out." Emmer placed the prepared education materials in front of Garen, the cover page was filled with fancy colourful images.

"Let’s start with the basic phonemes, then the alphabet." Emmer planned everything deliberately, his previous experience with Jason made him feel confident in his plans.

Garen opened his eyes wide, he felt that he shouldn’t be too extraordinary, it would be better if he pretended to be a bit more "normal" for now.

"The first alphabet, ‘a...’" Emmer opened his mouth at Garen.

"..."

"a..."

"..."

As such, the pair continued to stare intently at each other.

His mother Trish stood up, speechless, and walked out. After a short moment, she returned with another baby, swaddled in a red blanket and placed her into the cradle as well.

"This is the neighboring Serin, her mother just went outstation. Mr Walter needed people for the Public Security Team, so she asked us to take care of her child for a couple of days."

Lil’ Serin was about a couple months older than Garen, and after being placed in the cradle, all she did was sit, motionless, staring curiously at Garen with her jet black eyes.

"If you’re gonna teach Garen, you might as well teach both of them." Trish said, then walked off to read her theses.

"‘a...’ Repeat after me, ‘a...’" Emmer didn’t give up on his attempt.

"..."

"Come on, look at me, look into your dad’s eyes, you’re a prodigy, you’re a prodigy, you’re a prodigy you’re a prodigy youreaprodigyyoureaprodigy..." Emmer’s expectations started to crumble.

"k."

Emmer suddenly jolted in excitement.

"No, not ‘k’, it’s ‘a…’, look at my mouth shape."

"k..."

Garen followed his mouth shape, but for some weird reason the sound that came out was still "k..."

"Oh my God!! Trish!! Trish!!" His dad was a broken man, he threw the book down and went over to call his wife.

Garen uninterestedly shook his head, then turned his head to look at Serin.

At this age, the baby would still be bald, like him, and distinct facial features would not have been developed yet, so he couldn’t tell what she would look like in the future.

"I guess it’d be better for me to focus on my secret techniques..."

He once again placed his attention back on his secret techniques and attribute abilities.

Looking at his attributes:

"Garen Thomas: Strength 0.2, Agility 0.2, Vitality 0.3, Intelligence 0.4, Potential 0%."

"How poor..." he helplessly sighed. What about his Skill Pane?

"Soul Type: Northern Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique -- 1 attribute point limit increase per year. Innate Vitality change leaning towards Frost-Steel types."

"Secret Techniques: None"

After that, the list ended.

This body didn’t have any skills, and all his potential points were exhausted in the Mother Stream.

Well, since he already picked a secret technique, Garen started to focus his energy on his first introductory training of the secret techniques.

The Black Claw of Sethe had 4 levels, the first level required very specific commands, postures, and mental concentration, combined to precisely manipulate one’s vital energy and blood. Only then will one be initiated into the secret technique.

However, for Garen, having to go through all that trouble, his soul’ strongest strength was that it was his body’s vital energy and blood through neurons. This was actually a specialty of a Grandmaster of Combat - Aura.

After concentrating energy into an aura, the soul would gain authority to use said aura to manipulate the body. In other words, a soul’s strength could only be utilized through auras, otherwise it was no different than that of the average individual, using their soul as a form of consciousness to control their thoughts and replicate everyday actions, unable to control one’s body with extreme precision.

"The first level of the Black Claw of Sethe can train and improve one’s heart, slowly improving the blood typing. This requires one to absorb the cold at 12 midnight every night when the temperature is at its lowest. This is to get the body used to the cold, so it does not harm the body. With proper special vital energy and blood regulation, one can achieve the manipulation of vital energy and blood, without harming the body in the process." Garen thought to himself in a logical manner.

"Usually this requires a lot of strengthening from things like medication, but since my body has already been changed by evil techniques, this bit of cold won’t even bother me. All I need to do know is to accordingly absorb the cold everyday at 12 midnight."

After making that decision, Garen started to lie down to get some rest, completely ignoring Serin who was right next to him. This was his first introduction into the secret techniques, and would set a foundation for his skills in the future. He had to be extremely careful, after all, he was still only a few months old, his body must still be insanely weak.

After awakening from his sleep in the afternoon, his mother Trish came in to feed him some milk. However, he still felt hungry, so she gave him 2 more bottles of Camel’s milk, only then was Garen satisfied and went back to bed.

In the evening, his father Emmer came in once again, thinking of attempting his early education once again. But as he noticed that Garen sound asleep, he quietly left him to wash his diapers.

His mother Trish was in the room, occasionally checking if Lil’ Serin had wet the bed. Most of her time was spent on reading the theses written in her journal. As for Lil’ Jason, he was squatting in the living room completely focused on his cartoons.

As the night fell, the sky through the window slowly turned from white to gray, then slowly darker, and finally turning pitch black, with countless stars spread all over the night sky.

This room was on the second floor, and visible from it was a small town road, where a couple of cars would occasionally pass by. Yellow and white headlights kept flashing on the ceiling as each car passed through. The faint bickering of children also came in through the window, along with the cries of dogs and cats.

Trish surfed the web under the desk lamp, up till late at night, before washing up and going to bed with his husband.

After the two eventually fell asleep, Garen suddenly opened his eyes, waking up in the cradle.

He crawled out from his swaddle, looked over at Serin who was still next to him. That girl was still sleeping soundly.

The clock on the wall neared twelve o’clock.

Garen’s upper body was completely naked, wearing only a diaper, he was sitting at the edge of the cradle, slowly awaiting the designated time.

In the darkness, the only source of light was the streetlight from outside the window, shining dimly on the ceiling.

Outside, a car drove past. Garen could hear the muffled sound of the car radio, and a young couple cheerfully bantering.

Garen was sitting in the cradle, putting his hands together to form some complicated hand signs, which looked like an unruly tree branche in the shape of an "L", but also somewhat like an "A".

His body was seated in a cross-legged position, with one eye open and the other shut.

As every minute and every second passed, Garen maintained his posture, motionless, like a statue. However, in actual fact, his hand signs were changing with each of his heartbeats

Dong… Dong… Dong…

Midnight had come.

Garen’s heart suddenly vibrated, then stopped for an instant, before starting to beat at a steady, but even faster pace.

He concentrated his aura and controlled the regulation of his body’s vital energy and blood carefully and precisely.

"Level 1 of the Black Claw of Sethe - Heart of Frost"

On the skill pane, the secret techniques tab finally changed from "none", a complicated light red symbol started to form, its shape looking similar to Garen’s first hand sign, in the shape of an "L", but also somewhat like an "A".

"Secret Techniques:

The Black Claw of Sethe -- LV1 Heart of Frost 1%(1/4)"

He stayed in this position for a few more minutes. Garen the quickly recovered from his training, and felt sore all over. Looking at his skill pane, he can’t help but let out a small grin.

Chapter 570: Youth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"1% huh, getting 1% improvement just from the 1st training, that’s not bad." After all, all the secret techniques he picked out of his expert memory were not just any random simple secret technique. If they weren’t one discovered by the ancients, it would be a high-leveled secret technique developed by the major gates in the world of Wushu.

Not only that, all of the selected secret techniques had a common trait; they are all secret techniques that Garen could not "see through". At his level of expertise, an average secret technique could be effortlessly mimicked by him, even without training. Only secret techniques that were at an extremely high level or self-pioneered in a field that Garen had no experience in could not be "seen through" by him.

The Black Claw of Sethe was what he accidentally discovered from his travels with Andrela when he returned to the Secret Technique World. It was one of the 20 gates of secret techniques that made Garen hit a brick wall when trying to mimic.

Based on his own experience, he tweaked some minor details of it to improve the overall effect of it, but even then, he was still excited to witness the tangible effects of this skill.

This secret technique should at least be a God-tier level advanced secret technique, since even with his expertise he still couldn’t see through its secrets, the effect must be well above average.

After finishing his 1st training, Garen didn’t dare to be greedy. No matter how good the food was, eating excessively would still lead to indigestion. Everything must be done in moderation.

After cleaning up a bit, he lied down and went back to bed.

******

As the days passed, Garen continued his routine of eating, drinking, sleeping, training, then repeat.

This dull and mechanical lifestyle, along with having to pretend to be a baby in light of his dad’s early education, he had to find ways to seek pleasure in this miserable life. His only joy in this lifestyle was trying to play with Lil’ Serin, who was occasionally brought over, or just bullying his brother Jason Thomas.

His mother Trish would occasionally be busy with a website for posting her theses. This was her primary source of income, for a good thesis, every time someone bought, downloaded or read it, she would get a large portion of the earnings.

His father also recruited a new research student recently, every day he went out with this young lady, running around, claiming it was in the name of research.

Garen couldn’t believe his mother was worried about his father getting along with that beautiful young lady. In fact, she was completely calm about it.

This household was still calm as usual.

Garen steadily practiced the Black Claw of Sethe every day, and had consistent improvement, with almost a 1% improvement every day. He felt that the rate of growth really was absurdly quick, it must have had something to do with this modified body being extremely compatible with this gate of secret techniques.

According to the records on this Secret Technique, finishing level 1 would at least take 10 years.

However, at his rate of growth, he only needed slightly more than 100 days to complete the level 1 foundation training. He was truly a genius of geniuses.

In such a peaceful environment with no threats or safety issues, even Garen started to become fully immersed in his training.

About three months swiftly passed.

Lil’ Serin, who was occasionally brought over, had also learned how to crawl, making intelligible sounds while frolicking in the crib.

In comparison, Garen was already able to stand up steadily in the cradle and walk on two feet. He also started to grow blonde hair like his mother’s.

A blue-eyed blonde, with skin as white as milk. Except for his dislike of speaking, Garen was no different from a normal baby. His pretending was largely based on Lil’ Serin’s actions, who should be slightly older than him, thus he should be considered normal.

His mother also found an early education cartoon from somewhere and played it on loop in Garen’s room every day.

Garen was also living quite the carefree life, no one was paying much attention to him, so he could focus completely on his internal body. Whenever there seemed to be a problem with a part of his body, he could immediately use his aura to manipulate his vital energy and blood to regulate the area. As a top-level Grandmaster of Combat, he had no problems in completely understanding the structure and inner mechanisms of his body.

His life was very relaxing, occasionally having his parents’ friends or neighbors coming over to pay a visit. Garen was also occasionally brought outside to get some fresh air and sunshine. This allowed him to gain some information about the town.

The whole town is in the shape of a gigantic circle, surrounded by luscious greenery. In the middle of it all was a town center. Every night, there would be a gathering among the seniors of the town to banter or play cards and chess.

The town was deep in the woods, and it was said to be the originally built up by the natives. However, due to external influence and the advancement of technology, the scale of the town kept expanding. Now it was a small town with a population size in the millions.

The town had a church, with the Reverend Father and the Mayor being the most respected people in this town, every major decision would be made by them. The town also has a Public Security Team, in charge of the security of the town and also to drive out the wildlife from the forest that entered the town.

Garen also discovered that most of the townspeople were hunters or lumberjacks, and most of them also had their own land and use to farm their own grain and vegetables for food. There was also a beach nearby with a decently sized fishing market, and the fishermen often sent some seafood over to the town for sale. Occasionally, there would also be tourists who came here to visit. It was even considered a decent source of income.

To put it simply, this seemed like a Heaven on Earth, everyone living here was content and law-abiding, while foreign businesses attempting to enter for profit were all driven out by the locals.

The townspeople locals, permanent residents, and foreigners who were brought back by locals, like wives who married in. This included doctors, lawyers, restaurant owners, teachers and all sorts of other professions, creating the unique structure and exclusivity of this town.

Garen’s was reborn into the Thomas household, who were considered quite well-known within this area. After all, it was a university professor and a psychologist who decided to move into this small town to settle down. In the eyes of the townspeople, this was major news.

Many people wanted to speak to this group of intellectuals, hoping some of their genii would rub off on them.

Every year before Christmas, they would also receive countless gifts.

Garen was still unsure about this world, but not only did it contain America, it also had holidays like Christmas. He even heard a few mentions of England and other terms.

This made him wonder if he had returned to Earth.

However, there was once his parents left him alone, he immediately seized the opportunity to use his mother’s laptop, pretending to randomly press stuff, while searching for information like the world map.

To his surprise, he found a map of this world. It looked similar to Earth, but at the same time, there were major differences.

The area of the 5 continents were much larger than Earth’s, the sea as well, it was almost 2 times the size of the Earth. Just as he was staring at the map in shock, Trish walked back in.

"Don’t go so near, there’s radiation." Trish quickly took away the laptop in fear of harming the child’s eyes.

Garen was placed back into the cradle, allowing his mother to freely change his diaper while he was thinking intently.

After all, he was quite free every day. A baby’s energy seems to be limitless with no place to expend it on. Except for his Black Claw of Sethe - LV1 Heart of Frost training every night, he had nothing else to do.

"Putting all information together, this world might be a planet similar to Earth but in a parallel universe, but I have no idea why the planet would be so much bigger in size."

Garen refused to believe that there would be 2 planets with so many similarities within one universe, and there was also the matter of the laws of physics being different in this world. He started to confirm his suspicion.

"This world and this universe, might not even be my original universe anymore…"

He felt that continuing on doing nothing would be too boring, so he sneakily took the laptop and started to look up more information about this alternate earth.

As compared to the pile of early education resources his dad had found, doing self-learning online courses was much faster.

Kindergarten, primary school, lower-secondary school, he swiftly breezed through these courses. All he needed to do was vaguely skim through it, his soul’s memory could remember every image it saw with just a glance.

However, as he was about to start his upper-secondary school course, his parents confiscated the laptop with the reason being they were afraid him using it too much would affect his sight and health.

Even though he had just been playing around with the laptop for a couple of days.

As such, his boring life continued on. Soon, Garen was already 2 years old.

From the cradle to his first running steps, to being able to dress, eat and use the toilet all by himself, the 2-year-old Garen was exhibiting terrifying early maturation and independence. He never threw tantrums, and was not a picky eater. Coupled with his glowing blonde hair, milk-white skin and big blue eyes, he became a hot topic around the town.

A lot of his parents friends liked to come visit and play with Lil’ Garen.

Garen also started to show his talents in speaking, at 2 years old, while other children were childishly speaking, his sentences seemed to be deliberate, complex and well-structured, all whilst still being fluent in his expression.

Even his height was just slightly shorter than his 6-year-old brother Jason. Jason’s face was filled with acne and he was filled with energy every day. He spent his time causing trouble, whilst his brother Garen preferred to read quietly or listening to music. The two formed a stark contrast.

Obviously, the younger Garen naturally became the favorite of his parents. This seemed to cause a mental imbalance in Jason.

Whoosh...

With one swift swipe, Jason took all the lollipops given by the neighbors into his pockets, then cheekily walked over to Garen looking at him.

"All the lollipops the Uncle Walter gave us belongs to me!" he loudly exclaimed.

"Idiot."

Garen expressionlessly said as he walked past his brother.

Jason stood there motionlessly, as if he was struck by lightning. After a long while, he looked over in the direction his brother left.

"Garen how dare you insult me! I’m your brother! Let me come punish you right now!"

He shouted as he charged over towards Garen.

Two minutes later...

"Mama..." Jason left Garen’s room in tears, running towards their parents’ room.

"How many times has it been? He still had no improvements…" Garen said condescendingly while shaking his head.

On the surface, his current body’s seemed to be comparable to a 5 or 6 year old boy, but in reality, his body has far exceeded that of a child, all his stats are already almost at 0.8, almost at an adult’s level of strength.

This was one of the advantages of the Heart of Frost, all of his organs had an abnormal, but steady pace of growth, becoming stronger and stronger, effectively working with the Living Secret Technique’s constant modification of the blood cells and his heart.

He did not know how long these kinds of modifications will require, but with the effects of the Heart of Frost, his heart has started to show signs of frosting. This sense of cold usually concentrated in his chest, but it would occasionally split and move through the bloodstream.

Once the modification of his heart is complete, this 1st level would have completely reached its peak, then it would be time for him to start his training for the next level.

Chapter 571: Youth 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Listen, Garen." His mother Trish bent down and said to her child, "I’ve decided to send you the Kindergarten, otherwise you’ll be idling around in the house everyday bullying your older brother. At this point, he starts trembling just at the sight of you. What do you think of this decision?"

Garen nodded his head.

"Kindergarten? You mean the one in town?"

"Yes, although you may be a bit too young, but your father and I agree that you should already have met the entry requirements." Trish answered seriously.

"Jason’s going to primary school, right?" Garen suddenly changed the topic.

"Yes, the primary school in town."

"Then I also want to go to primary school." Garen definitely didn’t want to spend his days in kindergarten playing house with the other brats, that would definitely be a waste of time.

"Primary school requires pre-school education, do you know what is pre-school education? Also, you should call him ‘Brother’, not Jason."

"Is that so? Well that’s regretful, but I still want to go for Primary School." Garen said affirmatively. "Regarding pre-school education, haven’t I already went through all that?"

"A 2-year-old is not allowed to go to primary school, you’re still too young, dear," Trish started to feel that talking to her son is getting a bit tiring.

"Do the laws and legislations of this country state that 2-year-olds are not allowed to go to primary school?" Garen countered.

"Where did you even learn the phrase ‘laws and legislations’?" Trish started to get a headache. "Anyways, even though you can now speak fluently, the basics of Art, Music, Math and Languages all require a strong foundation."

"Like Jason?"

"Like Jason."

"But he always gets beaten by me to the verge of crying, he’s far too weak."

"..." Trish took a deep breath, "Dear, sometimes issues cannot be resolved purely through using your fists."

"But those things have nothing to do with me beating him up."

Garen said calmly.

"Holy..." Trish felt as if she was gonna go mad. As a psychologist, she completely could not understand what her child was thinking.

"Mama, what do you think about my suggestion? As a parent, you should have more confidence in your own child!"

The result of this conversation was that Trish had fled from the room.

She didn’t know how she could persuade her own son, or maybe she needed to hatch a plan against his overly mature son, let him understand that not everything can be solved with physical strength.

"He’s completely unlike a 2 year old, in fact he seems to be more mature than even 5 or 6 year olds! Emmer, I’ve run out of ideas on how to teach our son…..."

Trish’s voice could be heard from outside the room.

"Don’t worry, I told you, our son is a prodigy!" Emmer said proudly.

Garen helplessly shook his head and walked over to the bookshelf, picking up a random book.

"Hey Garen!" Jason came out of nowhere, cockily waving around a plastic bat.

"This time I’m gonna make you cry uncle!" Jason boldly exclaimed.

Garen just glared at him and walked straight up to him, putting his book back on the shelf.

With a left hook to the jaw, following it up with an uppercut to the gut, his opponent fell.

"Bang!!"

"Mama!!!" Jason threw away the plastic bat and crawled out of the room.

Garren then proceeded the walk back to the bookshelf to continue reading.

After this incident, Garren was once again dragged off by his father for some ideological education. The 30-minute long nonstop ideological speech was said to be his father Emmer’s special move, and it was also his pacifist way of teaching that he was so proud about.

However, when it came to Garren, the effects of this education method seemed to be less than obvious.

Garen was definitely listening to it seriously, he confirmed that as Garen continuously nodded in agreement to his words. However, what was worrying was that there weren’t any visible effects from it. After listening to the talk, he’d just go back the way he was immediately after.

This kind of peaceful lifestyle continues on.

Garen was still forced into Kindergarten in the end, along with their neighbors’ Lil’ Serin. They were both enrolled together in the town’s Kindergarten. The reason was that as a human, a social creature, too much interaction with people of a different age than you can cause problems. Garen had no choice but to agree, though clearly Serin was very obviously not ready for Kindergarten.

******

The kindergarten was located on the west side of the town near the suburbs, it was about 300 meters away from Garen’s house. It was the only rainbow colored building in a sea of gray blocks.

The white outer wall was covered with drawings of strawberries, apples, bananas, and pineapples. The building was also surrounded by a walled fence, and within the fence were slides, tire swings, seesaws and other children’s playground items.

Inside was a wide classroom, it had white walls and a black blackboard. On the left of the classroom were 3 wide window panes.

There were 3 big, long tables in the middle of the classroom, with reddish-brown surfaces covered with varnish, while the sharp corners were covered with a rubber protector.

A woman wearing red sporting attire was raising both her hands, imitating a cat while singing. Although she was already 30 years old, her actions made her look like she was a lot younger.

"Everyday is the kitty’s birthday, she can eat fish every day ~"

"Kitty likes to catch mice, yarn she also likes~"

"She can jump and can climb, she can even swim and dive~"

"Cute meowing in the end, kitty is our best friend~"

Every line sang by the teacher, was then followed up by a chorus of tens of cheery kids. It combined to form an unintelligible song of gibberish, but since a child’s voice was crisp and youthful, it didn’t sound that bad.

"That’s right, this is Music class." Garen was sitting at the very end of one of the long tables, he was cringing slightly as he looked out at the swaying trees.

Under the bright morning sun, the dried yellow leaves of the parasol tree were falling one after the other, creating a thick layer of autumn leaves on the ground. The janitor lady swept up the falling leaves, preventing it from being infested by caterpillars.

This was 2 months after he had enrolled in the kindergarten, he was already bored out of his mind.

He was pondering if he should actually display his actual maturity and intellectual level, so he can escape this torture that is being surrounded by numerous snot-nosed brats.

"Eileen! Eileen Kurt!" the teacher shouted again.

This was an everyday occurrence, this little girl called Eileen Kurt would always get into trouble for sleeping in class.

Garen glanced over at the little girl in twintails, who was now standing up. She had big, watery black eyes, yellow skin with a tender complexion, and a face that still had baby fat, but still weirdly cute. However, at the moment, she had a troubled face, looking like she was on the verge of tears.

"T-Teacher… I’m s-sorry… It was an accident..."

Eileen said softly.

The teacher helplessly reprimanded her just for a bit, after all, children this age were very prone to crying, except for a few exceptions of course.

"Garen! Garen!" The child next to him asked in a shouting whisper, "Do you know why birds can fly?"

"Of course, it’s because they have feathers."

"What are feathers?"

"They are hairs that grow all over the bird’s body."

"Really? You can fly if you have enough hair? But my dad has a lot of hair, why can’t he fly?"

"Because his hair is growing in the wrong places."

"Is that so?"

"Yes it’s true, you can go back and ask your father about it, Serin," Garen said to his small friend.

"Ok..."

The 1st period was finally over, now they had Maths class.

"Garen, come to the board. What is 2 + 5 =?" The Maths teacher was a bespectacled young lady who looked like she was in her early twenties, wearing a white T-shirt and a gray knee-length skirt. She was sporting a long ponytail.

Garen immediately became the center of attention of all the kids in the class. He wearily dropped his pen he used for doodling to pass time, and walked up to the board.

It was already autumn. He was wearing a gray turtleneck shirt, looking as if he was completely snugged in the shirt; he looked adorable.

He took a long chalk and mindlessly wrote a big 7 on the board, then promptly walked back to his seat.

"Did everyone see that? The answer was 7 ! 2 + 5 = 7 ! Great work Garen! Let’s give Garen a round of applause!" The teacher enthusiastically clapped loudly.

At that moment, the students in the class also started applauding for him.

Sigh...

Garen let out a long sigh, how many more days do I have to spend like this...

He felt the chill in his chest getting colder and colder, but his body felt no discomfort at all. On the contrary, it felt quite comfortable, that icy chill wasn’t just comfortable, it felt as pleasurable eating a cold and juicy watermelon on a hot summer day.

However, even though his Heart of Frost training was completed, this type of modification made Garen’s body temperature much lower than the average child, it also seemed to have affected Garen’s body growth and facial features.

His build was becoming more and more unisexual, if you looked at him from a distance, you wouldn’t even be able to tell if he’s a boy or a girl.

Yet, Garen didn’t mind that, he was still a kid after all, and kids generally don’t look overly masculine or feminine anyway.

The subjects taught in the kindergarten include Nature studies, Social studies, Maths, Language, Arts, and Music. 1 period was only 20 minutes long, so class ends very quickly, after that, they have lots of different playtimes. They have group play, outdoor play, playing house, and sometimes, even the teachers joined in.

At these times, Garen would usually just sit at a corner and quietly draw, his loyal admirer and friend Serin would also sit right beside him, attempting to mimic his actions.

No matter if it were crayon, watercolor or a pen, Garen was able to use it in a strangely mesmerizing manner.

He was actually not very good at art, and even then he was purposely doing badly to prevent from blowing his cover. Hence, although his drawings look complete, they were nothing more than childish scribbles.

Houses, sunsets, birds, watchdogs, etc. Garen would just draw anything that came to mind. However, in actuality, though no one managed to see it, Garen was secretly testing out the extent of the modification from the Heart of Frost.

With the Heart of Frost modification in place, just by visualizing it, Garen could manipulate the movement of the chilliness, gathering it at his fingertips. This level of chilliness could only lower his finger temperature by about 10°C, it would only make the skin feel slightly colder at most, hence it had no extra functionality. However, Garen just took this as a form of training to control the balanced unleashing of power, and whilst unleashing this power, silently assess the origins of it.

Life in Kindergarten was boring, other than training his secret techniques, everything else was boring. Especially since he had to interact with the other brats and the teachers, all whilst trying to hide his actual intellectual level.

Chapter 572: Youth 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was good that his ability to make time pass quickly was decent.

Soon, winter came and a snowstorm engulfed the entire Grano town, turning it snow white. A thick layer of snow covered the streets and plazas, and crisp crackling sounds could be heard from footsteps upon the snow.

After Christmas, Garen received a set of high-end drawing equipment, as well as a pretty-looking violin. Mom intended to make him acquire artistic and elegant musical skills.

Surprisingly, Trish got pregnant again soon. Days passed in boredom.

As the autumn of the second year came, the third kid was born.

Vivien, Vivien Thomas was his sister's name.

The good news was, Garen's kindergarten life would soon be over, as the four-year-old him would soon enter primary school.

His brother Jason's body had also become stronger; he was 4 years older than Garen. At 8 years old, he was now indulged in music and football. He went to the preschool when he was five, and as he entered third grade, his height had grown rapidly even for someone of the puberty age, he was already about one head higher than Garen.

"I heard you're coming to school soon?" Jason screamed while rushing into Garen's room on one random day.

"Yes."

There was only one primary school in the town, so both siblings would be in the same school, which made Jason excited.

"Is there something that matters?" Garen was practicing his violin, that redwood violin was pressed between his shoulder and neck, the precise control of his power allowed him to pull out a pure, uniform sound with ease.

After a month of teaching her son, Trish no longer taught him; after she taught him the standard pose, she decided to let him self-learn online. After all, simple things like violins were completely possible to self-learn so long as the pose were fine.

"No… nothing." After that glare from his brother, Jason shivered, and he hurried out of the room. He wasn't entirely sure why was he excited, but being happy was all that mattered.

Compared to kindergartens, primary schools were much more normal, grade schoolers were so much stronger than kindergartners, in terms of intelligence and socializing.

As he saw Jason run out the room, he continued his own violin training course.

Mono practice, scale transformation, complex music variation Etude.

With only one glance on the video's bow style, Garen could replicate any sounds without any mistakes, as he was sensitive to minute changes to the vibration, it allowed him to swiftly master the technique.

That was why he could be this masterful in a month.

But, oddly enough, the tunes that he played had a cold icy feeling, instead of a melodious feeling, it spooked people.

The more precise his controls, the more obvious this feeling became, just like a psychopath who played violin in a puddle of blood after murdering his victims.

Oddly, this oddity didn't attract his parents' attention under his cover-up, he suspected that this was a problem originating from the Heart of Frost.

Following the Heart of Frost's peak modification, he'd achieved a realm whereby he could exude a calming aura just by standing around them.

Heart of Frost's official second level was to use the frost breath for battles, but Black Claw of Sethe's strongest point was not about its near infinite control on cold poison. Instead, it was the ability to absorb the chill from organic enemies. This Secret Technique's complete philosophy revolved similar to the Yin-Yang philosophy. In its system, all creatures were made from Yin's Coldness and Yang's warmth, and if one had mastered the Black Claw of Sethe, it would cause two special damage effects, one being the Yin Coldness' damage, and the ability to absorb opponents' Yin Coldness in their bodies.

Once the opponent's Yin Coldness was absorbed, their body's heat would not be contained, and the outer cold poison which had berserk properties would continuously destroy the balancing ability of the body. This way, it could cause immense internal injuries.

If the opponent wasn't an expert who specialized in healing, they would find it extremely hard to counter such complicated moves.

On the other hand, the yin coldness absorbed by Garen could be used to strengthen Garen's Secret Technique and enhance his vitality.

Following the greater realms achieved in Sethe's Secret Technique, its damage and absorption power would also be strengthened.

As Garen played the violin, he identified that he had indeed reached the peak of the first level. It was just that he wasn't aware of when he could make a breakthrough.

After his violin session, he wiped the pine oil off the strings to prevent corrosion of the strings, he then carefully stored the violin in the box.

The time to enroll in primary school soon arrived.

Little Serin was still the same class as Garen. This was neither luck nor was it planned, but because the primary school only had one preschool class…

Aside from the two of them, all the children of age would join this class.

Serin's father was a security officer, whereas her mom was a housewife. Compared to the three children in Garen's household, they obviously looked more well off, hence Trish asked Serin's mom, Mrs. Feller, to pick up her children when she fetched her daughter from school.

The primary school was on the right side of the town's central plaza, up ahead were some shops, including a buffet restaurant, a stationary shop, florist, and some eateries.

The life in primary school was better compared to kindergarten, but the actual situation was about the same, the curriculum was like to torture to Garen, and he had to act like his peers sometimes.

The saving grace, however, was the fact that he could now freely use a computer, not the notebook that belonged to his mother but the desktop that he built.

This was greatly useful for him in understanding the knowledge system of this world.

His daily life continued to repeat itself, schooling, eating, finish school, goes home, violin practice, computer games, sleep. This repeated in an endless loop.

Preschool, Standard 1, Standard 2, time flew by without any mishaps.

Everything was calm as time flowed by.

Garen observed that nobody surrounding him had any trace of abnormality, except that the families living in the town maintained their ancient prayer ceremony where they prayed to their own ancestors. Aside from that, there were no differences or anything special.

Not only that, there seemed to be a certain barrier between the residences of the northern bound town and the rest of the territories. The people of the north were seen to be the representatives of the pastor, whereas the remaining villagers were seen to be the representatives of the mayor. The territories of the pastor had a small river stream, and as there was a deeper, more dangerous forest nearby, there were cases of wild animals attacking human beings outside of the forest. There were even cited cases of people being poisoned by venomous snakes or deaths from cheetahs' and wolves' attacks. Hence the primary schoolers typically refrained from playing near the river on the north.

"That place is very dangerous, big grey wolves will come out to catch children for snacks."

This was quoted from the teacher, word for word.

According to Garen's own observations, the north side did have fewer inhabitants, and the situation there was slightly worse. The thugs of the town would sometimes be seen on the streets and were mostly the familiar faces of the town, and they would normally join the festivals organized by the town.

They usually donned an attire that obviously looked like a thug but at the same time, they also seem to be a bunch of organized folks. They were oddly disciplined and aside from the occasional brawl in the north, the rest of the citizens of the territory were all lawful people.

As though there were someone pulling the strings from behind,

The primary schoolers' lives were boring, but soon there would be an interesting event.

A school-organized picnic.

As the two classes of Standard 2 students merged, including the school ten-odd teachers' participation, they all set the journey to the forest nearby.

Totalling over 40 students, wearing an assortment of clothes, each of them was excited, and so were the accompaniment of the parents.

The forest vicinity of the picnic was guarded by the security officers, and there were patrol officers passing through this area daily, establishing it as a safe zone.

Garen had just advanced to Standard 2, but aside from Serin, he didn't have any friends, hence he preferred to stay at the back of the line.

The group followed in a line and soon, they reached the safe zone and put out the tablecloth, took out their ready-made lunches from their bags. As a primary schooler, it would've been way too tough to have them find food out in the wilds.

Some of the teachers were guarding the outer boundaries of the forest, and the rest of them brought the children along for preparatory works.

The so-called picnic was actually bringing ready-made food from home to be eaten in the forest….

Garen found a shady area to lay out his own white tablecloth, beside him was Serin who wore a white skirt and had a left ponytail tied. She always liked to follow Garen around at all times with shimmering eyes.

Sandwiches with roasted meat, corn-mixed vegetable salads, canned fish, canned fruit, little bear-shaped biscuit, sandwich jam with toffee... Each of them was taken out from Garen's bag and were placed on the tablecloth.

"Can we be a group?" His classmate since kindergarten, Serin came over and squatted in front of Garen's tablecloth, she looked at her own pitiful two-piece sandwich and fruit juice, and looked at Garen's awfully scrumptious preparation, her tender face almost couldn't contain her drooling.

"Eeleen, then let the three of us form a group." Garen nodded without being bothered. Actually, it was the same, be it two or three people. Compared to those naughty kids, Eeleen liked to nap more compared to the rest, while Serin was quiet.

Of course, there was another reason, it was that these two Lolitas turned out cute and tender, even though he didn't know how they would look like when they grew older, the kid version right now looked very cute. Just that, in comparison, Serin's skin was better, while Eeleen was slightly darker, a little bit scrawny, maybe due to malnutrition.

All the good food on the tablecloths made the kids surrounding them distracted, and have glared in their direction.

The kids in town rarely had that many delicacies. As there wasn't much interaction with the outside world, there were many ingredients that were hard to find. These snacks and sweets were bought by Trish and Emmer during their occasional trips home from college. Of course, these things were way beyond any child's imagination, as most of the things could only be observed from the front of the television.

Just the toffee alone had 5 brands, it was exceptionally luxurious.

To be honest, Garen didn't like these, but a kid should have a kid's mannerisms, so he didn't prepare anything else.

Sitting on the grassland, the shade was obviously more cooling. As the sunlight brightened, the grassland was baked in golden rays, and it got warmer.

Chapter 573: Strange 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was that independent kid who did not need tender loving care in the class, who also consistently churned out good grades. The most teachers did were just occasional glances, to make sure he was safe.

Sitting on the grassland, he watched the two lolitas greedily munching on the snacks, Garen reclined against the tree in boredom, completely disregarding his own white shirt and jeans’ cleanliness.

Suddenly, an ice cold cylindrical object lightly caressed his right arm.

"Hmm?" Garen glanced down, it was a small snake.

A black snake with a yellow plaid pattern, with a length of about a palm.

"Ahh!" suddenly, a primary school boy screamed. "A snake! Teacher, there’s a snake!"

That little boy cried out with his nose dripping, as he crawled and rolled away from his own tablecloth. The students around him also gradually drew away from the area.

Both of the more experienced teachers were shocked as well, and they immediately approached Garen carefully.

"It’s a Ghastly Snake! Oh God, how can there be such venomous snakes around?!" One teacher immediately identified this snake.

The Ghastly Snake was impeccably venomous; any adults who were bitten would die within 10 minutes from their heart numbing if no antivenom was administered on time, nevermind a grade schooler aged 7-8 years old. Once they were bitten, who knew what would happen.

A few teachers were unable to conceal their horrified emotions.

After a while, another Ghastly Snake showed up on a different branch, scaring the students into an even more chaotic state of panic.

There were two now, and soon, a third snake appeared as well. It was another kind of snake, which was also highly venomous.

Little Serin who was next to Garen had turned pale from fright, whereas Eeleen was less afraid and was staring at the venomous snake attentively.

Garen frowned, and he looked up at the tree he was leaning upon.

Among the branches tucked away in the dark, there was another Ghastly Snake, furthermore, this snake was much larger in terms of girth and close to the length of a forearm.

The triangular eyes of the snake gazed coldly at Garen. This snake which had the widest girth was not discovered by others aside from Garen, but it was just a matter of time.

At this point, multiple snakes had already surrounded the primary schoolers, gradually appearing and growing into tens of them.

Some teachers had begun calling the security squad and their faces had all paled, unsure of what to do. Now it wasn’t just the students who were in danger, even they themselves were in trouble.

Garen frowned and with a change of gaze, he glared at the largest venomous snake.

Unknowingly, a cold breath seeped towards the snake and touched its body.

Hiss…..

This venomous snake shuddered, and as though it met its nemesis, it turned around and fled immediately.

In that instant, all the venomous snakes surrounding them fled into the forest, as though they had never appeared.

"Aura?" Garen did not anticipate this, that with an intent, the Heart of Frost which had reached its peak long ago actually made a breakthrough to the second realm of Sethe; Yin Coldness’ Hand.

What surprised him the most was that his Standard 2 body could exude Aura already.

Aura was the combination of the mental and spiritual energy, and as he’d always had overbearing spirit but lacking mental energy, it resulted in an obnoxiously weak body which could not activate Aura.

With this breakthrough to level 2, he could finally directly activate his Aura. It was a pleasant surprise.

However… This congregation of snakes made him wary, as these snakes would not venture into human territory without reason.

He carefully looked around, but all the venomous snakes seemed to have fled along the largest snake.

They did not harm any of the kids, other than giving them a huge scare.

Suspicious, Garen began observing the kids and teachers carefully when he suddenly realized that there was a girl with platinum-colored hair staring in the direction where the snakes fled with a petrified expression. She stood close to Garen, completely stunned, while she wore a white skirt that was smudged with green juice from the grass.

This girl was different from the rest, she didn’t look only terrified of the venomous snakes, she even had some unknown complex mixed feelings.

The regular kids had relaxed as soon as they saw the snakes retreating. Aside from the few who cried from the shock; the rest had begun regulating their emotions. But this girl didn’t, she seemed to have felt even more frightened by their absence.

Garen made a mental note about this girl.

This picnic was abruptly ended, as the teachers were afraid of further incidents. They were sent back to their school as soon as possible.

Garen also had a strange wariness of this picnic... This world appeared to be more complicated than he thought.

**************************

The Northern area of the town.

In a large, white steeple church.

In the large well-lit church, devout couples could be seen praying in the pews.

Vagar, a pastor in a white robe, stood in front of the podium, murmuring to a pale, muscular young man.

"Your people have been a little too active."

"Only a small disciplining, it’s just a traitor."

The man snickered and laughed without a care.

He has a strong physique and he wore a shirt that bared his chest, showing off glistening chest muscles. A metal belt was looped around his waist while a diamond earring adorned one ear, and his white handsome face was mysterious and wickedly charming.

"The mayor sent his words that you should tone down, they have been dissatisfied with your recent actions." the pastor whispered, while he made some actions similar to a prayer.

"No worries, hasn’t the issue been resolved? This is just a small incident." The man bowed his head while the pastor drizzled holy water over him.

"I sure hope so." the pastor nodded.

After the man was drizzled with holy water, he drew a cross sign on his chest out of devotion, and then murmured a few sentences of prayers. He turned around and left the podium towards a pew for a seat.

Soon, someone sat next to him and spoke to him softly.

The man suddenly frowned.

"Those troublesome women…" he looked into the air, as though he was thinking.

After a while, he tapped the shoulder of the man next to him.

"Were there any outsiders coming in recently?"

"The foot traffic wasn’t high, but most of them were tourists."

"They only drove the snakes away?"

"Yes, it seemed like a threat, or showing some sort of attitude to others." The subordinate replied softly.

"Get someone to warn them. Following the agreement, the first to disobey the rules will be punished." The man said emotionlessly.

"Okay."

"I do not wish to see Grano’s peaceful reputation to be tarnished by them. After all, we do receive a sizable portion of tourism income every year." The man shook his head as he muttered.

"But Leader, these women have recently become more radical, what if…." The man’s subordinate asked reservedly.

"Then we catch a few of their men, and deal with them as usual." The man’s eyes narrowed coldly.

********************************

The class was rowdy; the grade schoolers ran about while chattering away, and the teacher was busy reading books on their own.

The evening light glowed through the windows, warming the room.

Garen’s table was surrounded by a few classmates. Each of them was concentrating on the Rubik's cube in his hands. The three-by-three cube was played like a magic trick in his hands, and he managed to get all the sides to the same color in less than a minute. And then Garen would mess it up again to repeat the entire process.

The children would let out some surprised exclamations from time to time.

Most of the children in the class were from the town and they were not very well-dressed, with grey, red and black hues being the majority. There also weren’t many fancy accessories or good looking hairstyles, as they all dressed simply.

In their eyes, Garen’s tender white skin and shiny golden hair, such a doll-like boy was as eye-catching as a television star. It was rumored that he knew how to play the violin, and even how to use a computer to surf online. Such rumors were unintentionally spread from Serin, making Garen a legendary character in the class.

Even the few strongest and jumpiest boys in the class dared not offend him, even though he looked weak and soft. But for an unknown reason, he felt very strong.

"That girl over there, do you know her name? Garen glanced at the platinum-colored hair girl at the corner of the classroom while playing with the Rubik’s cube.

That girl was the one who had reacted strangely during the venomous snake incident. She was no beauty; she was scrawny and had an unhealthy skin tone, one that indicated a lack of exposure towards sunlight.

After a buffer period of several days, Garen suddenly recalled the event that day, so he asked away while there were many classmates around him.

"I think she's called Syves." One child answered.

"She's Syves Latin, I heard that her mother passed away a few days ago, I think she was drowned to death."

With this reply, the surrounding children quietened. They were not even ten-years-olds yet they were discussing mature topics, and it was even on matters such as death, which was rather frightening.

"It happened after our picnic?" A voice next to Garen cried out suddenly.

"Eh?" A flicker of suspicion crossed Garen’s mind.

"Let’s stop, she has it bad enough," Serin called out in dissatisfaction.

"Garen, don’t offend Syves, she’s weird." A cute girl who was near Garen spoke softly. In her eyes were unadulterated admiration, perhaps she didn't know anything about restraint.

"Weird? How so?" Garen asked.

"She doesn’t like to play with everyone, plus, she talked back to the teacher. I heard that she was even kidnapped once, and is no longer a good girl." she murmured softly.

"Stop yapping." Serin stood up abruptly from the side and glared at the other girl.

The girl was frightened by the aura let off by Serin, and she bit her lip while glancing at Garen. She felt that she couldn’t afford to lose her reputation in front of the boy she adored, hence even though she was terrified, she let out a hmph and left.

The kids around them were also taken aback by this and dispersed.

Chapter 574: Strange 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Why were you so feisty, Serin?" Once again, Garen gently nudged Serin to sit down.

"Nothing, I just thought that it’s not right to talk behind someone’s back." Little Serin replied with a huff.

Garen suddenly felt a little strange; Serin had always been nice since their childhood, but as they grew up, Serin slowly began having her own opinions.

Even Eeleen was the same. Also, a few girls in the class were the same and had become very proactive, as though they’d matured over a short period.

Comparatively, the boys were much slower to mature. Aside from the two boys who were the most active, the other boys actually seemed to be submissive. Sometimes, they were even frequently bullied by the girls.

This phenomenon was utterly absurd.

Garen’s couldn’t help but glance over at the weird girl with platinum-colored hair.

"Syves Latin?"

After the incident with the venomous snakes, the school had slowly returned to a peaceful state.

Standard 2 soon ended uneventfully, and Standards 3, 4, and 5 without any major incidents. There were no anomalies that happened again. Garen’s violin skills had improved tremendously, but following the greater mastery of the Black Sethe Claw, he occasionally lost control during his violin practice and that bone-chilling aura would leak into his music.

The third child, Garen’s sister Vivien, had also finally been enrolled in primary school, and she proudly became a member of the primary school.

Standard 5 was the time when one would graduate to the next tier of education, but to everyone, it was an undeniable fact that Garen would qualify for the only junior high in the town.

As the matter of fact, this place should be called Standards 6, 7, 8.

Tick…

The bell for recess had rung.

Garen, who was now about 1.5 meters tall, stood up and began packing his notebooks into his backpack.

Following the end of the final year examinations, the straight A’s on his report made the teachers smile from ear-to-ear. As his graduation approached, the teachers prepared a dinner, with the finale being Garen’s violin play.

The twelve-year-old Garen now looked physically close to perfection. Unlike his past life, he now boasted a slender, well-balanced body, bright golden hair and his face had a hint of gender-neutrality. As he immersed himself in music all year round, he now exuded a mysterious femininity.

He was very polite in his daily engagements too; with a kind temperament, Garen soon became one of the top two popular boys in his class.

As for the most famous boy, Jimmy was a handsome boy with a strong physique and amazing athletic abilities. Garen had observed him from afar before, noting that this person has a healthy charm and a wild personality. He excelled in basketball, football and baseball, and had even been appointed the head of the school’s PE department. With a skin tone slightly darker than wheat, he was wildly popular among the girls.

"Hey Garen, shall we go home together?" Serin and Eeleen came by in pairs, the trios were best friends who have grown up together.

Serin was dressed in a red T-shirt and washed out bell bottom jeans and was about Garen’s height. Her fair and lovely face seemed a little rougher nowadays, as the pores became pronounced. However, her black pixie cut matched her handsome facial look, which was rather tomboyish at times.

Eeleen, on the other hand, had become much prettier, she’d gone to dye her hair one random day, and her previously black hair was now a lovely hue of burgundy. Moreover, her hair had become silkier, and one could even see the individual strands of her hair when the lighting in the room was good.

Eeleen had a stereotypical Asian look and was completely different from Serin’s Caucasian appearance. As both of them grew older, Eeleen now stood about 1.4 meters, and her skin condition was much better as compared to her childhood as her skin’s texture had smoothened, and her eyes were like a pair of crescent moons when she laughed. She was comparable to the two most beautiful girls in the class and was one of the most typical crushes among the boys.

Aside from the differences in their physical appearance, Eeleen’s personality was very similar to Serin's. She was slowly becoming more independent and opinionated, and when they were met with issues or conflicts, they might even brawl it out.

"Is there anything more important than the final graduation dinner?" Serin snickered while covering her mouth.

Just as the three of them walked out of the classroom and were descending to the second floor, a voice suddenly called out to Garen.

"Garen, could you wait for a moment?" a group of upperclassmen girls appeared behind them.

The three of them turned around. The leader of the group was a girl with shoulder-length hair and silky smooth skin. Although she looked slightly snobbish, her tall body had appropriate womanly curves, probably a student from the junior high Standard 6 class. It was apparent that this girl was confident in her body, as she wore a white skin tight tee as well as figure-hugging white jeans, showing off her perfect figure. A pair of brown leather boots gave out loud clear thumps with every step.

The students who were passing by started to slow down when they noticed that there was some juicy drama waiting to happen, they lingered with interest in the 2 groups, waiting to see what would happen.

"I am Raffaele." the upperclassmen proudly swept her voluminous hair back, while her boots thudded with every step she took towards Garen. "I have observed you for a long time, Garen. Why don’t you become my boyfriend? Aren’t you bored of being together with these two underdeveloped brats?"

She puffed out her chest in a seductive manner. The fourteen, fifteen-year-old had already learned the ways to exhibit her body’s charm.

Garen was taken aback. Even though there were girls who wrote him love letters, they no longer approached him if he didn’t reply to them, but it was certainly a first to him, for a girl to be this brazen and confessing to him in public.

Deep inside, he was still a conservative Eastern man, and to suddenly encounter events like a public confession from girls, he couldn’t help but be shocked.

Just as he snapped back to reality and was prepared to reply, two silhouettes suddenly walked past him and blocked his path.

"Who did you refer to as ‘underdeveloped’?"

Serin’s face turned cold.

"Raffaele Dockman, I know you, Class 2 Standard 6, are you here for trouble?"

"Two tomboys, having absolutely no femininity, do you think Garen would like people like you two?" Raffaele sneered as she crossed her arms.

The girls behind her began snickering too.

"Only our lady boss is fit for Garen, the two of you are better off blending in among the lowerclassmen, you’re sorely lacking in both breasts and butts."

"Our lady boss is the boss beyond the Standard 6, how dare you oppose her?"

"They are children, after all, it’s normal to think that they would be of the same class after graduation, we have to be considerate and forgive their silliness."

That group of girls started chattering and laughed non-stop.

Serin chuckled coldly for a moment.

"Are you all made of only mouths?"

She clenched her fists, which let out a crisp crack. Her expression turned darkened, and she was unusually angry.

In actual fact, both Serin and Eeleen had secretly liked Garen for a long time. It was just that Eeleen had become more beautiful while she only became worse, and as they grew older, this gap only became wider. Serin then buried her affection in order to encourage Eeleen to be with Garen, it felt like the two of them had become more compatible with each other, but now, an outsider had appeared, with the intentions of ripping apart their friendships.

Garen frowned; in his eyes, this was all but a childish drama, but as he realized that her words were a bit too offensive and that Serin and Eeleen might have been hurt, he moved his body slightly in order to stand out to talk.

"Don’t you dare meddle in!" Serin suddenly blocked him, "This is an issue among us girls, just sit back and be quiet." She sounded determined with no hesitation in her tone.

Garen gazed at her and Eeleen beside her. Their eyes held a firm determination and sincerity and clearly, they didn’t want him to mediate this disagreement.

"Very well."

He no longer resisted while he nodded slightly. Kids have to face these difficulties eventually in life, as this was a part of growing up.

"How do you want to do this?" Raffaele began laughing and folded her sleeves, showing her fair, slender arms, "One-on-one?"

"Don’t even bother us again if we win!" Serin began to flex her shoulders.

"Let me do this, you take on the other people." Eeleen took a step forward and spoke in a low voice.

"Okay." Serin’s dad was the squad leader of security, so she’d learned many combat techniques from her dad. It wasn’t her first couple of times in a brawl either. "Do you remember the techniques I taught you?"

"Yeah." Eeleen nodded.

The two girls took their stance and were prepared to fight.

"Right here?" Raffaele frowned as she looked at the crowding spectators. "Let’s change the venue, it wouldn’t be fun if the teachers come over."

"The grove of trees behind," Eeleen said impassively.

"Sure."

The two groups then walked down the stairs, they stormed off to the grove behind the school with a strangely grim vibe.

"I was saying…" Garen was speechless, he’d a small suspicion after he started primary school, but he didn’t expect that these indicators had begun to exacerbate and become more obvious.

The townspeople of this place were disproportionately female and here, the women took up the role of breadwinner. The women were also the ones who resolved conflicts, and this phenomenon was not unique to the schools, he’d also observed similar experiences outside.

Aside from working outside, women took charge of most of the similar issues. The patriarchy system of the outside world seemed to be reversed here,

Just like now.

Two gangs of girls prepared to fight it out over a boy, "See you at the grove after school." Wasn’t that what boys would say?

If it was the outside world, the situation would be the inverse. Two groups of men fighting for a girl, that would be the logical way…

To be a protagonist being fought over, Garen felt weird, but Serin insisted that he didn’t follow, it’s a woman’s matter and men should stand aside.

It didn’t feel logical no matter how he looked at it.

Speaking of which, he didn’t have any heterosexual attraction towards any of those girls, he was an old man inside, after all, if he was attracted to these kids, then he was truly twisted inside. Of course, this was related to the fact that Serin and Eeleen were slow to grow. If it were to be Raffaele’s figure, it would have been normal to have some lust and react to the body’s natural reaction at this age. Otherwise, he would have to assess if this body had any issues.

Chapter 575: Strange 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

But in comparison, Garen was still much closer to Serin and Eeleen. After all, he had been so familiar with them for so long, making them friends at the very least, so he should still go check them out.

As he thought that, Garen could not resist but walk towards the direction that they had left in. On the way, however, he encountered two girls who seemed to be there specifically to block his way.

"Big Sis Raffaele doesn’t want you going there." One of the larger girls growled at him, she was much larger in size than Garen.

Garen looked into the distant woods, but could only see a sea of pitch black.

Soon he would need to prepare for the event at night too, so he just shook his head, turned around and left anyway. In any case, elementary school and junior high students would not harbor any deep grudges, and even if they fought, there probably should not be any accidents.

****************

The beautiful music of the violin slowly rang out on the stage.

Garen wore a small white suit, raising his violin and playing it with his eyes slightly closed, he needed to work hard to control the sound, so that it sounded normal, if he really played as he wanted, that creepy aura from before would appear again.

In the hall, all he could see was a sea of black, eighty or ninety percent of the school’s students and teachers were here.

Serin, Eeleen, and Raffaele's group were there too, Serin looked somewhat depressed, her neck all red, while Raffaele was completely unharmed, so the result was evident.

Garen put his violin down lightly, and bowed towards the bottom of the stage. There was an instant wave of thunderous applause.

He turned around and walked off the stage, hearing the emcee speak on-stage, but that already had nothing to do with him.

Once he got off the stage, he had not even changed out of his clothes before he saw Raffaele standing beside the stage, waiting for him to come down. She was even surrounded by some curious students.

"Good work, Garen, come have a drink." Raffaele greeted him with a seductive smile, handing him a wet towel and a bottle of mineral water.

Garen glanced at Serin who was nearby, she was also walking towards him, but seeing that Raffaele was there, she actually stopped walking, clenching her teeth as she waited there.

"What happened between the two of you?" he asked, frowning.

"Nothing really." The smile on Rafaelle's face sank, but after a pause, she smiled again, still that calm, proudly appreciative smile. "Do you want to walk with me? Just the two of us."

Garen ignored her, walking right up to Serin and Eeleen, Eeleen even had a fresh scratch on her face.

He looked at the two of them exasperatedly, and quietly told them a few things, asking them if they wanted to go back with him. By then, the students in the audience were already beginning to scatter.

Some of the students that had come over to call the three of them sensed something amiss in the atmosphere, and there was still the stone-faced Raffaele and crew, so the newcomers instantly fell silent, and had no idea what to do.

Garen was surprised to find that Serin and Eeleen had lost, and were refusing point-blank to go back with him, what was up with that expression that said ‘since we lost, we need to admit it’?

Watching Serin and Eeleen leave the crowd by themselves, Garen’s feelings got a little out of pace, are all the kids nowadays so self-determined?

"Now there’s no one left to disturb us, right?" Raffaele said with a triumphant smile. She very naturally hugged Garen’s arm, lightly leaning her well-developed chest onto him.

Garen felt like he had a headache coming on, and decided he was too lazy to bother with these little kids’ problems, things would probably go back to normal soon enough.

He glanced at Raffaele next to him, she had shoulder-length golden hair, a seductive face, smooth skin, long and slender legs, as well as her supple breasts pressed tightly against his arm, but he could smell a faint virgin fragrance in his nostrils.

He could tell that Raffaele’s actions were making even herself slightly nervous.

The people around them were already noticing the movements here, and there was the occasional whistle.

Raffaele picked up Garen’s hand and put it around her tiny waist, she was very confident in her own figure, leaning her entire body onto Garen’s, her face flushing pink.

"Don’t you like me?" She reached her face closer, so that their lips were almost touching. "Am I not sexy enough?"

"Although I won’t exactly look a gift horse in the mouth, but you gotta at least let me know, exactly what do you like about me?" Garen asked exasperatedly. He knew that he did not really communicate with the others except for how he chatted with Serin and Eeleen sometimes.

"I just like you, do I need a reason?" Raffaele retorted, "I want you to become my man."

Garen opened his mouth, but did not know what to say.

"Even if I can’t get your heart, I want your body," Raffaele said forcefully.

Uhh…

Why did that sound so familiar?

Wasn’t that something men usually said to women?

Garen was feeling rather confused, there really was something wrong with the trends in this town…

Raffaele dragged Garen everywhere and showed him off to all her friends, not just her girl friends, but even some of the other girls and schoolmates in the school were beginning to raise a commotion.

After the ball ended, Raffaele sent away everyone else and offered to send Garen back.

On the way back, neither of them said anything, they just advanced forward quietly.

It was only when they could vaguely see Garen’s double-story house ahead, that Raffaele finally stopped walking.

"Tomorrow I’ll come get you, just wait at home like a good boy, okay?" She approached Garen, temptingly letting her twin peaks brush against Garen’s chest.

"If you listen to me, I can give you a little incentive~~~"

"We’re so soon, does this count as puppy love?" Garen asked, somewhat flabbergasted. "Although I don’t dislike you, I’ll still be with Serin and Eeleen tomorrow. So you don’t need to come get me…"

"They won’t come." Raffaele laughed, "The competition between us has already decided everything, this is a battle between w...women, no one can break an ancient oath like that."

When she mentioned the ancient oath, there was a looming and strange feeling in her eyes.

This got Garen’s alarms ringing slightly, it seemed that the duel was not just a skirmish between kids as he had first thought.

"You are already mine," Raffaele stressed again. "Even if you don’t choose me, they can’t break the vow and approach you."

"That’s why I hate presumptuous kids who act like adults the most…" Garen felt a headache coming on.

"Aren’t you a kid as well?" Raffaele could not help but laugh. She reached over her soft hand to touch Garen’s neck, and then left as fast as the wind, disappearing into the night in an instant.

"See you tomorrow."

A clear voice came from the distance.

Garen watched Raffaele leave speechlessly, shook his head, and walked towards his own little home.

"Mom, I’m back!"

Opening the door, Garen changed out of his shoes and walked inside, closing the door behind him.

"There’s cream of corn soup in the microwave, I added some black mushrooms, go heat it up yourself." His mother Trish’s voice came from the study, she was evidently hard at work again, recently she was writing a research paper, and hid in her room all day. She never left her computer once she sat down in front of it, and even most of the house chores were left up to his father Emmer recently, all she did was occasionally make her children some nourishing soups.

"Got it."

Garen threw down his bag and violin case, putting them back in his own room, and he saw that the door to his brother Jason’s room opposite his was wide open, Jason himself was sprawled on his bed, reading a book.

"Jason, do you know Raffaele? She’s an upperclassman."

"Raffaele?" Jason turned around, he was already in high school and almost as tall as his father, having undergone a growth spurt, his room was covered in posters of boxers and the King of Boxing, each poster full of muscles and sweat.

His dream was to become a great boxer, in other words, the legendary King of Boxing. Perhaps Garen had contributed in part to this dream as well, having grown up with countless beatings at the hands of his little brother, Jason had always had an almost perverse craving for strength, he trained his muscles every day, increasing the power of his boxing.

"I know, Raffaele Dockman, right, she’s a huge force in the school, pretty, confident, proud, she and her people have dominated the school’s changing room, tennis club, music club, about a third of the territory there, she sets the rules in those places, and is a very forceful kind of girl." Jason turned around and glanced at his younger brother, "Why are you asking about her suddenly?"

"Big Brother~~~" Their little sister Vivien ran over to them with a spring in her step, and threw herself into Garen’s embrace, the little fella had inherited their mother’s good genes. She was already in third grade, and looked like a pretty little loli, unnaturally adorable in her small white nightdress, her long golden hair let loose, her huge eyes blinking, and her little mouth pouting.

"Big Bro, you look so handsome in this outfit!"

His little sister gave Garen a thumbs-up and a huge grin.

"Was the performance a success?"

"Since Vivien helped me rehearse, of course, it was successful." Garen reached out his hand to pinch his younger sister’s cheeks, those fair and puffy cheeks were his favorite place to pinch, he yanked them here and there, appreciating their texture.

"I drew your portrait in art class today, do you wanna see it?" Little Vivien looked at Garen expectantly.

"Of course I do."

So the night passed quickly with all of his sister’s shenanigans, Garen slept very early, and he did not even know when his old pops who had gone out for a survey returned.

After completing his routine secret technique training, he soon fell asleep, and it felt like the first time he had slept so well.

The second level of the Insidious Poison Hand was truly focused on building up Insidious power, to the point where it could be used on the enemy. He could also gather up all the poisonous substances in his body in one place, turning it into Insidious power, a side effect of that being a better quality of sleep for Garen himself.

The only thing Garen was not satisfied with was the speed of advancement in this level of his secret technique, it had already taken him so long to reach the second level, but he was still stuck here after all this time. Although he could feel himself making progress, it was simply too slow. If he continued training according to this speed, he would need at least several years to reach the third level. The time required for every level of the Black Sethe Secret Technique increased proportionally, Garen’s own talent had already drastically decreased the time needed, but even if he did decrease it, it would still mean he could only reach the third level when he turned twenty, and who knows how long it would take to reach the fourth level.

There was only one way to solve this problem -- potential points.

Chapter 576: Strange 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He had to find something that could increase his attribute talent’s potential points, that was the only way to reduce the training time. It was just that Garen had no idea how to go about it at all, all these years, he had already learned about many sorts of ancient items, but he had not sensed a hint of potential power in any of them.

He had also tried secretly killing wild animals, like snakes or wolves, but to no effect. This made him reconsider his thoughts, he might have made a mistake in his conjectures about the source of potential points.

If the source of potential points was merely the mysterious power of Antiques of Tragedy, then in the subsequent Totem World, killing should not have been able to increase his potential points as well.

But in the Totem World, be it killing totem users or Aberrated creatures, each of them gave him a substantial amount of potential points, so that was strange.

The conclusion Garen came to, was that he should make more attempts based on soul power.

This is because the upper limit to his attribute-increasing power was the power of his soul, just as how the Evil Technique Soul Seed deep in his soul would increase the limits of his attributes slightly every year. Ever since he was born up until now, his limits had far surpassed his attribute limits from before, and was now at thirty points. It was terrifying to have an average upper limit of thirty points, but the modification power of the Soul was not limitless either, after he went from the twenty points to thirty, it had gone utterly quiet, that modification power and effect was still there, but it had stopped strengthening his soul and upper limit.

This meant that the power of the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique could only modify this body to an excess limit of thirty points.

Since the thing increasing his attributes’ upper limits was the power of his soul, then in order to obtain attribute potential points so he can progress to the next level, he should probably need something related to the soul as well.

Thinking of the special tragedy effect of the Antiques of Tragedy, and then thinking of the unique qualities of totem users with their totem power, Garen vaguely felt that his general direction of study should have something to do with the soul.

But this world was still an unknown place to him even now, he had yet to see even a natural phenomenon that seemed to show unnatural power, much less something to do with the field of the soul, which was considered higher class even among the unnatural.

Waking up feeling refreshed, Garen sat up, and pulled away the covers. He picked up the cool drinking water by his bedside and gulped straight from it, drinking a cup of plain water in the morning helped to wash out the toxins in the body.

After getting out of bed, he walked up to the window, and pulled apart the pale yellow curtains with a whoosh.

"Hey!!" On the clean white streets below, a pretty girl riding a bicycle was waving at him. It was Raffaele!

She had changed into a white sleeveless T-shirt, and was wearing the same bleached jeans from yesterday, riding her bike as she smiled at Garen, waving. Her fair and supple skin reflected the glaring white light under the sun, add that to her similarly golden hair, and it seemed as though Raffaele’s whole person was glowing.

"Hurry up, Garen!" She seemed to be worried that everyone around them could not hear her, her voice unnaturally loud.

Garen walked out of his bedroom, feeling confused, and saw Jason was also walking out with his messy golden hair opposite him, evidently frustrated by Raffaele’s shocking actions as well.

"Is this why you asked me yesterday?" He glanced at his younger brother, feeling extremely emotional. "That girl has been waiting down there since half an hour ago…"

Garen was speechless.

As they ate their breakfast, their father gave Garen a big thumbs-up, his gaze encouraging, and he grinned happily, looking just like their little sister Vivien. As expected, their little sister had picked up this ugly habit from him.

Their mother Trish had even gotten up and was about to invite Raffaele into the house to have breakfast with them, but Garen rejected that hurriedly. He drank his milk, hastily polished off his fruit and vegetable salad, took two more slices of toast from the toaster, and rushed out of the door, just in time to see Raffaele smiling dazzlingly as she waited by the road on her bike, chatting with an aunty from the neighborhood.

"Kiddo, what’s your relationship with lil’ Garen? You sure came here early to wait for him."

"I… I’m his… you know…" Raffaele lowered her head shyly, a blush rising in her cheeks.

"What am I supposed to know? Wait, could you two be…" Aunty had a vivid imagination, and was instantly surprised.

"That’s right…"

"You’re so young, you have to take care of your body." Aunty was in disbelief, "Have you two really done that? That thing?"

Raffaele lowered her head in embarrassment.

Garen walked up to them speechlessly, if they spoke any more the misunderstanding would worsen, Raffaele clearly had an ulterior motive.

The neighborhood aunty greeted Garen smilingly, and left in a hurry, claiming that she did not want to get in their way.

"I’ll take you, hop on." Raffaele smiled at Garen cheerfully.

Garen looked left and right, usually he should be able to see Serin and Eeleen now, but neither of them was anywhere to be seen. He had no choice but to reconsider what that so-called oath did.

"Alright." Garen let out of a breath, and took the bicycle’s back seat.

"Hold my waist, be careful not to fall."

"It’s okay, you just go ahead, I’m stable here." Garen replied off-handedly.

"Alright then."

Raffaele did not say anything more, and stepped down hard on the pedal, making the bike shoot forward abruptly.

The entire way there, she pedaled with all her might, making the bike go faster and faster, faster and faster, if it was anyone else under these circumstances, they would have long since gone pale with fright.

Why isn’t Garen holding my waist?

Raffaele thought with her ulterior motive, and turned around to glance at Garen, but he had actually fallen asleep. No matter how the bike swayed, he just sat there, perfectly balanced and sound asleep.

"This guy…" Raffaele was helpless.

They went past the few streets in no time, and soon they had arrived at the school.

The bike stopped at the school gates with a screech, and Garen opened his eyes, waking up as if on cue.

The two of them dismounted separately.

"Oh yeah, Garen, do you remember our promise from yesterday?" Raffaele spoke suddenly.

"You mean the reward?" Garen raised his eyebrows.

"This is for you." Raffaele suddenly stuffed something small and round at him, it felt cool in his palm.

Garen raised his hand to look at it, it was an ancient black-silver badge, there was the image of a buck on it, and most of the carvings at the sides had been rubbed away, as though it had spent a lot of time in someone else’s hand.

"What is this?"

"My grandma gave it to me, it was passed down from before, don’t lose it, ‘kay?" Raffaele said with a smile, and then, surrounded by her many underlings, she pushed the bike away from where they stood.

Garen stood at the school gates, his expression slightly strange as he looked at the buck badge in his hand.

Some wisps of familiar aura darted into his arm from the badge. It was just a little, of something he used to be extremely familiar with.

"Potential points?!" Garen’s heart pounded heavily.

"No… This little bit of potential power can’t even form one potential point, it’s just a tiny bit of the energy left on it…" Garen glanced at his attribute pane, the pane for his potential points jumped a bit, and blurred ever so slightly from 0%, but that was all.

That little bit of energy from before could only make his potential point value blink slightly.

"This is… an Antique of Tragedy?" Garen picked up the buck badge.

Throughout class that morning, he constantly played with his buck badge, and noticed that when two of the girls saw the badge in his hand, their eyes sparkled somewhat.

These junior high students obviously seemed to know how to hide things better than elementary schoolers, but compared to an adult like Garen, they naturally could not hide anything.

"Or maybe this thing also has some special meaning?" He caressed the badge as he mused.

He noticed that Serin and Eeleen were sitting at the other far end of the classroom, but their gazes drifted over now and then, glancing at him, and then quickly moving away.

"Garen, could I ask you how to solve this?" During recess, the boy behind him patted Garen’s back, and passed him a little notebook with math questions.

Garen took it, explaining the question to the boy as he watched Serin’s and Eeleen’s movements.

The more he thought about it, the more he felt something off with that ancient oath, in his eyes, it was supposed to be just a minor conflict between girls, but he had not expected such a surprising outcome.

Just then Garem saw Raffaele standing at the classroom door, dressed up all pretty, smiling as she chatted with one of her besties, their voices extremely low, as though whispering.

Right now almost everyone knew that Raffaele and Garen had a relationship going on, even the male teacher who was packing his things and leaving the room gave Garen a mischievous look.

Raffaele chatted quietly with her bestie, in a voice only the two of them could hear, nobody knew what they were saying, but they laughed together happily.

They waited until all of the students had more or less left for lunch.

Raffaele pushed away her friend, and walked into the classroom alone, going up to Garen’s desk.

"Come, let’s have lunch together, I prepared some good food especially for you."

Garen glanced at Serin and Eeleen again, they were talking among themselves there, not meeting his gaze at all.

"Alright." He had already sensed something amiss, and decided to look into the mysteries here properly, plus the strange and ancient trend of having active girls and passive boys in this town, all of the things hidden here were piquing his interest.

The two of them got up and walked out of the classroom, Garen practically being pulled forward by Raffaele.

"That thing you just gave me was pretty good, I really like it."

"I just knew you would like it, I remember you used to really like antiques." Raffaele laughed as she replied, "Don’t think I was joking before, I really did pay attention to you since a long time ago, even my grandma has approved of our relationship."

"Hah? Your grandma?" Garen felt as though his reaction was slightly delayed, "Isn’t this development a little too fast?"

"Fast? How so? If you like ‘em, get ‘em! Do what you want to do! Whether it’s fast or slow, what’s the point of comparing yourself with others?" Raffaele replied with disdain, "That was the principle my grandma told me since I was young, if I find something good, I gotta act fast, if I’m slow there won’t be anything left."

"Your grandma sure is… bold… haha…" Garen did not know how to comment, wasn’t her grandma worried that her granddaughter would come out of it badly?

Chapter 577: Secret 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the vast canteen, the silver metal tables and chairs were fixed to the ground and neatly arranged on the floor, the clean white walls around them were covered with pictures of ducklings, apples, and pears.

The students sat on the chairs in twos and threes, eating the food on the trays, while others were lining up at the canteen window to bring out their trays.

Garen and Raffaele sat opposite each other on the right end of a long table, the two of them eating the sandwiches on their respective trays, occasionally dipping them into the cheese sauce between them, drinking some of the tomato and potato beef stew.

There was a low buzzing around the canteen, the sound of many people talking reflecting around the empty canteen, mixed with echoes. It felt as though he could hear what they were saying, but after listening closely, all he could hear was a blur.

Garen raised his head and looked at Raffaele sitting opposite him.

"You haven’t answered my question from last time."

"What question?"

"What exactly do you like about me?" Garen picked up a piece of apple with his fork and put it into his mouth.

"Everything, probably…" Raffaele’s expression was completely open, "If I have to choose, it’s probably because you look good, so wouldn’t it be really cool when I bring you out?"

"....."

"Then what other reason do you want?" Raffaele shrugged.

Neither of them said anything more for some time.

Garen felt that this person was slightly strange, she was obviously a girl, but acted like a boy.

"Can you tell me what promise you made with Eeleen and Serin?"

"I can’t tell you that." Raffaele smiled, "But you just need to know that the power of the oath cannot be stopped. This is more than just me and them."

"Is that so?" Garen narrowed his eyes, thinking that he might have to go back and ask his parents about these secrets of the town. The two of them had lived here for so long, they might know some of the mysteries here, more or less.

This secret might very well involve his potential points problem.

"Let’s go play ball after eating, I have a girl friend waiting at the court for me, you can cheer me on then." Raffaele still acted as though all this was completely natural.

Garen wanted to know more about her too, to get into the secrets of the place, so he just nodded and did not refuse.

After eating, they went to the court for a game or two of basketball, and after class in the afternoon, Garen was escorted home by Raffaele, Raffaele insisted on sending him all the way home, just like how a boy would send his girlfriend all to way to the gate of her house.

At home, he played with Vivien, who kept calling him Big Bro adorably, and finally waited until his parents returned home one after the other.

In the study during the evening, Garen distracted his older brother and younger sister, sitting alone as he looked at his mother opposite him, her expression confused.

"Is there something up? You look so serious, just like a little adult." His mother Trish laughed, reaching out her hand to pinch Garen’s face. "Alright, did you get bullied at school?" She asked gently.

Shaking his head, Garen avoided his mother’s hand.

"Mom, I wanted to ask, is there some ancient traditional oath in this town, that you must obey after you promised to make it?"

"An oath?" Trish thought about it, perplexed, "It’s been many years since we moved here, true, there is something like a ritual here, only the locals will follow it, as outsiders who moved here, we’ve only heard it but haven’t actually seen it. They call it something like the Oath of the Ancestors."

"A ritual?"

"Mn, more or less, the locals treat it like a very formal and solemn thing, their ancestors are something that you must be careful around, you can’t even joke about it, if you swore at someone using their ancestors, for example, it might end up costing your life." His mother Trish told him straight-facedly. "Oh yeah, I hear a girl is pursuing you? And she’s really pretty to boot? Is that so?"

Seeing his mom’s face instantly turn mischievous, Garen also figured that he would not get any more information from her. After talking for so long, she had basically said nothing.

His mom’s expression seemed to really not know anymore, so he had to give up on her end.

After chatting idly with his mom for a bit longer, Garen left the room. He grabbed his computer notebook, a birthday present from his dad last year.

Hammering out a line of words on the keyboard, he entered a web address into the search engine.

There were many hits about oaths, so to reduce the range, he added a space and once more typed in America, Grano.

Smack.

He pressed the Enter button, and there were only five results left on the screen.

It was an oath from something like a religious ritual, four of them were local public ritual oaths, and one was the oath students made to the national flag, swearing to uphold the American spirit.

He read all the information about the religious rituals carefully, they were all public affairs, rituals that required many items in preparation beforehand, and they were either for the spring harvest or fishing, or an event for a holiday, with no other worth whatsoever.

Turning off the computer, Garen sat by his bed and mused. In this town, many of the women, especially the local women, all had a special common secret, a secret that was ancient, solemn, and one that everyone seemed to obey the rules to.

"Looks like the best way to get to the bottom of this is to use my relationship with Raffaele… once we get close enough, many secrets won’t be secrets anymore…"

His life after that did not change much from before, the only difference was that the two girls who had always stuck with him, Serin and Eeleen, became just one girl, Raffaele. Raffaele would run over here every day, precisely on time, to meet and send Garen to school, occasionally giving him some little presents, which were always decent old gadgets and little antiques. Garen wanted to chat up Serin and Eeleen several times, but they kept avoiding him, so he had no choice but to give up.

The days passed one after the other, and he slowly got used to Raffaele’s existence as well.

Sometimes he would give Raffaele some little items back, and their relationship began to grow warmer, like best friends but also like lovers.

To children like them, their completely unchanged lives passed by extremely fast.

Slowly, Eeleen and Serin gradually faded from Garen’s vision, and his relationship with Raffaele became better and better. He was never someone to approach others himself, pursuing his own target, so he had no time to get to know the people around him. But the type who approached him of their own accord, such as Raffaele, slowly became an exception for him.

There was not much difference between his junior high life and his elementary school life, the only thing was that the students grew up slightly faster, and their thought processes were slightly more mature.

Garen practiced his secret technique every day, but his power stayed on the second level, his progress was extremely slow, and he had subtly asked Raffaele about the buck badge several times, but every time she just said that she did not know, only her grandma would know more about it. This made Garen, who was basically stuck where he was, more and more curious.

*********************

On the bright blue sea, the golden-red waves of twilight kept rippling about.

A beach a hundred kilometers away from Grano.

On the pale yellow beach, a golden-haired boy in his early teens was walking slowly toward the ocean, wearing nothing but black swimming trunks, his clothes tossed far away on a black coral rock.

The boy had handsome features, with a hint of gentle androgyny, giving off a feeling of tender weakness. He was obviously a boy, but somehow he had a gentle beauty that made people want to protect him.

He walked toward the seawater slowly, step by step, his feet getting submerged, followed by his calves, then his knees, thigh, stomach, chest.

In an instant, wisps of ink-black mist extended from his body, spreading everywhere with the tide.

The mist was like ink, rapidly dying the water around the boy black.

The boy seemed completely oblivious to it, however, continuing to walk towards the depths of the sea.

Strangely, the seawater that had reached his chest did not go any higher than that, even as he left the shallows and walked towards the depths, the water level did not budge at all, reaching his chest and no further than that.

Whoosh!!

Suddenly, there was the rippling of waves on the surface of the sea nearby, and two triangular fins rushed toward the boy from the distance. Under the mixed blue surface, there were two large blue-black giant sharks, they swam towards the boy rapidly, their fins cutting through the waves like submarines, drawing out two lines of white waves behind them.

Just as the fins swam into the black water around the boy.

The boy’s weakness changed abruptly, his hands as pencil-straight as two sharp knives, stabbing down into the water hard.

Psst!

The two giant sharks exploded abruptly with two popping sounds, becoming two chunks of bloodied meat, the bloody water was quickly integrated into the black water territory around the boy, the color of bright blood quickly covered by the black, and then everything returned to the same peaceful scene at the very beginning.

Garen raised his hands, frowning.

"The progress is too slow…" He sighed.

The Black Claw of Sethe’s power had already achieved the same level as a Grandmaster of Combat, and his current body was already capable of just barely releasing his aura, so he had indeed recovered some of his power.

But the laws of this world are different, it seemed that he could no longer fully condense his aura, and even at his current state, he could only insert his aura into an item and then use that to influence other external objects, he could no longer simply release it as he used to, and overwhelm the enemy with it alone.

But this way, he merged his aura into the water, and into the air, turning it into something ordinary people could see as well, and not just something only for the eyes of Grandmasters of Combat. It was just that this required a lot of energy, and right now Garen could only sustain this aura release for ten minutes max, the area covered by his aura included a radius of about ten meters with him in the center, within these ten meters, any and all creatures that enter this area would be subjected to a terrifying psychological illusory pressure, while at the same time the materialized Black Sethe Insidious Palm Power would also seep into the enemy’s body together with his aura, slowly weakening the opponent’s vitality and speed.

Right now, rather than saying his aura was a product of the merging of his spirit, it was more like a pure poisonous gas released from Garen’s body. This poisonous gas had a powerful hallucinatory effect, and could even weaken the opponent’s vitality and speed, plus it was soluble in water.

"Garen! You went into the water again!" Far away on the beach, a slender golden-haired girl was waving at him hard. "Come up to shore, there’s something I want to tell you."

Garen turned around to look, it was Raffaele, he was very into training these days, so he would ride his motorbike to the beach for a swim every day after school, but in truth, he was practicing his application of the Black Sethe’s Insidious Palm Power.

This secret technique seemed to truly be an evil technique, it could actually absorb and dissolve the blood and flesh of other creatures, external blood and flesh even boosted his palm power significantly. Since randomly hunting and killing in the forest might attract unwanted attention, he decided to go further away, and ended up training here in the ocean, so no one actually noticed anything at all.

As an evil technique, the Black Sethe was unique in its poison and also its potent ability for camouflage, perhaps even Grandmasters of Combat at the same level as him would not be able to sense that Garen was using any secret technique power at all. That was also something Garen was extremely satisfied with.

Garen quickly pulled back the poisonous mist that had melted into the surrounding seawater, and turned around, heading back to shore.

His movements were extremely natural, the lines of his body unnaturally gentle, and with every stroke, his body would swim ahead quickly, like a fish.

Chapter 578: Secret 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He quickly went back to shore and accepted the dry towel Raffaele handed him. Ever since they got to know each other, in these past two years, they had gotten so close that there was nothing they could not tell each other. Of course, they still had their respective innermost secrets that remained hidden from each other, Garen could sense that, and he could tell that it was the same with Raffaele.

The Raffaele right now was no longer as childish as she used to be, in the past two years, she seemed to have undergone some special education, her thoughts becoming more and more mature, while her personality grew more and more aloof, other than Garen, she had fewer girl companions, and more underlings who looked up to her.

Before she knew it, her reputation among her peers became stronger and stronger, and now that she was in her first year of high school, she had already become the most powerful boss lady in the school.

Raffaele was wearing white swim clothes, her chest was still not very developed but small and delicate, peeking vaguely from beneath the swim clothes, her fair white arms, and smooth white long legs were her most eye-catching assets.

Her skin was unlike other girls, as she grew older, rather than growing coarse, her skin grew smoother and softer.

"There's something I need to handle at school, I need to go back guest." A trace of exhaustion flashed past Raffaele’s face, "You ride back on your own later, I won't send you then."

"No problem." Garen nodded, seeing the exhaustion on Raffaele’s face, it was her true face that she only showed him. "You're too tired, why don't you give that organization or whatnot to someone to handle, we're just students, we don't need to create an organization or summat to trouble ourselves."

"It's fine, I can do it." Raffaele waved her hand, she had always been a forceful kind of woman and was equally formidable. "It's just a minor problem, I can get it settled in no time."

She was just like a ferocious lioness, powerful, fierce, but also had her proud and beautiful side.

As she grew older, that quality of here also intensified, she could always make the best decisions, until her many peers and even her elders silently approved of her leadership.

Simply said, she was just like a natural-born leader.

But there was something that Garen could not understand at all, and that was the reason behind Raffaele creating a Blood Pact Group. The core members of the group were also all shrouded in mystery, and could not be seen anywhere, but there were a ton of outer members everywhere, be it boys or girls, a large portion of the excelling students had all joined this club.

Watching Raffaele turn as though to leave, Garen suddenly pulled her back.

"Don’t rush, let me show you one last magic trick."

Raffaele smiled, turned around and looked at Garen, her expression full of anticipation. Sometimes Garen would show her some magic tricks that looked very magical, they were very interesting, and also very fun.

Garen smiled slightly as he held open both hands, his palm upturned in front of her.

"There’s nothing in my hands, right?"

"And then…"

He gripped his hands lightly, and then, right in front of Raffaele’s eyes, he gripped them slowly, as though he was holding something in them.

Abruptly, he spread open his fists.

There was a small red pebble in the middle of his palms. They came in a pair, very organized and delicate, and there was a seemingly natural carving of a girl’s blurry features on them.

"Close-distance magic! Impressive!" Surprise flashed through Raffaele’s eyes, her mood apparently lightened, "One each." She just took one of the pebbles, putting it in her palm carefully, and then she looked at Garen with a smile.

"Alright, one each." Garen smiled too.

Raffaele’s thoughts had always been very mature, and also slightly odd, she seemed to be very insistent on something, an aim or ideal that was extremely hard to achieve, that was also why Garen was slowly beginning to accept her, although Raffaele’s growth was incomparable to his, but compared to the other, even more childish normal students, he would naturally choose Raffaele, who he could communicate more with.

With that subtle acknowledgment, over these past two years, the two of them had become a pair that was like friends, but also like lovers.

Keeping the red pebble away, Garen suddenly felt a touch of warmth around his right wrist, and his hand was pulled into Raffaele’s.

Raffaele’s hand grabbed his, placing his right hand on her right chest, and then pressing down slowly.

That perky, full, and bouncy feeling, that warm touch, tinged with the bodily fragrance of a young girl, slowly permeated into his nostrils.

"This is your reward…"

Raffaele turned around and jogged away, leaving behind only her chiming, tinkling laugh.

From afar, Garen watched Raffaele put on her shirt and trousers, get onto her own white motorbike, wave in his direction, and then kick-start the engine, beginning her journey back.

As the motorbike picked up speed, the female rider’s golden hair began to wave backward in the wind.

In a place where Garen could not see, the pretty face under Raffaele’s helmet began to grow colder as she left the beach.

"Since you won’t listen to warnings, looks like we have no choice but to start the war."

She murmured, and the image of that stout white person with the earstuds seemed to appear in her eyes.

****************

Garen remained where he stood, raising his right hand slightly and sniffing it, there was still the girl’s fragrance lingering on it.

"I never thought…" He shook his head and laughed, an ancient monster like him who had lived for so long, was actually beginning to truly feel something for that child-like little girl.

In that instant, it was as though he could see his cousin Hathaway’s shadow on Raffaele.

Turning around and continuing to walk into the water, his exceptional swimming skill allowed him to tread water in the depths of the ocean, and he would not sink even if his body was upright, that was also the reason why his family had slowly begun to put down their concerns and gotten used to this habit of his.

Returning to his previous position, Garen immersed himself into practicing the channeling of his secret technique once more, and he would occasionally use himself as bait, to lure some sea sharks that wanted to eat him, and then he would ‘eat’ them in a few strokes, using them to increase the Black Sethe’s Insidious Palm Power.

Thinking back to how Raffaele had hurried back just now, Garen suddenly thought of something. "Why don’t I follow her quietly and see what she’s up to?"

Raffaele had always been secretive, he had no idea what she was doing, and he had also tried to investigate once before, but it never came up to anything. This time, however, it seemed like something important was happening, so Garen’s curiosity was ever so slightly piqued.

Looking at the sky, he saw that the setting sun was almost about to sink under the sea’s horizon, and only a tiny bit of the arch was still poking out.

Garen trained for a little longer, and only turned around to swim back to shore when the sky had nearly gotten completely dark.

Just then, a shadow seemed to flash before his eyes, a black shadow.

"Hmm?"

Garen frowned slightly, and felt something was amiss, stepping onto the sand bare-footed, he suddenly turned around.

He had no idea when, but somehow there was a delinquent standing behind him, with his hair dyed red and white.

This man was wearing flashy clothes that practically sparkled silver, his hands in his pockets, his head cocked and his expression unhappy as he stared at Garen.

"Who are you?" Garen asked in shock.

"For some reason, looking at a guy like you, who’s so perfect you don’t look like a man, really pisses me off…" The delinquent said, his expression condescending.

"Looks like you’re not a normal person?" Garen asked, ever so slightly surprised.

"Very smart, I like talking to smart people. Alright, look at my eyes." The delinquent’s eyes stared hard at Garen, and his voice suddenly became softer.

Garen felt slightly dizzy, his eyes seemed to have some strange pull and whirlpool, luring him into meeting his gaze. Garen was just about to resist, when something occurred to him, and he forced down the urge to retaliate.

"When Raffaele comes back at night later, you find a chance to send a message to this number using your phone, a blank message. Then you do your best to keep Raffaele there, perhaps truly making her your woman would be a good way to do that." That delinquent’s bleary voice seemed to come from far, far away. At the same time, he showed Garen a paper slip with a number on it, letting Garen see it closely.

Garen relaxed his body and heart, carefully feeling this sudden feeling of fogginess, this new and unfamiliar feeling was as though his own body was reacted automatically. The delinquent in front of him was like a natural enemy, just one glance, was enough to affect most of his main bodily functions.

Despite himself, he knew, if he just obeyed his instincts, he might actually truly have to obey the other person’s instructions.

This strange feeling of being controlled was extremely new and exciting to him.

Unfortunately, although this feeling of being controlled might be very powerful to normal people, to the point where they could not resist it, but to him, he just needed to move his already-formed aura slightly, and he could already easily break through this feeling of being controlled.

It was like tying an elephant with a string as thick as a hair… or covering a powerful time-bomb with a paper lantern.

By the time this feeling vanished, there was already no trace of that delinquent anywhere.

That extremely terrifying speed, as though he teleported, also left Garen in awe.

It was as though his physical body had no weight at all, just like a shadow, moving and stopping at will, completely disregarding momentum.

The night breeze blew softly.

Garen stood alone on the beach, looking at the empty space in front of him, as though that scene just now was just an illusion, and a feeling of excitement rose instantly in his heart.

"This world… is finally not so boring anymore…" The corners of his lips curved slightly, and he turned around, walking toward the rock with his clothes on it.

Soon enough, amidst the roar of a motorcycle engine, a white motorbike rode down the twisting paths, headed towards Grano.

Not long after the motorbike left, behind a rock on the beach, a brunette girl walked out slowly, she looked at the direction Garen had left in quietly, taking out a black cell phone and quickly calling a number.

"The target has left, the plan is a success." She said softly.

"You be careful, don’t let that woman notice your movements." There was an attractive man’s voice coming from the other end.

"Don’t worry, I’ll just distract the guardian for less than a minute, and I’ll just be giving some psychological hints to control them, I won’t do anything more than that, so I surely won’t be discovered."

"That’s good." The male voice on the phone paused, "I’ll come find you at night, wait for me."

The woman’s eyes immediately lit up with a burning passion.

"Mn, I’ll wait for you…"

She put down the phone, turned around, and disappeared into the crack between the rocks.

Chapter 579: Secret 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Brrr…

Amidst the buzzing of the motorcycle engine.

Raffaele rode like the wind down the path between the forests, her body leaning onto the motorbike, her hair flying in the wind, her gaze as sharp as a hawk.

Large swathes of forests flew past her, the bike leaping up suddenly, and then falling down again hard.

Bzzz…

All of a sudden, the bike moved sideways, turned a few rounds, and abruptly stopped in a small clearing in the woods. The tires seemed to emit faint wisps of white smoke.

Raffaele took off her helmet, looking at the few figures who walked out slowly from the surrounding woods, they were all young girls, of around her age.

"Is Vixie back yet?" She asked nonchalantly, leaping off the bike.

"She is, she just arrived in the afternoon train, and rushed here from the city, now she’s catching up on some sleep." One of the black-haired young girls surrounding her replied respectfully.

"What about the others? How many of those who had gone out came back?"

"About six of them came back, the rest of them are occupied and can’t come back for now." The black-haired girl said softly.

"That’s enough." Raffaele nodded, "The Blood Breeds on that side are getting too much, Grano is still our Grano, it’s where our ancestors are buried, not somewhere those outsiders can show off."

"President, you want to open fire?" A brunette girl frowned. "I don’t think Serin’s group would agree."

"It doesn’t matter, this is just a small lesson." Raffaele tossed her long golden hair, her eyes cold as she said so. "Their hands are reaching too far."

"Do we need to report to the elders?" A girl asked.

"No, this was originally their intention." Raffaele smiled, her skintight black clothes showing off her slender body, in the forest that grew gradually darker, matched with her dazzling golden hair, it showed off how deep and powerful she was.

She looked around her, "Gather half of our people, tonight at eight, let’s go to the north area together."

"Yes."

All of the girls around her replied respectfully.

*****************

Brrr…

The white motorbike slowly stopped in front of Garen’s house.

Garen leaped off the bike in his black skin-tight riding clothes, in the dark of the night, on the street leading to his own house, there were several suspicious-looking people around, mixed in with the regular passersby, surrounding the whole house quietly.

Garen looked around subtly, and noticed these people all had a common characteristic, they all looked like small-time delinquents. They seemed to be chewing gum, with their hands in their pockets, but in truth their eyes would occasionally be fixed on his house.

"Watchmen?" Garen pushed his bike into the yard, he could feel that as soon as he pushed his bike into the house, the people watching him slowly retreated one by one.

"Big Brother~~"

As soon as he opened the door, his little sister Vivien bounced out and pounced onto him, the little scamp was in third grade now, wearing a dark red silk skirt, white children’s stockings, her pigtails sticking up at the ends, and add that to her cherubic face, all of it made her a very standard image of the adorable loli.

But as usual, she idolized Garen, and liked to stick to him all day.

"Big Bro, does this look good?" Vivien darted out of Garen’s embrace, and spun around on the spot, her short red skirt flying up slightly, giving off a light and pure feeling.

"Sure, our Vivi is the cutest of all, you’ll definitely be a great beauty who’s loved by everyone in the future!" Garen picked Vivien up in his arms and closed the door behind him.

"Did you bring Vivi a present?"

"Of course."

Garen flipped his hand and brought out a red pebble-like the ones from earlier, this one had the picture of a duckling carved onto it, and looked quite quaint.

He tossed it at the little scamp, and little Vivien instantly bounced away, bringing the stone to show off to Jason. And then there were the sounds of impatient yelling and bright cheerful laughter, evidently the little devil was causing Jason trouble again.

It was a completely different treatment from what Garen got.

Garen went back to his bedroom speechlessly, pulling out his computer notebook, turning it on, and then connecting to the Internet.

With a pitter-patter of the keyboard, he entered in the word, Grano.

Hitting Enter, a list of the most recent news in town appeared.

The most recent result was from one day ago.

‘Two rangers from the Grano Forestry Department were attacked by wolves, the scene too gruesome for words.’

This headline caught his eye at a glance, and Garen moved his cursor, tapping this news piece lightly.

With a light clicking sound, the page was opened.

In the darkness, under the illumination of the white computer light, Garen carefully read that short piece of news, which only had words and no pictures.

‘... The victims’ necks had canine bite barks on either side, and most of their organs had been dug out and eaten by the wild wolves…’

He noticed these words in the news.

Ever since he noticed something was wrong here, Garen had always been paying attention to the different news happening in Grano.

These past few years, he had been constantly collecting news articles, and by now, he had collected up to a hundred different articles.

"This thing again…" Closing the web page, Garen mused slightly. "There are at least about a dozen of these cases every year, a few tourists getting lost in the forest, or drowning to the bottom of the ocean, so that even their bodies could not be found. Haha… what flawless camouflage…"

He let go of the mouse, laced his fingers, and propped his arms in front of the computer.

"Wild wolves? I've lived here for so long, I know there are barely any wolves here, even if someone walked in the dense forests away from the main roads, and walked for half an hour, they might still not come across any wolves, they've practically been cleared out by the hunters, to have a dozen wolf mauling incidents every year, what a joke."

Turning off the computer, Garen stood up and walked to the window, reaching out his hand to peel the curtains open ever so slightly, and looking out.

There really was still someone watching him, but it had reduced from the multiple people just now to just one.

"Looks like Raffaele’s problem is tonight." Garen was thoughtful, he mused for a bit, pulled open in his closet, and found a large black raincoat from inside, this raincoat was one that everyone in town wore, and this one was adult-sized.

He put it over him, and in an instant his whole person was covered in that raincoat, looking just like the wide black hoods from the Totem World.

Pulling on the good as well, and lowering his head, he instantly became a stranger whose features could not even be seen properly.

Garen stood in front of the closet’s dressing mirror, and took a slight breath.

Crack-crack…

His body abruptly began to emit a series of loud cracking sounds, and soon his whole shape had changed slightly, his shoulders were slightly broader, and he utterly hid his presence as well, standing in front of the mirror, it was as though he was merely a fashion dummy in a raincoat, with no indication of life whatsoever.

"After investigating for so long, it's about time I figured out the truth."

He buttoned up his raincoat, walked up to the window, and lightly opened the window.

The person watching him on the street down there was still smoking as he looked this way.

Garen went around the windows by the side of the house, the back of the house was facing the woods, so the side facing the back was completely quiet, and there was barely anybody to be seen.

He opened the window lightly, with a whoosh of wind and a flash of a black shadow, Garen darted straight out of the window, landing soundlessly on the surrounding wall underneath him, and then he landed, as though floating, into the dark recesses of the woods.

Without a moment’s hesitation, Garen walked at a normal pace into the depths of the forest, dressed in his raincoat, he was familiar with the lay of the land around here, so he was completely capable of taking a long road to the place Raffaele’s house was.

The surrounding forest was completely dark, so that he could not even see his fingers in front of him, but every so often he could see moonlight shining down from the cracks above, that was the only signpost he could see in the darkness.

Before long, Garen suddenly stopped in his tracks.

"Who are you!" A black shadow had somehow stood in his path before he had noticed it. It was that smoking watchman. He was dressed fully in black, and his hair was dyed white, his head tilted slightly as he leaned against a large tree.

He was the one who asked that question.

"Speak."

The watchman was cold, and slightly impatient.

Garen did not reply, and instead stood quietly on the spot, not making a sound.

"Could you be Raffaele’s…" White Hair’s expression changed suddenly.

Psst!

Instantly, he disappeared from where he stood.

A piercing wind appeared behind Garen, pale but sharp nails grabbing towards Garen’s back like sharp thorns.

Smack!

White Hair’s fingers were blocked by one arm, and he looked shocked, his figure flashing away, appearing again on Garen’s other side, and this time both his hands grabbed towards Garen mercilessly.

At the same time, he opened his mouth abruptly.

Scree!!!

A piercing soundwave instantly crashed into Garen’s brain.

Bam!!

The four arms crashed into each other hard.

White Hair instantly separated from Garen, both of them taking several steps back, their chests rising and falling heavily.

"You…!" White Hair opened his mouth and was about to say something, when suddenly he saw his opponent disappear in a flash, he instantly knew that was bad, and he quickly used his arms to block the front of his body.

In that instant, there was a loud sound in his mind, and all the hairs on his body stood on end, the arms blocking in front of him did not touch anything, even at such high speeds, his opponent could still change the direction of his attack, and he was hit straight in the stomach, causing him intense pain.

With a bam, his whole body flew into the air, his backbone very obviously bending in the center, like a wooden plank broken in half.

He rolled onto the ground and went quite some distance, all the way until he crashed into a large rock and broke it into smithereens, only then did he finally stop, his body a mess of blood and flesh.

"Damn you!" White Hair leaped up, and with a crack, he actually managed to recover his broken spine, but as soon as he got up, a black shadow instantly appeared in front of him, and reached for his heart with his claw.

White Hair hurriedly avoided it, but with a tearing sound, his right arm was forcefully torn off, and yet strangely, there was no blood coming from the wound at all.

"Ahh!!" White Hair screamed. Using the momentum from his dodge, he instantly began to run away.

But immediately, a fist-sized rock came shooting at his back, piercing through his chest, and dragging out a trail of flesh and blood behind it before it embedded itself into a tree trunk.

White Hair fell face-first onto the ground, a large hole blown straight through his chest, but he immediately bounced back up, his face twisted as he continued to flee.

"His speed and strength are about the same as mine, but his techniques are much stronger!!" White Hair was both angry and terrified, "He’s definitely an experienced Vampire who’s much older than me!! Damn it! Why is there suddenly an experienced Vampire here!!?"

He accelerated madly, but did not sense any hint of killing intent or movement anywhere around him. This just emphasized how well-trained his opponent was.

Psst!

A white arm suddenly pierced through his neck, and a large hole was blown straight through it, creating a mess of flesh and blood.

White Hair stiffened where he stood, his speed instantly coming to a halt.

"The leader… won’t forgive you!!" White Hair forced out these few words.

With a tearing sound, his whole body was torn into four or five chunks, scattered onto the grass and the bottom of the trees.

Garen’s figure slowly appeared on that spot. Glancing at the corpse around him, he turned around and was about to leave.

Smack!

Something seemed to have grabbed his ankle abruptly, a piercing pain coming from the bottom of his foot.

Garen gave it a jolt of power.

With a bam, he instantly jolted away from the thing at his ankle.

Chapter 580: Secret 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He looked down, it was White Hair’s severed hand, its sharp nails furiously scratching about. It was this thing that grabbed on the his ankle earlier, the one that left 5 deep scratch marks.

From afar, White Hair’s skull suddenly split open wide, revealing a gigantic fanged mouth, roaring at Garen.

"Intruder! Chief won’t let you off that easily! You’re dead! Dead!! Hahahahaha…..." White Hair loudly laughed.

Garen bit his lip.

"What strong life force..." Looking at his opponents ferocious fangs, those bloodshot eyes, and that pale skin, it all reminded him of a certain familiar species.

"You’re a blood breed?" He unconsciously said aloud.

White Hair’s laughter suddenly came to an abrupt stop. He looked at Garen, stunned.

"You… You’re not a Vampire?"

Bam!

With a strong stomp, Garen bust open White Hair’s head. Inside, the inside was absent of blood or flesh, just a clump of black dust, nothing else remained.

Taking a quick look at his surroundings, he felt a twitch in his chest. Garen had a fairly clear idea as to what kind of world he was currently in now…

Quickly looking through White Hair’s clothing, he stood up and quickly left the scene. After walking around the woods for a bit, he dumped the clothes and walked back home.

Following the same route, he stealthily went home, without anyone noticing his presence.

In his own bedroom, Garen swiftly closed the curtains.

In the darkness, without even tuning on the light, Garen started inspecting the wound he got from the fight.

It was completely unexpected to him. The fact that when its body had already been completely torn apart, White Hair could still move freely, even to the point where it could wound his body. This kind of monstrous life force, completely eclipses the abilities of the Grandmasters of Combat.

Seeing that his wound didn’t have any infections or scars, he breathed a sigh of relief.

Checking his Attribute Plane, his potential points did not increase at all from killing that vampire. This made him feel slightly disappointed.

Recentering his focus, he started to ponder about the whole issue surrounding Raffaele and the Vampires.

"This vampire, and also the delinquent from the beach, all of these signs point to Raffaele as the cause of them trying to monitor and trying to control me. Being someone who gained the attention from the Vampires, Raffaele’s Blood Pact Group must not be any ordinary group… Raffaele herself must also have some sort of ability comparable to the vampires as well. That kind of power… coupled with the strange phenomenon and culture in the town, it must be a power only this lady can use…"

Garen suddenly remembered, no matter if it were the Earth or the Secret Technique World, there had been legends about Witches.

"What if she’s a witch?" From the collections of messages he’s received in the past and all the ancestral rituals taking place, he gathered that, "She’s most likely a witch."

Coming to 2 possible hypotheses, Garen immediately turned on the laptop in front of him.

"Maybe it’s time for me to start improving my technological skills, it would be good to create a programme specifically for collecting and sorting out the messages…" He searched the web for legends revolving around vampires and witches, but unfortunately for him, most of it were either about novels, television series, or other forms of entertainment. There were also a few search results about myths and urban legends, but most of them had been read before by him, serving no real value.

Connecting to the website of the National Security Agency of the USA, Garen was hoping that there were some relevant records for this issue. However, maybe these kinds of confidential information wouldn’t be uploaded to the Internet. It was highly possible that the information would be saved in the internal Local Area Networks of the agency, sealing it away from the public. As such, even the best hackers in the world would be rendered useless, since the Network wasn’t even connected to the Internet with any cables or optical fibers.

Unlike before, when looking through the national criminal records this time, especially the murder and disappearance cases, Garen made a new discovery.

All the criminal reports by the government had been carefully selected. Some of the resolutions of the cases seem perfect, but it still somehow felt off. Even some of the testimonials given by eyewitnesses, they seem to be slightly flawed and occasionally had some mutually contradictory statements.

Connecting the dots, a thought started to form in Garen’s brain.

The situation was becoming more and more clear, he was more and more sure of his hypothesis.

"Blood Breed, Vampires, and Witches, even if they weren't exactly the same, something similar to them exists here."

Closing his laptop, he sat back down in the darkness.

He heard the sounds of the door closing, his parents were home. He could vaguely hear his sister and her mother, Trish, talking,

Garen was sitting on the edge of hs bed, thinking back about his battle with White Hair.

The battle was quite easy. Even though his body hasn’t returned to the level it was back in the Totem World, and his average stat points sat only at slightly above 2, he had his years of battle experience and his secret technique, so beating White Hair was pretty effortless.

"His speed and strength was almost close to mine… No, it might even be better than mine. He also had that absurd life force and regeneration…" Garen said while caressing his skin, "It was only because his technique was bad, or rather he didn’t have any technique, just average level street-fighting skills. His speed was so fast to the degree that he himself wasn’t able to control his movements. This kind of vampire was nothing to be feared. But that life force though…"

Thinking back to the hand that could continue to attack its opponent, Garen’s knowledge of vampires had increased.

"For a pawn used to tail me, he already had strength and speed on par with me… Blood Breed’s advantages over an average human being sure is overwhelming."

Garen was worried that this was not just a normal species of Vampires. From their rank, it seems like White Hair is quite a low-ranked lackey. If even a low-ranked vampire could possess this absurd speed and strength, along with that life force and regeneration, how strong would a high-ranked vampire be?

In addition, the Blood Breed in the legends are immortal creatures.

This point garnered Garen’s attention, could they really live forever? Were they truly immortal?

He was really curious about this.

"Though it’s probably better not to rush to find out at this time… I should take it slow." He felt his slow growth of his Secret Technique - Black Claw of Sethe, although its regenerative ability was quite decent as compared to normal humans, when compared to the Blood Breed, it naturally pales in comparison.

If the Blood Breed were all at the same level as White Hair, he could easily take down a few more of them, but if a stronger Blood Breed appears… Against an absurdly strong unknown lifeform, even Garen felt a bit worried.

After all, the Blood Breed in the legends were monstrous immortal beings. Even in the Secret Techniques world or the Totem World, there wasn't anything that was truly immortal.

At best, there were only beings with extreme longevity, who can live up to thousands of years, like the Demon Phoenix. However, Vampires were different… If we go according to the legends, it’s wasn't just thousands of years, they could even be millions of years old…

"This world was not as normal as I thought…"

******

"What? We lost a tailing agent?"

In the church at the North of the town, a muscular man with earrings squinted at the minion giving a report to him.

It was the middle of the night, a group of blood-covered delinquents, most of them had some sort of injury or wound, with some major injuries such as the loss of 2 of their limbs, to minor ones like a few mere scratches.

However, even some of the minor injuries looked absurd, there was even a guy with a metal pole impaled in his chest. The entire church looked like a horror film makeup room.

"Yes, when it was time to change shifts, I went to find Carl, but that guy totally disappeared. I tried looking around in the surrounding areas but he was nowhere to be found, he might have left himself." The guy who was speaking was a dark-skinned, muscular male with a bandage wrapping his head, covering one of his eyes. Blood could be seen slowly seeping through the bandage.

"Looks like it was Raffaele’s work. She must’ve found something out." The white chief calmly said, "This bastard seems to be much more of a handful as compared to her grandma…"

"Since this line has been discovered, what are your plans for this?" The Reverend Father suddenly walked out from the side, frustratedly looking at the chief.

"Let’s leave it be for now. We’ve suffered quite a bit of damage, but it should be the same for that bloody witch too. In my estimation, both parties would be needing quite some time to regroup and recover." The white man hesitated, "I can’t shake the feeling that Raffaele is scheming something, that bastard is known as Grano’s strongest witch, tonights actions were definitely not just a warning shot."

"That Blood Pact Group or whatever, except for that old Witch, have less than a hundred core members. As long as you don’t break your contract with the ancestors and willfully destroy the balance, no matter how strong she is she won’t need to initiate in breaking the rule." The Reverend Father shook his head, "And what about those other Vampires who are roaming about outside? How are you gonna take care of that?"

"What do those random vampires have to do with me?" The white male laughed coldly, "Let that witch take care of them. I have already sent the a message before they entered my turf: ‘Those who don’t obey me, Jaern, shall all die."

******

BumTskBumTskBumTsk... My heart is ways onn fr you....cleary yt unser dain sky…

In the nightclub, the DJ was mixing the music tracks with a strong rhythmic beat, with loud foreign lyrics howling through the speakers.

The people on the dancefloor were twisting their bodies to the music under the flashing strobe lights. Some were screaming, some were clapping, and there were even couples tongue-deep with each other.

Two big, muscular men were at the centre of this dance floor, each with a hot girl in their arms, moving their body to the beat.

As the burly men were grabbing a handful of the girls' breasts, a loud sound suddenly started ringing in their ears.

The men’s pupils suddenly dilated. They looked at each other, then pushed away their respective girls and forced their way out of the club.

Ignoring the calls of the girls behind them, both of them left the bar. After talking a few turns, they arrived at a dead end alleyway.

It was nearing midnight, the alleyway was completely empty.

Poof!

Two strong women appeared out of nowhere and pinned the two men against the alley wall.

"You broke the rules."

At the exit of the alleyway, a beautiful young lady with long blond hair appeared. She coldly glared at the two guys.

"A witch? What rules? We didn’t do anything!" One of the guys frantically said. "We just arrived today morning!"

With a loud "bam", one of the girls kneed him in the gut, rendering him unable to speak.

"No sucking blood in the public, this is the rules of our Grano…"

"Bullshit!" The other guy interrupted, "Humans are nothing but animals, we will eat what we want whenever we want! If it wasn’t for you bitches and that bunch of traitors!"

Bam!!

This time, the impact was much louder.

The guy rolled back his eyes, nearly completely unconscious.

"Traitors?" The blonde shook her head, "Slaughter them. They are not welcome in Grano."

As she walked out of the alleyway, she could vaguely hear the sounds of the two girls’ ferocious hits, coupled with the men's desperate cries.

Chapter 581: Secret 5

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After a good night’s sleep, Garen slowly rose from his bed.

Taking a deep breath, he turned to look at the window. The sunlight was seeping through his curtains, making the dust in the air somewhat visible.

He pushed away his blanket, once again looking at his wounded heel from yesterday. Except for a light red scar at the very top, it looks nothing like a wound anymore.

Today was a weekend, so he didn’t have to rush to school.

After dressing himself, he walked up to the window and opened the curtains.

"Hey!!"

Raffaele was on her bike waiting for him as usual.

Opening the window, Garen shouted, "What’s the plan?"

"How about the beach again? We can make barbecued seafood!" Raffaele answered after some thought.

"Sure." Garen didn’t invite her to come into his house. The last time she was in the house, there was an awkward atmosphere.

"I’ll be out in a bit!!" Garen shouted out loud.

Walking out of the bedroom, Jason and his sister Vivien were already eating breakfast in the kitchen. His mother was still in her study, and his father was in the living room sitting, talking with his new research student about their learning objectives for the day.

"Going out again?" Jason asked loudly.

"Yea, Rafi is waiting outside." Garen sloppily picked up 2 pieces of bread and spread some tomato jam on them, chugged a few mouthfuls of milk, then walked straight towards the door.

"Bro, you haven’t even brushed your teeth!" Vivien loudly said.

"Oh, right!" Garen placed the bread on the bathroom counter and proceeded to speedily lather his teeth with toothpaste.

All of the sudden, the bathroom door cracked open, and in came a red-headed girl in a black dress. Looking at Garen, she was a bit shocked, but managed to recover herself and politely gave her greetings.

"Good morning big brother Garen."

"Oh, Morning. You are?"

"She’s my best friend Arisa! She came to visit, she’s a tourist!" His sister Vivien ran it and answered. "Arisa, this is my brother."

This girl looked no older than 10, she gave of the aura of a shy young lady. With Garen staring intently at her, she started to blush.

"I-I’m Arisa, n-n-nice to meet you, big brother Garen…"

"Same here, but sorry, I have a friend outside waiting for me, so I’ll leave you in my sister’s care," Garen said after gargling, wiping off the remaining bubbles around his mouth.

He did not know why, but he felt that this Arisa was a bit different from other average people, so he couldn’t help but look at her a bit more.

"Arisa is here with her older sister, but the inn was full already, I ran into her at the town center, so I offered her to stay at our house," Vivien answered seriously. "Her sister is living in Serin’s place next door!"

"Ahh that’s great. Travelling at such a young age." Garen started ruffling her hair a bit, lightly patting her head, making her blush even more.

Her hands were behind her back, playing with her fingers frantically.

"Then I’ll be off, you guys have fun! Grano is a quiet and beautiful place, I hope you guys enjoy yourselves!" Garen said with a smile, walking towards the door.

"No worries, I’ll take good care of them!" Jason confidently slapped his chest, there was a sly grin on his face, he probably was scheming on bringing them through some strange tour.

Opening the door, a tall brunette girl with long hair was standing at the side of the gate, wearing a black slim fit windbreaker, carrying a small purse. She had an oval face and white skin, giving of a cool and unapproachable aura. At the moment, she was staring blankly at the distance.

This beautiful cool girl was still giving off that unapproachable vibe, even when she was just staring idly at nothing.

Garen, clad in nothing but a simple T-shirt and jeans, started pushing his white motorcycle out of his garage. The sound seemed to have startled the girl.

She frowned as he walked over.

"Good morning, I am Arisa’s older sister. I am here to pick her up. Thank you for your hospitality from yesterday." The brunette bent down slightly and gave a proper curtsy.

"There’s no need for the formalities…" Garen felt that this girl was slightly too serious.

"It’s only appropriate," she replied seriously. "Nice to meet you, my name is Isaros, I’m in your care."

"Nice to meet you." Garen nodded as he opened the gate and pushed his motorcycle out. " Arisa is inside with my sister, please make yourself at home, I didn’t lock the doors."

"Then, sorry for interrupting." Isaros bowed slightly.

Garen quickly assessed this girl, she looked younger than twenty, and had a cool aura about her. She was well-mannered but somehow spoke in a very traditional, formal manner. This made her even more unapproachable.

Furthermore, the name "Isaros" reminded him of the colloquial name of Duskdune Shura in the Totem World - Anzera. The two were only a syllable apart, this gave Garen a strange sense of familiarity.

"Grano is a beautiful and quiet place, I hope you guys enjoy your stay!"

Isaros nodded with all the seriousness in the world, "Thank you."

Garen looked back. He saw Jason frantically opening the door, his face blushing like a beetroot. He didn’t even dare to look Isaros straight in the eye. Garen finally knew why he was so adamant in taking the initiative to give them a tour just now.

Pushing his motorcycle, he waved to Raffaele, who was standing afar. They then proceeded to ride off.

Coldly looking at the direction Garen and Raffaele headed in, Isaros slightly frowned.

They weren’t here in this town as tourists, although, how they managed to escape their pursuers from Primary Colors escaped her. Fortunately for them, this was no doubt one of the safer places they had arrived at. She could probably stay here with her younger sister for around 2 more years.

Thinking about that, she let out a sigh of relief.

Arisa was still so young, yet she had to put up with so much pressure, living her life like a fugitive. Hopefully, they could live here for some more time… In the best case, the people from Primary Colors won’t ever find them… They already gave up trying to seek revenge for all the things in the past, all she wanted now was to live a peaceful, normal life, watching her sister grow up.

******

Two motorcycles were speeding across the woods.

As the sound of the motorcycle engines roared through the woods, they could see rustling leaves slowly falling to the ground.

Garen was wearing a black helmet, following closely behind Raffaele. However, his mind was still fixated on the sisters Arisa and Isaros, from just now.

The kind of feeling they give off, it was as if… there was an indescribable kind of vibe, strange and thick, but he just couldn’t put his tongue on it.

"What are you thinking about?" Raffaele’s voice interrupted his line of thought, she had apparently slowed down, now riding next to Garen.

"Nothing much, I just had a weird dream last night, I haven’t calmed down completely yet." Garen didn’t dare to say that he was thinking of 2 other girls. Raffaele treated him well. When it came to things like this, she had a short temper, if he wasn’t cautious he could easily piss her off. These unnecessary conflicts should just be avoided.

"You’re not thinking of other girls, are you?" Raffaele asked in suspicion.

"Of course not. I already have you." Garen nervously laughed.

"Hmmm."

Raffaele once again sped up and went ahead.

With this little interruption, Garen somehow figured out what he was feeling earlier on.

He might be on to something here.

The vibe he got from looking at the 2 sisters, felt similar to when he was looking at the history of the planet in the Totem World.

Although he didn’t see any special imagery or messages, but that unique vibe he got, was exactly like when he was viewing the history of the planet from outside of the planet in the Totem World!

"This feeling..." He muttered with his head down. Although his sights were still on the road, his mind was on the sisters.

"It should be from the Soul Seed…" He finally managed to distinguish this feeling he had.

Soul seeds are hidden in the deepest parts of one’s soul, at this moment, it was emitting a strange wave, affecting his current thoughts.

He felt that, around the 2 sisters, a lot of interesting things will start to happen.

Screech!!

The 2 motorcycles came to a halt on the road next to the beach, sliding into the opposite direction which they came from.

The two stepped off of their respective bikes and removed their helmets.

"Why were you so out of it just now? Are you starting to fancy that girl from before?" Raffaele aggressively asked, her hands on her hips, standing right in front of Garen.

"How is that possible?" Garen said, "It was just about the dream I had last night…"

"Stop lying! I can see it clearly in your eyes that you were thinking of the girl you saw earlier." Raffaele interrupted.

"Alright alright… I admit it, but it was only because that girl gave off a weird vibe, nothing more." Garen meekly admitted.

"She’s just a tourist, what’s so weird about that? You’re my man, don’t you dare go around playing with other girls! Or else, hmmmm…" Raffaele raised her fists up in a threatening manner, her cute appearance making such a violent pose made Garen chuckle. He couldn’t resist his urge to pinch her angry face.

The two then started to play fight a bit, chasing each other on the beach, accidentally falling into the sea getting themselves all wet.

Going back to their bikes, while they were changing their clothes, Garen quickly took out his phone and sent a blank text to the number he got from that Vampire yesterday. After that, he deleted the message records and kept his phone.

Looking to his side, he saw Raffaele had changed into her swimsuit.

"What do you wanna eat? I’ll go catch some for you. I might have to leave a bit earlier because I have some stuff I need to do."

"Can’t you even have some fun on just on the weekend?" Raffaele’s pure white skin was glowing under the sunlight, almost as if it were forming a halo. It was surprising, that after spending so much time in the sun, her skin was as white as ever.

"I have some stuff to do. As you know my parents are always busy with their things, when I got old enough they stopped taking care of us too much, so most I do of the stuff at home." Garen shrugged.

"Oh, right." Raffaele leaned closer, her height was slightly shorter than Garen, she looked up at him innocently. "If there’s any trouble, don’t hesitate to ask me for help, don’t try to carry the burden by yourself, okay?"

"Of course, I won’t forget my manly girlfriend is one of the strongest girls in town." Garen lightly grabbed her waist, his hand slowly moving downwards, almost reaching the thigh gap below her butt.

Raffaele smiled slyly, then turned around out of his embrace.

"Alright, since you have some stuff to do, when are you leaving?"

"We can still play around for about 2 hours." Garen disappointedly retracted his hands.